[
  {
    "answer": " Well I just think we have much bigger risks",
    "question": " Don’t good businessmen hedge against risks, not ignore them?",
    "question_vector": "q6qq2hVYwj8AAAAA4GwcP1VVVYXRwak/q6qqMhJEqr+rqqpK0keMP6uqqipXR5G/VVVV1aTqk78AAADQy5WGv6uqqqo4Sqq/q6qqqjLKsD+rqqry+nWtv6uqqiqJjMI/AAAAgA7PeT8AAAAA3NKlPwAAAIAVnZY/AAAAgMxCqT+rqqqKueXCPwAAAMDcF4a/AAAAQM/YqD+rqqrqTWm4v1VVVTV7PcY/VVVVlXIJrb+rqqrKL0iOv1VVVdUySIC/AAAA4LL/tb+rqqoq9UvOv6uqquoxQ50/VVVVZWVXsb9VVVXVHY+bv6uqqkrcFLc/VVVVddoJ2D8AAACgxt61PwAAAPgcy8E/q6qq3mTKub8AAADA2zaav1VVVRWiF6+/q6qqChPxzb+rqqqaIeqmv1VVVeVVbpU/VVVVtSgntL9VVVW1SMzBv6uqqioh4I6/VVVVlbMPxz+rqqoKaN/HPwAAAMDyysQ/q6qqmo7ywr+rqqoSRZO+vwAAAGRzhcE/VVVVpQVBtj8AAACAkA55vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "hedge",
      "businessmen",
      "risks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean I think we have militarily tremendous risks",
    "question": " Don’t good businessmen hedge against risks, not ignore them?",
    "question_vector": "q6qq2hVYwj8AAAAA4GwcP1VVVYXRwak/q6qqMhJEqr+rqqpK0keMP6uqqipXR5G/VVVV1aTqk78AAADQy5WGv6uqqqo4Sqq/q6qqqjLKsD+rqqry+nWtv6uqqiqJjMI/AAAAgA7PeT8AAAAA3NKlPwAAAIAVnZY/AAAAgMxCqT+rqqqKueXCPwAAAMDcF4a/AAAAQM/YqD+rqqrqTWm4v1VVVTV7PcY/VVVVlXIJrb+rqqrKL0iOv1VVVdUySIC/AAAA4LL/tb+rqqoq9UvOv6uqquoxQ50/VVVVZWVXsb9VVVXVHY+bv6uqqkrcFLc/VVVVddoJ2D8AAACgxt61PwAAAPgcy8E/q6qq3mTKub8AAADA2zaav1VVVRWiF6+/q6qqChPxzb+rqqqaIeqmv1VVVeVVbpU/VVVVtSgntL9VVVW1SMzBv6uqqioh4I6/VVVVlbMPxz+rqqoKaN/HPwAAAMDyysQ/q6qqmo7ywr+rqqoSRZO+vwAAAGRzhcE/VVVVpQVBtj8AAACAkA55vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "hedge",
      "businessmen",
      "risks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think we’re in tremendous peril",
    "question": " Don’t good businessmen hedge against risks, not ignore them?",
    "question_vector": "q6qq2hVYwj8AAAAA4GwcP1VVVYXRwak/q6qqMhJEqr+rqqpK0keMP6uqqipXR5G/VVVV1aTqk78AAADQy5WGv6uqqqo4Sqq/q6qqqjLKsD+rqqry+nWtv6uqqiqJjMI/AAAAgA7PeT8AAAAA3NKlPwAAAIAVnZY/AAAAgMxCqT+rqqqKueXCPwAAAMDcF4a/AAAAQM/YqD+rqqrqTWm4v1VVVTV7PcY/VVVVlXIJrb+rqqrKL0iOv1VVVdUySIC/AAAA4LL/tb+rqqoq9UvOv6uqquoxQ50/VVVVZWVXsb9VVVXVHY+bv6uqqkrcFLc/VVVVddoJ2D8AAACgxt61PwAAAPgcy8E/q6qq3mTKub8AAADA2zaav1VVVRWiF6+/q6qqChPxzb+rqqqaIeqmv1VVVeVVbpU/VVVVtSgntL9VVVW1SMzBv6uqqioh4I6/VVVVlbMPxz+rqqoKaN/HPwAAAMDyysQ/q6qqmo7ywr+rqqoSRZO+vwAAAGRzhcE/VVVVpQVBtj8AAACAkA55vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "hedge",
      "businessmen",
      "risks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think our biggest form of climate change we should worry about is nuclear weapons",
    "question": " Don’t good businessmen hedge against risks, not ignore them?",
    "question_vector": "q6qq2hVYwj8AAAAA4GwcP1VVVYXRwak/q6qqMhJEqr+rqqpK0keMP6uqqipXR5G/VVVV1aTqk78AAADQy5WGv6uqqqo4Sqq/q6qqqjLKsD+rqqry+nWtv6uqqiqJjMI/AAAAgA7PeT8AAAAA3NKlPwAAAIAVnZY/AAAAgMxCqT+rqqqKueXCPwAAAMDcF4a/AAAAQM/YqD+rqqrqTWm4v1VVVTV7PcY/VVVVlXIJrb+rqqrKL0iOv1VVVdUySIC/AAAA4LL/tb+rqqoq9UvOv6uqquoxQ50/VVVVZWVXsb9VVVXVHY+bv6uqqkrcFLc/VVVVddoJ2D8AAACgxt61PwAAAPgcy8E/q6qq3mTKub8AAADA2zaav1VVVRWiF6+/q6qqChPxzb+rqqqaIeqmv1VVVeVVbpU/VVVVtSgntL9VVVW1SMzBv6uqqioh4I6/VVVVlbMPxz+rqqoKaN/HPwAAAMDyysQ/q6qqmo7ywr+rqqoSRZO+vwAAAGRzhcE/VVVVpQVBtj8AAACAkA55vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "hedge",
      "businessmen",
      "risks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " The biggest risk to the world, to me – I know President Obama thought it was climate change – to me the biggest risk is nuclear weapons",
    "question": " Don’t good businessmen hedge against risks, not ignore them?",
    "question_vector": "q6qq2hVYwj8AAAAA4GwcP1VVVYXRwak/q6qqMhJEqr+rqqpK0keMP6uqqipXR5G/VVVV1aTqk78AAADQy5WGv6uqqqo4Sqq/q6qqqjLKsD+rqqry+nWtv6uqqiqJjMI/AAAAgA7PeT8AAAAA3NKlPwAAAIAVnZY/AAAAgMxCqT+rqqqKueXCPwAAAMDcF4a/AAAAQM/YqD+rqqrqTWm4v1VVVTV7PcY/VVVVlXIJrb+rqqrKL0iOv1VVVdUySIC/AAAA4LL/tb+rqqoq9UvOv6uqquoxQ50/VVVVZWVXsb9VVVXVHY+bv6uqqkrcFLc/VVVVddoJ2D8AAACgxt61PwAAAPgcy8E/q6qq3mTKub8AAADA2zaav1VVVRWiF6+/q6qqChPxzb+rqqqaIeqmv1VVVeVVbpU/VVVVtSgntL9VVVW1SMzBv6uqqioh4I6/VVVVlbMPxz+rqqoKaN/HPwAAAMDyysQ/q6qqmo7ywr+rqqoSRZO+vwAAAGRzhcE/VVVVpQVBtj8AAACAkA55vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "hedge",
      "businessmen",
      "risks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " That’s – that is climate change",
    "question": " Don’t good businessmen hedge against risks, not ignore them?",
    "question_vector": "q6qq2hVYwj8AAAAA4GwcP1VVVYXRwak/q6qqMhJEqr+rqqpK0keMP6uqqipXR5G/VVVV1aTqk78AAADQy5WGv6uqqqo4Sqq/q6qqqjLKsD+rqqry+nWtv6uqqiqJjMI/AAAAgA7PeT8AAAAA3NKlPwAAAIAVnZY/AAAAgMxCqT+rqqqKueXCPwAAAMDcF4a/AAAAQM/YqD+rqqrqTWm4v1VVVTV7PcY/VVVVlXIJrb+rqqrKL0iOv1VVVdUySIC/AAAA4LL/tb+rqqoq9UvOv6uqquoxQ50/VVVVZWVXsb9VVVXVHY+bv6uqqkrcFLc/VVVVddoJ2D8AAACgxt61PwAAAPgcy8E/q6qq3mTKub8AAADA2zaav1VVVRWiF6+/q6qqChPxzb+rqqqaIeqmv1VVVeVVbpU/VVVVtSgntL9VVVW1SMzBv6uqqioh4I6/VVVVlbMPxz+rqqoKaN/HPwAAAMDyysQ/q6qqmo7ywr+rqqoSRZO+vwAAAGRzhcE/VVVVpQVBtj8AAACAkA55vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "hedge",
      "businessmen",
      "risks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " That is a disaster, and we don’t even know where the nuclear weapons are right now",
    "question": " Don’t good businessmen hedge against risks, not ignore them?",
    "question_vector": "q6qq2hVYwj8AAAAA4GwcP1VVVYXRwak/q6qqMhJEqr+rqqpK0keMP6uqqipXR5G/VVVV1aTqk78AAADQy5WGv6uqqqo4Sqq/q6qqqjLKsD+rqqry+nWtv6uqqiqJjMI/AAAAgA7PeT8AAAAA3NKlPwAAAIAVnZY/AAAAgMxCqT+rqqqKueXCPwAAAMDcF4a/AAAAQM/YqD+rqqrqTWm4v1VVVTV7PcY/VVVVlXIJrb+rqqrKL0iOv1VVVdUySIC/AAAA4LL/tb+rqqoq9UvOv6uqquoxQ50/VVVVZWVXsb9VVVXVHY+bv6uqqkrcFLc/VVVVddoJ2D8AAACgxt61PwAAAPgcy8E/q6qq3mTKub8AAADA2zaav1VVVRWiF6+/q6qqChPxzb+rqqqaIeqmv1VVVeVVbpU/VVVVtSgntL9VVVW1SMzBv6uqqioh4I6/VVVVlbMPxz+rqqoKaN/HPwAAAMDyysQ/q6qqmo7ywr+rqqoSRZO+vwAAAGRzhcE/VVVVpQVBtj8AAACAkA55vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "hedge",
      "businessmen",
      "risks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We don’t know who has them",
    "question": " Don’t good businessmen hedge against risks, not ignore them?",
    "question_vector": "q6qq2hVYwj8AAAAA4GwcP1VVVYXRwak/q6qqMhJEqr+rqqpK0keMP6uqqipXR5G/VVVV1aTqk78AAADQy5WGv6uqqqo4Sqq/q6qqqjLKsD+rqqry+nWtv6uqqiqJjMI/AAAAgA7PeT8AAAAA3NKlPwAAAIAVnZY/AAAAgMxCqT+rqqqKueXCPwAAAMDcF4a/AAAAQM/YqD+rqqrqTWm4v1VVVTV7PcY/VVVVlXIJrb+rqqrKL0iOv1VVVdUySIC/AAAA4LL/tb+rqqoq9UvOv6uqquoxQ50/VVVVZWVXsb9VVVXVHY+bv6uqqkrcFLc/VVVVddoJ2D8AAACgxt61PwAAAPgcy8E/q6qq3mTKub8AAADA2zaav1VVVRWiF6+/q6qqChPxzb+rqqqaIeqmv1VVVeVVbpU/VVVVtSgntL9VVVW1SMzBv6uqqioh4I6/VVVVlbMPxz+rqqoKaN/HPwAAAMDyysQ/q6qqmo7ywr+rqqoSRZO+vwAAAGRzhcE/VVVVpQVBtj8AAACAkA55vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "hedge",
      "businessmen",
      "risks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We don’t know who’s trying to get them",
    "question": " Don’t good businessmen hedge against risks, not ignore them?",
    "question_vector": "q6qq2hVYwj8AAAAA4GwcP1VVVYXRwak/q6qqMhJEqr+rqqpK0keMP6uqqipXR5G/VVVV1aTqk78AAADQy5WGv6uqqqo4Sqq/q6qqqjLKsD+rqqry+nWtv6uqqiqJjMI/AAAAgA7PeT8AAAAA3NKlPwAAAIAVnZY/AAAAgMxCqT+rqqqKueXCPwAAAMDcF4a/AAAAQM/YqD+rqqrqTWm4v1VVVTV7PcY/VVVVlXIJrb+rqqrKL0iOv1VVVdUySIC/AAAA4LL/tb+rqqoq9UvOv6uqquoxQ50/VVVVZWVXsb9VVVXVHY+bv6uqqkrcFLc/VVVVddoJ2D8AAACgxt61PwAAAPgcy8E/q6qq3mTKub8AAADA2zaav1VVVRWiF6+/q6qqChPxzb+rqqqaIeqmv1VVVeVVbpU/VVVVtSgntL9VVVW1SMzBv6uqqioh4I6/VVVVlbMPxz+rqqoKaN/HPwAAAMDyysQ/q6qqmo7ywr+rqqoSRZO+vwAAAGRzhcE/VVVVpQVBtj8AAACAkA55vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "hedge",
      "businessmen",
      "risks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " The biggest risk for this world and this country is nuclear weapons, the power of nuclear weapons",
    "question": " Don’t good businessmen hedge against risks, not ignore them?",
    "question_vector": "q6qq2hVYwj8AAAAA4GwcP1VVVYXRwak/q6qqMhJEqr+rqqpK0keMP6uqqipXR5G/VVVV1aTqk78AAADQy5WGv6uqqqo4Sqq/q6qqqjLKsD+rqqry+nWtv6uqqiqJjMI/AAAAgA7PeT8AAAAA3NKlPwAAAIAVnZY/AAAAgMxCqT+rqqqKueXCPwAAAMDcF4a/AAAAQM/YqD+rqqrqTWm4v1VVVTV7PcY/VVVVlXIJrb+rqqrKL0iOv1VVVdUySIC/AAAA4LL/tb+rqqoq9UvOv6uqquoxQ50/VVVVZWVXsb9VVVXVHY+bv6uqqkrcFLc/VVVVddoJ2D8AAACgxt61PwAAAPgcy8E/q6qq3mTKub8AAADA2zaav1VVVRWiF6+/q6qqChPxzb+rqqqaIeqmv1VVVeVVbpU/VVVVtSgntL9VVVW1SMzBv6uqqioh4I6/VVVVlbMPxz+rqqoKaN/HPwAAAMDyysQ/q6qqmo7ywr+rqqoSRZO+vwAAAGRzhcE/VVVVpQVBtj8AAACAkA55vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "hedge",
      "businessmen",
      "risks"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think there’s a change in weather",
    "question": " You think climate change is a real thing? Is there human-caused climate change?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqqsCJWL8AAADUk36QPwAAAED5+Xi/VVVVFYDcqr9VVVXVjIurPwAAAAB8D2E/AAAAwFzhoL9VVVVFlq2zvwAAAMDGiLG/AAAAIOYgmD+rqqqqCh02vwAAACDM5LI/VVVV1WgDvL+rqqoijJ6TPwAAAMB5Eb0/q6qqSnepxT9VVVV1z0m8PwAAANBOv7S/AAAAODNcpT9VVVUV6frHv1VVVZWpVrC/q6qqquZ3br+rqqpa3raWPwAAAIAgiYe/q6qqiqxjwz+rqqrK9inVvwAAAODYxsO/AAAAIDqqhz+rqqrqKli9PwAAAADAvpg/VVVVNY9+5T8AAABAD8u6P6uqqrrfaMG/VVVVVav7xr+rqqpKZ0Kzv6uqqgp12cG/VVVVVaeHcb+rqqqqpD2PP1VVVVW0e5C/q6qq6hhdrr+rqqqqMijBv6uqqmrOGmk/q6qqCoK9oL9VVVW1zxOpP1VVVVVDVG+/VVVVdX5xrT8AAACAcFGcP1VVVRWrrrk/AAAA9Rm3pj8AAAAAOvjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "change",
      "change"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I am not a great believer in man-made climate change",
    "question": " You think climate change is a real thing? Is there human-caused climate change?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqqsCJWL8AAADUk36QPwAAAED5+Xi/VVVVFYDcqr9VVVXVjIurPwAAAAB8D2E/AAAAwFzhoL9VVVVFlq2zvwAAAMDGiLG/AAAAIOYgmD+rqqqqCh02vwAAACDM5LI/VVVV1WgDvL+rqqoijJ6TPwAAAMB5Eb0/q6qqSnepxT9VVVV1z0m8PwAAANBOv7S/AAAAODNcpT9VVVUV6frHv1VVVZWpVrC/q6qqquZ3br+rqqpa3raWPwAAAIAgiYe/q6qqiqxjwz+rqqrK9inVvwAAAODYxsO/AAAAIDqqhz+rqqrqKli9PwAAAADAvpg/VVVVNY9+5T8AAABAD8u6P6uqqrrfaMG/VVVVVav7xr+rqqpKZ0Kzv6uqqgp12cG/VVVVVaeHcb+rqqqqpD2PP1VVVVW0e5C/q6qq6hhdrr+rqqqqMijBv6uqqmrOGmk/q6qqCoK9oL9VVVW1zxOpP1VVVVVDVG+/VVVVdX5xrT8AAACAcFGcP1VVVRWrrrk/AAAA9Rm3pj8AAAAAOvjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "change",
      "change"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’m not a great believer",
    "question": " You think climate change is a real thing? Is there human-caused climate change?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqqsCJWL8AAADUk36QPwAAAED5+Xi/VVVVFYDcqr9VVVXVjIurPwAAAAB8D2E/AAAAwFzhoL9VVVVFlq2zvwAAAMDGiLG/AAAAIOYgmD+rqqqqCh02vwAAACDM5LI/VVVV1WgDvL+rqqoijJ6TPwAAAMB5Eb0/q6qqSnepxT9VVVV1z0m8PwAAANBOv7S/AAAAODNcpT9VVVUV6frHv1VVVZWpVrC/q6qqquZ3br+rqqpa3raWPwAAAIAgiYe/q6qqiqxjwz+rqqrK9inVvwAAAODYxsO/AAAAIDqqhz+rqqrqKli9PwAAAADAvpg/VVVVNY9+5T8AAABAD8u6P6uqqrrfaMG/VVVVVav7xr+rqqpKZ0Kzv6uqqgp12cG/VVVVVaeHcb+rqqqqpD2PP1VVVVW0e5C/q6qq6hhdrr+rqqqqMijBv6uqqmrOGmk/q6qqCoK9oL9VVVW1zxOpP1VVVVVDVG+/VVVVdX5xrT8AAACAcFGcP1VVVRWrrrk/AAAA9Rm3pj8AAAAAOvjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "change",
      "change"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " There is certainly a change in weather that goes – if you look, they had global cooling in the 1920s and now they have global warming, although now they don’t know if they have global warming",
    "question": " You think climate change is a real thing? Is there human-caused climate change?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqqsCJWL8AAADUk36QPwAAAED5+Xi/VVVVFYDcqr9VVVXVjIurPwAAAAB8D2E/AAAAwFzhoL9VVVVFlq2zvwAAAMDGiLG/AAAAIOYgmD+rqqqqCh02vwAAACDM5LI/VVVV1WgDvL+rqqoijJ6TPwAAAMB5Eb0/q6qqSnepxT9VVVV1z0m8PwAAANBOv7S/AAAAODNcpT9VVVUV6frHv1VVVZWpVrC/q6qqquZ3br+rqqpa3raWPwAAAIAgiYe/q6qqiqxjwz+rqqrK9inVvwAAAODYxsO/AAAAIDqqhz+rqqrqKli9PwAAAADAvpg/VVVVNY9+5T8AAABAD8u6P6uqqrrfaMG/VVVVVav7xr+rqqpKZ0Kzv6uqqgp12cG/VVVVVaeHcb+rqqqqpD2PP1VVVVW0e5C/q6qq6hhdrr+rqqqqMijBv6uqqmrOGmk/q6qqCoK9oL9VVVW1zxOpP1VVVVVDVG+/VVVVdX5xrT8AAACAcFGcP1VVVRWrrrk/AAAA9Rm3pj8AAAAAOvjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "change",
      "change"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They call it all sorts of different things; now they’re using “extreme weather” I guess more than any other phrase",
    "question": " You think climate change is a real thing? Is there human-caused climate change?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqqsCJWL8AAADUk36QPwAAAED5+Xi/VVVVFYDcqr9VVVXVjIurPwAAAAB8D2E/AAAAwFzhoL9VVVVFlq2zvwAAAMDGiLG/AAAAIOYgmD+rqqqqCh02vwAAACDM5LI/VVVV1WgDvL+rqqoijJ6TPwAAAMB5Eb0/q6qqSnepxT9VVVV1z0m8PwAAANBOv7S/AAAAODNcpT9VVVUV6frHv1VVVZWpVrC/q6qqquZ3br+rqqpa3raWPwAAAIAgiYe/q6qqiqxjwz+rqqrK9inVvwAAAODYxsO/AAAAIDqqhz+rqqrqKli9PwAAAADAvpg/VVVVNY9+5T8AAABAD8u6P6uqqrrfaMG/VVVVVav7xr+rqqpKZ0Kzv6uqqgp12cG/VVVVVaeHcb+rqqqqpD2PP1VVVVW0e5C/q6qq6hhdrr+rqqqqMijBv6uqqmrOGmk/q6qqCoK9oL9VVVW1zxOpP1VVVVVDVG+/VVVVdX5xrT8AAACAcFGcP1VVVRWrrrk/AAAA9Rm3pj8AAAAAOvjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "change",
      "change"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I am not – I know it hurts me with this room, and I know it’s probably a killer with this room – but I am not a believer",
    "question": " You think climate change is a real thing? Is there human-caused climate change?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqqsCJWL8AAADUk36QPwAAAED5+Xi/VVVVFYDcqr9VVVXVjIurPwAAAAB8D2E/AAAAwFzhoL9VVVVFlq2zvwAAAMDGiLG/AAAAIOYgmD+rqqqqCh02vwAAACDM5LI/VVVV1WgDvL+rqqoijJ6TPwAAAMB5Eb0/q6qqSnepxT9VVVV1z0m8PwAAANBOv7S/AAAAODNcpT9VVVUV6frHv1VVVZWpVrC/q6qqquZ3br+rqqpa3raWPwAAAIAgiYe/q6qqiqxjwz+rqqrK9inVvwAAAODYxsO/AAAAIDqqhz+rqqrqKli9PwAAAADAvpg/VVVVNY9+5T8AAABAD8u6P6uqqrrfaMG/VVVVVav7xr+rqqpKZ0Kzv6uqqgp12cG/VVVVVaeHcb+rqqqqpD2PP1VVVVW0e5C/q6qq6hhdrr+rqqqqMijBv6uqqmrOGmk/q6qqCoK9oL9VVVW1zxOpP1VVVVVDVG+/VVVVdX5xrT8AAACAcFGcP1VVVRWrrrk/AAAA9Rm3pj8AAAAAOvjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "change",
      "change"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Perhaps there’s a minor effect, but I’m not a big believer in man-made climate change",
    "question": " You think climate change is a real thing? Is there human-caused climate change?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqqsCJWL8AAADUk36QPwAAAED5+Xi/VVVVFYDcqr9VVVXVjIurPwAAAAB8D2E/AAAAwFzhoL9VVVVFlq2zvwAAAMDGiLG/AAAAIOYgmD+rqqqqCh02vwAAACDM5LI/VVVV1WgDvL+rqqoijJ6TPwAAAMB5Eb0/q6qqSnepxT9VVVV1z0m8PwAAANBOv7S/AAAAODNcpT9VVVUV6frHv1VVVZWpVrC/q6qqquZ3br+rqqpa3raWPwAAAIAgiYe/q6qqiqxjwz+rqqrK9inVvwAAAODYxsO/AAAAIDqqhz+rqqrqKli9PwAAAADAvpg/VVVVNY9+5T8AAABAD8u6P6uqqrrfaMG/VVVVVav7xr+rqqpKZ0Kzv6uqqgp12cG/VVVVVaeHcb+rqqqqpD2PP1VVVVW0e5C/q6qq6hhdrr+rqqqqMijBv6uqqmrOGmk/q6qqCoK9oL9VVVW1zxOpP1VVVVVDVG+/VVVVdX5xrT8AAACAcFGcP1VVVRWrrrk/AAAA9Rm3pj8AAAAAOvjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "change",
      "change"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think that’s something that would be okay",
    "question": " What about having a vote in the House of Representatives?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAcJjaoD8AAAAAtQGXv1VVlWnDFKk/VVVVVUU5jL+rqqpKUYO7PwAAAEgJNbA/AAAAMMNyvr8AAAAYJ9uwP1VVVbX9lr6/q6qqjq9lxb+rqqr6SFrJv6uqqlqTO8K/VVVVPRVorj+rqqrpeiKpPwAAACCgjJ8/q6qqKl7+fD9VVVXVN4BjPwAAAODO9r+/VVVVlWbOtT+rqqrKJvzBvwAAwM7+1sA/AAAAwKh0gD9VVVXVC+eqP6uqqorCpIk/VVVVXWpQs79VVVU1K8nRvwAAAEAbjXu/AAAAELVbsb9VVVWFl8bCv1VVVc312Zs/VVVVFQPd3z8AAAAALcZ+vwAAADDOENC/VVVVtYkYu7+rqqqq6j6IP6uqqjwD+sK/AAAAIDfopD8AAABgxNyKv6uqqipcYX6/VVVVBddusr+rqqrKiKO6v1VVVXXXv5s/AAAA4MiuqL+rqqoqsbp0v1VVVa8rEru/VVVV1cQ6vj+rqqqKLvjLv1VVVVXtuF0/q6qqSnEJdL8AAACIH8yCPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "vote",
      "House",
      "Representatives"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Having representation would be okay",
    "question": " What about having a vote in the House of Representatives?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAcJjaoD8AAAAAtQGXv1VVlWnDFKk/VVVVVUU5jL+rqqpKUYO7PwAAAEgJNbA/AAAAMMNyvr8AAAAYJ9uwP1VVVbX9lr6/q6qqjq9lxb+rqqr6SFrJv6uqqlqTO8K/VVVVPRVorj+rqqrpeiKpPwAAACCgjJ8/q6qqKl7+fD9VVVXVN4BjPwAAAODO9r+/VVVVlWbOtT+rqqrKJvzBvwAAwM7+1sA/AAAAwKh0gD9VVVXVC+eqP6uqqorCpIk/VVVVXWpQs79VVVU1K8nRvwAAAEAbjXu/AAAAELVbsb9VVVWFl8bCv1VVVc312Zs/VVVVFQPd3z8AAAAALcZ+vwAAADDOENC/VVVVtYkYu7+rqqqq6j6IP6uqqjwD+sK/AAAAIDfopD8AAABgxNyKv6uqqipcYX6/VVVVBddusr+rqqrKiKO6v1VVVXXXv5s/AAAA4MiuqL+rqqoqsbp0v1VVVa8rEru/VVVV1cQ6vj+rqqqKLvjLv1VVVVXtuF0/q6qqSnEJdL8AAACIH8yCPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "vote",
      "House",
      "Representatives"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think it’s just something that I don’t think I’d be inclined to do",
    "question": " Tough politically?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYDr0v78AAACgc0O1vwAAAGB22bO/AAAAgH13qL8AAABg2hGdvwAAAIB8/Xk/AAAAYBFHqD8AAACAXnqoPwAAAKBXKry/AAAAoCwfhT8AAACAFEnJvwAAAEDCXZ2/AAAAoGiOx78AAAAAK1a9PwAAAIB8OrE/AAAAgOinZb8AAABgcRHGPwAAAIBDvKy/AAAA4JzJrD8AAADAISjDvwAAAOAac8S/AAAAAG+Drj8AAACAQRSyvwAAAGBl+H0/AAAAwPOknT8AAACgnXLavwAAAGBvoKE/AAAAQLy9uj8AAABgPrXBPwAAAOD1Sii/AAAAgB6y4j8AAABAQE22PwAAAMAOsbm/AAAAILWhkD8AAABgOyRzPwAAAMBv+GS/AAAAIMnkkr8AAADgIUi/PwAAAABbl8C/AAAAIBzd0L8AAAAgbmzAvwAAAABUvKg/AAAAoMaxtT8AAADgSjmiPwAAAKB/a8U/AAAAQHmeqT8AAACgQIOpPwAAACDFtLY/AAAAwHBgqT8AAACgfm3HPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Tough"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’d like to study it",
    "question": " Tough politically?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYDr0v78AAACgc0O1vwAAAGB22bO/AAAAgH13qL8AAABg2hGdvwAAAIB8/Xk/AAAAYBFHqD8AAACAXnqoPwAAAKBXKry/AAAAoCwfhT8AAACAFEnJvwAAAEDCXZ2/AAAAoGiOx78AAAAAK1a9PwAAAIB8OrE/AAAAgOinZb8AAABgcRHGPwAAAIBDvKy/AAAA4JzJrD8AAADAISjDvwAAAOAac8S/AAAAAG+Drj8AAACAQRSyvwAAAGBl+H0/AAAAwPOknT8AAACgnXLavwAAAGBvoKE/AAAAQLy9uj8AAABgPrXBPwAAAOD1Sii/AAAAgB6y4j8AAABAQE22PwAAAMAOsbm/AAAAILWhkD8AAABgOyRzPwAAAMBv+GS/AAAAIMnkkr8AAADgIUi/PwAAAABbl8C/AAAAIBzd0L8AAAAgbmzAvwAAAABUvKg/AAAAoMaxtT8AAADgSjmiPwAAAKB/a8U/AAAAQHmeqT8AAACgQIOpPwAAACDFtLY/AAAAwHBgqT8AAACgfm3HPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Tough"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " It’s not a question really – maybe Chuck didn’t ask me like you’re asking me – I don’t see statehood for D",
    "question": " Tough politically?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYDr0v78AAACgc0O1vwAAAGB22bO/AAAAgH13qL8AAABg2hGdvwAAAIB8/Xk/AAAAYBFHqD8AAACAXnqoPwAAAKBXKry/AAAAoCwfhT8AAACAFEnJvwAAAEDCXZ2/AAAAoGiOx78AAAAAK1a9PwAAAIB8OrE/AAAAgOinZb8AAABgcRHGPwAAAIBDvKy/AAAA4JzJrD8AAADAISjDvwAAAOAac8S/AAAAAG+Drj8AAACAQRSyvwAAAGBl+H0/AAAAwPOknT8AAACgnXLavwAAAGBvoKE/AAAAQLy9uj8AAABgPrXBPwAAAOD1Sii/AAAAgB6y4j8AAABAQE22PwAAAMAOsbm/AAAAILWhkD8AAABgOyRzPwAAAMBv+GS/AAAAIMnkkr8AAADgIUi/PwAAAABbl8C/AAAAIBzd0L8AAAAgbmzAvwAAAABUvKg/AAAAoMaxtT8AAADgSjmiPwAAAKB/a8U/AAAAQHmeqT8AAACgQIOpPwAAACDFtLY/AAAAwHBgqT8AAACgfm3HPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Tough"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "C",
    "question": " Tough politically?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYDr0v78AAACgc0O1vwAAAGB22bO/AAAAgH13qL8AAABg2hGdvwAAAIB8/Xk/AAAAYBFHqD8AAACAXnqoPwAAAKBXKry/AAAAoCwfhT8AAACAFEnJvwAAAEDCXZ2/AAAAoGiOx78AAAAAK1a9PwAAAIB8OrE/AAAAgOinZb8AAABgcRHGPwAAAIBDvKy/AAAA4JzJrD8AAADAISjDvwAAAOAac8S/AAAAAG+Drj8AAACAQRSyvwAAAGBl+H0/AAAAwPOknT8AAACgnXLavwAAAGBvoKE/AAAAQLy9uj8AAABgPrXBPwAAAOD1Sii/AAAAgB6y4j8AAABAQE22PwAAAMAOsbm/AAAAILWhkD8AAABgOyRzPwAAAMBv+GS/AAAAIMnkkr8AAADgIUi/PwAAAABbl8C/AAAAIBzd0L8AAAAgbmzAvwAAAABUvKg/AAAAoMaxtT8AAADgSjmiPwAAAKB/a8U/AAAAQHmeqT8AAACgQIOpPwAAACDFtLY/AAAAwHBgqT8AAACgfm3HPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Tough"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think statehood is a tough thing for D",
    "question": " You told Chuck Todd last year on “Meet the Press” that you love D.C., you love the people, that you want to do what’s best for them. They think what’s best for them is statehood or at the very least voting rights. What is your position on those two things?",
    "question_vector": "AAAASFZsqr8AAABnrx+3PwAAAAiHvq4/AAAA3FWluT8AAADQS/SmPwAAAAAox3Q/AAAAIFxfwr8AAADgapOXPwAAAKZQYaa/AAAADCr7xb8AAADQi/B7vwAAAOADO7A/AAAAwFKcwr8AAACYePd3PwAAALR2Yr8/AAAAAGAlZz8AAEAtoLSePwAAAGDux5U/AAAAAISWeD8AAABU0+WqvwAAANbQuKY/AAAAABTUkT8AAADg9Wl4vwAAAIrP5rc/AAAAkFghnT8AAACo+yHPvwAAANQjRpM/AAAAoHI3pr8AAAAQFceivwAAACGA4qK/AAAAmGLG1z8AAADv0BKcPwAAABirDKi/AAAAsjbFs78AAACo0FOgvwAAABDjZHC/AAAAlnT8pT8AAAAQGfievwAAALg2EKE/AAAAgBkpjj8AAAAAa7+kPwAAABwJjLk/AAAAcFuxmr8AAABQ137DvwAAAIAbHYA/AAAAEAY5sT8AAAD0tfWsvwAAAFZz05s/AAAAcAEppb8AAKDqgR7APw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "Todd",
      "Meet",
      "D.C."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "C",
    "question": " You told Chuck Todd last year on “Meet the Press” that you love D.C., you love the people, that you want to do what’s best for them. They think what’s best for them is statehood or at the very least voting rights. What is your position on those two things?",
    "question_vector": "AAAASFZsqr8AAABnrx+3PwAAAAiHvq4/AAAA3FWluT8AAADQS/SmPwAAAAAox3Q/AAAAIFxfwr8AAADgapOXPwAAAKZQYaa/AAAADCr7xb8AAADQi/B7vwAAAOADO7A/AAAAwFKcwr8AAACYePd3PwAAALR2Yr8/AAAAAGAlZz8AAEAtoLSePwAAAGDux5U/AAAAAISWeD8AAABU0+WqvwAAANbQuKY/AAAAABTUkT8AAADg9Wl4vwAAAIrP5rc/AAAAkFghnT8AAACo+yHPvwAAANQjRpM/AAAAoHI3pr8AAAAQFceivwAAACGA4qK/AAAAmGLG1z8AAADv0BKcPwAAABirDKi/AAAAsjbFs78AAACo0FOgvwAAABDjZHC/AAAAlnT8pT8AAAAQGfievwAAALg2EKE/AAAAgBkpjj8AAAAAa7+kPwAAABwJjLk/AAAAcFuxmr8AAABQ137DvwAAAIAbHYA/AAAAEAY5sT8AAAD0tfWsvwAAAFZz05s/AAAAcAEppb8AAKDqgR7APw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "Todd",
      "Meet",
      "D.C."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think it’s a tough thing",
    "question": " You told Chuck Todd last year on “Meet the Press” that you love D.C., you love the people, that you want to do what’s best for them. They think what’s best for them is statehood or at the very least voting rights. What is your position on those two things?",
    "question_vector": "AAAASFZsqr8AAABnrx+3PwAAAAiHvq4/AAAA3FWluT8AAADQS/SmPwAAAAAox3Q/AAAAIFxfwr8AAADgapOXPwAAAKZQYaa/AAAADCr7xb8AAADQi/B7vwAAAOADO7A/AAAAwFKcwr8AAACYePd3PwAAALR2Yr8/AAAAAGAlZz8AAEAtoLSePwAAAGDux5U/AAAAAISWeD8AAABU0+WqvwAAANbQuKY/AAAAABTUkT8AAADg9Wl4vwAAAIrP5rc/AAAAkFghnT8AAACo+yHPvwAAANQjRpM/AAAAoHI3pr8AAAAQFceivwAAACGA4qK/AAAAmGLG1z8AAADv0BKcPwAAABirDKi/AAAAsjbFs78AAACo0FOgvwAAABDjZHC/AAAAlnT8pT8AAAAQGfievwAAALg2EKE/AAAAgBkpjj8AAAAAa7+kPwAAABwJjLk/AAAAcFuxmr8AAABQ137DvwAAAIAbHYA/AAAAEAY5sT8AAAD0tfWsvwAAAFZz05s/AAAAcAEppb8AAKDqgR7APw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "Todd",
      "Meet",
      "D.C."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I don’t have a position on it yet",
    "question": " You told Chuck Todd last year on “Meet the Press” that you love D.C., you love the people, that you want to do what’s best for them. They think what’s best for them is statehood or at the very least voting rights. What is your position on those two things?",
    "question_vector": "AAAASFZsqr8AAABnrx+3PwAAAAiHvq4/AAAA3FWluT8AAADQS/SmPwAAAAAox3Q/AAAAIFxfwr8AAADgapOXPwAAAKZQYaa/AAAADCr7xb8AAADQi/B7vwAAAOADO7A/AAAAwFKcwr8AAACYePd3PwAAALR2Yr8/AAAAAGAlZz8AAEAtoLSePwAAAGDux5U/AAAAAISWeD8AAABU0+WqvwAAANbQuKY/AAAAABTUkT8AAADg9Wl4vwAAAIrP5rc/AAAAkFghnT8AAACo+yHPvwAAANQjRpM/AAAAoHI3pr8AAAAQFceivwAAACGA4qK/AAAAmGLG1z8AAADv0BKcPwAAABirDKi/AAAAsjbFs78AAACo0FOgvwAAABDjZHC/AAAAlnT8pT8AAAAQGfievwAAALg2EKE/AAAAgBkpjj8AAAAAa7+kPwAAABwJjLk/AAAAcFuxmr8AAABQ137DvwAAAIAbHYA/AAAAEAY5sT8AAAD0tfWsvwAAAFZz05s/AAAAcAEppb8AAKDqgR7APw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "Todd",
      "Meet",
      "D.C."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I would form a position",
    "question": " You told Chuck Todd last year on “Meet the Press” that you love D.C., you love the people, that you want to do what’s best for them. They think what’s best for them is statehood or at the very least voting rights. What is your position on those two things?",
    "question_vector": "AAAASFZsqr8AAABnrx+3PwAAAAiHvq4/AAAA3FWluT8AAADQS/SmPwAAAAAox3Q/AAAAIFxfwr8AAADgapOXPwAAAKZQYaa/AAAADCr7xb8AAADQi/B7vwAAAOADO7A/AAAAwFKcwr8AAACYePd3PwAAALR2Yr8/AAAAAGAlZz8AAEAtoLSePwAAAGDux5U/AAAAAISWeD8AAABU0+WqvwAAANbQuKY/AAAAABTUkT8AAADg9Wl4vwAAAIrP5rc/AAAAkFghnT8AAACo+yHPvwAAANQjRpM/AAAAoHI3pr8AAAAQFceivwAAACGA4qK/AAAAmGLG1z8AAADv0BKcPwAAABirDKi/AAAAsjbFs78AAACo0FOgvwAAABDjZHC/AAAAlnT8pT8AAAAQGfievwAAALg2EKE/AAAAgBkpjj8AAAAAa7+kPwAAABwJjLk/AAAAcFuxmr8AAABQ137DvwAAAIAbHYA/AAAAEAY5sT8AAAD0tfWsvwAAAFZz05s/AAAAcAEppb8AAKDqgR7APw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "Todd",
      "Meet",
      "D.C."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But I think statehood is a tough thing for D",
    "question": " You told Chuck Todd last year on “Meet the Press” that you love D.C., you love the people, that you want to do what’s best for them. They think what’s best for them is statehood or at the very least voting rights. What is your position on those two things?",
    "question_vector": "AAAASFZsqr8AAABnrx+3PwAAAAiHvq4/AAAA3FWluT8AAADQS/SmPwAAAAAox3Q/AAAAIFxfwr8AAADgapOXPwAAAKZQYaa/AAAADCr7xb8AAADQi/B7vwAAAOADO7A/AAAAwFKcwr8AAACYePd3PwAAALR2Yr8/AAAAAGAlZz8AAEAtoLSePwAAAGDux5U/AAAAAISWeD8AAABU0+WqvwAAANbQuKY/AAAAABTUkT8AAADg9Wl4vwAAAIrP5rc/AAAAkFghnT8AAACo+yHPvwAAANQjRpM/AAAAoHI3pr8AAAAQFceivwAAACGA4qK/AAAAmGLG1z8AAADv0BKcPwAAABirDKi/AAAAsjbFs78AAACo0FOgvwAAABDjZHC/AAAAlnT8pT8AAAAQGfievwAAALg2EKE/AAAAgBkpjj8AAAAAa7+kPwAAABwJjLk/AAAAcFuxmr8AAABQ137DvwAAAIAbHYA/AAAAEAY5sT8AAAD0tfWsvwAAAFZz05s/AAAAcAEppb8AAKDqgR7APw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "Todd",
      "Meet",
      "D.C."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "C",
    "question": " You told Chuck Todd last year on “Meet the Press” that you love D.C., you love the people, that you want to do what’s best for them. They think what’s best for them is statehood or at the very least voting rights. What is your position on those two things?",
    "question_vector": "AAAASFZsqr8AAABnrx+3PwAAAAiHvq4/AAAA3FWluT8AAADQS/SmPwAAAAAox3Q/AAAAIFxfwr8AAADgapOXPwAAAKZQYaa/AAAADCr7xb8AAADQi/B7vwAAAOADO7A/AAAAwFKcwr8AAACYePd3PwAAALR2Yr8/AAAAAGAlZz8AAEAtoLSePwAAAGDux5U/AAAAAISWeD8AAABU0+WqvwAAANbQuKY/AAAAABTUkT8AAADg9Wl4vwAAAIrP5rc/AAAAkFghnT8AAACo+yHPvwAAANQjRpM/AAAAoHI3pr8AAAAQFceivwAAACGA4qK/AAAAmGLG1z8AAADv0BKcPwAAABirDKi/AAAAsjbFs78AAACo0FOgvwAAABDjZHC/AAAAlnT8pT8AAAAQGfievwAAALg2EKE/AAAAgBkpjj8AAAAAa7+kPwAAABwJjLk/AAAAcFuxmr8AAABQ137DvwAAAIAbHYA/AAAAEAY5sT8AAAD0tfWsvwAAAFZz05s/AAAAcAEppb8AAKDqgR7APw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "Todd",
      "Meet",
      "D.C."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well look, there’s many exceptions",
    "question": " How would you identify people to keep them out of this country?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAGLbqvz+rqqqq6gGYv1VVVXVn87c/q6qqGjYAnb+rqqp6Lqi7P6uqqoK9Q5w/q6qq+nnAsr9VVVXVjESFv6uqqkqXT6g/AAAAkFiclL9VVVWFG1qgP6uqqsqZHbO/q6qqyv8krz9VVVWFS36Bv6uqqtpTSrg/AAAAwJ1Llz9VVVX7EK+pPwAAAADGSog/q6qq0n45tT+rqqqqWUavv1VVVYVwcai/AAAA+PJYsj8AAAC43tWxPwAAALCCG7g/VVVVJb9Lsz9VVVWVyAbTv1VVVYXoOcG/AAAAaCyHub8AAADAjAySPwAAAEBvU6e/AAAAcCUg5D+rqiqy4sWzP6uqqqrDBay/q6qqqq1rxL9VVVVVw817vwAAALCpNJw/AAAAuJa2lr+rqqpazgWpv6uqqqoJeKW/q6qqOsVQpD9VVdVc4zvAv1VVVVUOm24/q6qqCqPDwj9VVVXVYWeXP1VVVRWwmLM/AAAAADnXlj9VVVX9FLjDvwAAAASkVaU/q6qq6v6WmT8AAABICkSyvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "identify",
      "people",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " There’s many – everything, you’re going to go through a process",
    "question": " How would you identify people to keep them out of this country?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAGLbqvz+rqqqq6gGYv1VVVXVn87c/q6qqGjYAnb+rqqp6Lqi7P6uqqoK9Q5w/q6qq+nnAsr9VVVXVjESFv6uqqkqXT6g/AAAAkFiclL9VVVWFG1qgP6uqqsqZHbO/q6qqyv8krz9VVVWFS36Bv6uqqtpTSrg/AAAAwJ1Llz9VVVX7EK+pPwAAAADGSog/q6qq0n45tT+rqqqqWUavv1VVVYVwcai/AAAA+PJYsj8AAAC43tWxPwAAALCCG7g/VVVVJb9Lsz9VVVWVyAbTv1VVVYXoOcG/AAAAaCyHub8AAADAjAySPwAAAEBvU6e/AAAAcCUg5D+rqiqy4sWzP6uqqqrDBay/q6qqqq1rxL9VVVVVw817vwAAALCpNJw/AAAAuJa2lr+rqqpazgWpv6uqqqoJeKW/q6qqOsVQpD9VVdVc4zvAv1VVVVUOm24/q6qqCqPDwj9VVVXVYWeXP1VVVRWwmLM/AAAAADnXlj9VVVX9FLjDvwAAAASkVaU/q6qq6v6WmT8AAABICkSyvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "identify",
      "people",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But we have to be very careful",
    "question": " How would you identify people to keep them out of this country?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAGLbqvz+rqqqq6gGYv1VVVXVn87c/q6qqGjYAnb+rqqp6Lqi7P6uqqoK9Q5w/q6qq+nnAsr9VVVXVjESFv6uqqkqXT6g/AAAAkFiclL9VVVWFG1qgP6uqqsqZHbO/q6qqyv8krz9VVVWFS36Bv6uqqtpTSrg/AAAAwJ1Llz9VVVX7EK+pPwAAAADGSog/q6qq0n45tT+rqqqqWUavv1VVVYVwcai/AAAA+PJYsj8AAAC43tWxPwAAALCCG7g/VVVVJb9Lsz9VVVWVyAbTv1VVVYXoOcG/AAAAaCyHub8AAADAjAySPwAAAEBvU6e/AAAAcCUg5D+rqiqy4sWzP6uqqqrDBay/q6qqqq1rxL9VVVVVw817vwAAALCpNJw/AAAAuJa2lr+rqqpazgWpv6uqqqoJeKW/q6qqOsVQpD9VVdVc4zvAv1VVVVUOm24/q6qqCqPDwj9VVVXVYWeXP1VVVRWwmLM/AAAAADnXlj9VVVX9FLjDvwAAAASkVaU/q6qq6v6WmT8AAABICkSyvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "identify",
      "people",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I was really referring in particular, you know, to migrations – Syrians, the whole migration, where we’re going to take in thousands",
    "question": " How would you identify people to keep them out of this country?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAGLbqvz+rqqqq6gGYv1VVVXVn87c/q6qqGjYAnb+rqqp6Lqi7P6uqqoK9Q5w/q6qq+nnAsr9VVVXVjESFv6uqqkqXT6g/AAAAkFiclL9VVVWFG1qgP6uqqsqZHbO/q6qqyv8krz9VVVWFS36Bv6uqqtpTSrg/AAAAwJ1Llz9VVVX7EK+pPwAAAADGSog/q6qq0n45tT+rqqqqWUavv1VVVYVwcai/AAAA+PJYsj8AAAC43tWxPwAAALCCG7g/VVVVJb9Lsz9VVVWVyAbTv1VVVYXoOcG/AAAAaCyHub8AAADAjAySPwAAAEBvU6e/AAAAcCUg5D+rqiqy4sWzP6uqqqrDBay/q6qqqq1rxL9VVVVVw817vwAAALCpNJw/AAAAuJa2lr+rqqpazgWpv6uqqqoJeKW/q6qqOsVQpD9VVdVc4zvAv1VVVVUOm24/q6qqCqPDwj9VVVXVYWeXP1VVVRWwmLM/AAAAADnXlj9VVVX9FLjDvwAAAASkVaU/q6qq6v6WmT8AAABICkSyvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "identify",
      "people",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I heard in the Democrat debate, I heard 55,000, okay",
    "question": " How would you identify people to keep them out of this country?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAGLbqvz+rqqqq6gGYv1VVVXVn87c/q6qqGjYAnb+rqqp6Lqi7P6uqqoK9Q5w/q6qq+nnAsr9VVVXVjESFv6uqqkqXT6g/AAAAkFiclL9VVVWFG1qgP6uqqsqZHbO/q6qqyv8krz9VVVWFS36Bv6uqqtpTSrg/AAAAwJ1Llz9VVVX7EK+pPwAAAADGSog/q6qq0n45tT+rqqqqWUavv1VVVYVwcai/AAAA+PJYsj8AAAC43tWxPwAAALCCG7g/VVVVJb9Lsz9VVVWVyAbTv1VVVYXoOcG/AAAAaCyHub8AAADAjAySPwAAAEBvU6e/AAAAcCUg5D+rqiqy4sWzP6uqqqrDBay/q6qqqq1rxL9VVVVVw817vwAAALCpNJw/AAAAuJa2lr+rqqpazgWpv6uqqqoJeKW/q6qqOsVQpD9VVdVc4zvAv1VVVVUOm24/q6qqCqPDwj9VVVXVYWeXP1VVVRWwmLM/AAAAADnXlj9VVVX9FLjDvwAAAASkVaU/q6qq6v6WmT8AAABICkSyvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "identify",
      "people",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " 55,000",
    "question": " How would you identify people to keep them out of this country?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAGLbqvz+rqqqq6gGYv1VVVXVn87c/q6qqGjYAnb+rqqp6Lqi7P6uqqoK9Q5w/q6qq+nnAsr9VVVXVjESFv6uqqkqXT6g/AAAAkFiclL9VVVWFG1qgP6uqqsqZHbO/q6qqyv8krz9VVVWFS36Bv6uqqtpTSrg/AAAAwJ1Llz9VVVX7EK+pPwAAAADGSog/q6qq0n45tT+rqqqqWUavv1VVVYVwcai/AAAA+PJYsj8AAAC43tWxPwAAALCCG7g/VVVVJb9Lsz9VVVWVyAbTv1VVVYXoOcG/AAAAaCyHub8AAADAjAySPwAAAEBvU6e/AAAAcCUg5D+rqiqy4sWzP6uqqqrDBay/q6qqqq1rxL9VVVVVw817vwAAALCpNJw/AAAAuJa2lr+rqqpazgWpv6uqqqoJeKW/q6qqOsVQpD9VVdVc4zvAv1VVVVUOm24/q6qqCqPDwj9VVVXVYWeXP1VVVRWwmLM/AAAAADnXlj9VVVX9FLjDvwAAAASkVaU/q6qq6v6WmT8AAABICkSyvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "identify",
      "people",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Now they say it’s really ten [thousand], but it’s already 10, and I just don’t think we can take people into this country",
    "question": " How would you identify people to keep them out of this country?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAGLbqvz+rqqqq6gGYv1VVVXVn87c/q6qqGjYAnb+rqqp6Lqi7P6uqqoK9Q5w/q6qq+nnAsr9VVVXVjESFv6uqqkqXT6g/AAAAkFiclL9VVVWFG1qgP6uqqsqZHbO/q6qqyv8krz9VVVWFS36Bv6uqqtpTSrg/AAAAwJ1Llz9VVVX7EK+pPwAAAADGSog/q6qq0n45tT+rqqqqWUavv1VVVYVwcai/AAAA+PJYsj8AAAC43tWxPwAAALCCG7g/VVVVJb9Lsz9VVVWVyAbTv1VVVYXoOcG/AAAAaCyHub8AAADAjAySPwAAAEBvU6e/AAAAcCUg5D+rqiqy4sWzP6uqqqrDBay/q6qqqq1rxL9VVVVVw817vwAAALCpNJw/AAAAuJa2lr+rqqpazgWpv6uqqqoJeKW/q6qqOsVQpD9VVdVc4zvAv1VVVVUOm24/q6qqCqPDwj9VVVXVYWeXP1VVVRWwmLM/AAAAADnXlj9VVVX9FLjDvwAAAASkVaU/q6qq6v6WmT8AAABICkSyvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "identify",
      "people",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You saw what two people did – the woman and the man, whether she radicalized him or [inaudible] – but you saw what two people did, and I just don’t think we can take people in when we have no idea who they are, where they come from",
    "question": " How would you identify people to keep them out of this country?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAGLbqvz+rqqqq6gGYv1VVVXVn87c/q6qqGjYAnb+rqqp6Lqi7P6uqqoK9Q5w/q6qq+nnAsr9VVVXVjESFv6uqqkqXT6g/AAAAkFiclL9VVVWFG1qgP6uqqsqZHbO/q6qqyv8krz9VVVWFS36Bv6uqqtpTSrg/AAAAwJ1Llz9VVVX7EK+pPwAAAADGSog/q6qq0n45tT+rqqqqWUavv1VVVYVwcai/AAAA+PJYsj8AAAC43tWxPwAAALCCG7g/VVVVJb9Lsz9VVVWVyAbTv1VVVYXoOcG/AAAAaCyHub8AAADAjAySPwAAAEBvU6e/AAAAcCUg5D+rqiqy4sWzP6uqqqrDBay/q6qqqq1rxL9VVVVVw817vwAAALCpNJw/AAAAuJa2lr+rqqpazgWpv6uqqqoJeKW/q6qqOsVQpD9VVdVc4zvAv1VVVVUOm24/q6qqCqPDwj9VVVXVYWeXP1VVVRWwmLM/AAAAADnXlj9VVVX9FLjDvwAAAASkVaU/q6qq6v6WmT8AAABICkSyvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "identify",
      "people",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " There’s no documents, there’s no paper, and we have ISIS looming over our head, and we have tremendous destruction",
    "question": " How would you identify people to keep them out of this country?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAGLbqvz+rqqqq6gGYv1VVVXVn87c/q6qqGjYAnb+rqqp6Lqi7P6uqqoK9Q5w/q6qq+nnAsr9VVVXVjESFv6uqqkqXT6g/AAAAkFiclL9VVVWFG1qgP6uqqsqZHbO/q6qqyv8krz9VVVWFS36Bv6uqqtpTSrg/AAAAwJ1Llz9VVVX7EK+pPwAAAADGSog/q6qq0n45tT+rqqqqWUavv1VVVYVwcai/AAAA+PJYsj8AAAC43tWxPwAAALCCG7g/VVVVJb9Lsz9VVVWVyAbTv1VVVYXoOcG/AAAAaCyHub8AAADAjAySPwAAAEBvU6e/AAAAcCUg5D+rqiqy4sWzP6uqqqrDBay/q6qqqq1rxL9VVVVVw817vwAAALCpNJw/AAAAuJa2lr+rqqpazgWpv6uqqqoJeKW/q6qqOsVQpD9VVdVc4zvAv1VVVVUOm24/q6qqCqPDwj9VVVXVYWeXP1VVVRWwmLM/AAAAADnXlj9VVVX9FLjDvwAAAASkVaU/q6qq6v6WmT8AAABICkSyvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "identify",
      "people",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We lost the World Trade Center, we lost the Pentag – you know, we had a plane go into the Pentagon, etc",
    "question": " How would you identify people to keep them out of this country?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAGLbqvz+rqqqq6gGYv1VVVXVn87c/q6qqGjYAnb+rqqp6Lqi7P6uqqoK9Q5w/q6qq+nnAsr9VVVXVjESFv6uqqkqXT6g/AAAAkFiclL9VVVWFG1qgP6uqqsqZHbO/q6qqyv8krz9VVVWFS36Bv6uqqtpTSrg/AAAAwJ1Llz9VVVX7EK+pPwAAAADGSog/q6qq0n45tT+rqqqqWUavv1VVVYVwcai/AAAA+PJYsj8AAAC43tWxPwAAALCCG7g/VVVVJb9Lsz9VVVWVyAbTv1VVVYXoOcG/AAAAaCyHub8AAADAjAySPwAAAEBvU6e/AAAAcCUg5D+rqiqy4sWzP6uqqqrDBay/q6qqqq1rxL9VVVVVw817vwAAALCpNJw/AAAAuJa2lr+rqqpazgWpv6uqqqoJeKW/q6qqOsVQpD9VVdVc4zvAv1VVVVUOm24/q6qqCqPDwj9VVVXVYWeXP1VVVRWwmLM/AAAAADnXlj9VVVX9FLjDvwAAAASkVaU/q6qq6v6WmT8AAABICkSyvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "identify",
      "people",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I don’t think so",
    "question": " But do you feel that your messages, your rhetoric, are dangerous and divisive for this country? How do you feel they’re ….",
    "question_vector": "VVVVMKxqoT+rqqoqCZBwv1VVVTVs7Kk/AAAAcIldqL+rqqpqJiKwP6uqqtrNYKK/VVVV9e6BtL9VVVWVbH6XP6uqqqqBQoG/AAAA3OAqsj+rqqrKW1qSv6uqqqo6MVG/VVVVFf4Xkj8AAACAAGl8P1VVVe1CC7A/AAAAAGhbVL8AAADAeI6nvwAAAMCd4pC/AAAAAFpcuD8AAAAAuRS1vwAAAPDgk6a/q6qqsqVFwD9VVVXdH5qyPwAAAFC1ebA/AAAAYIP5vz+rqqoKzAzSvwAAAHiq+7W/q6qqKrgElD8AAABop6i4PwAAAEDDGau/VVVVxd8h4z9VVVVVTELAP1VVVVU76ma/q6qqqpiRuL9VVVXVQua3v6uqqiqe4nu/AAAAFrzjor+rqqp8rYqtv1VVVUEOZLy/q6qqSsNIp78AAAAAKL1cv1VVVZU2kI8/VVVVFZhknD+rqqoqz6ClP1VVVU0Ra6A/VVVV/bKDqj8AAAD4QC+9vwAAAPQhTqA/q6qqWh4Anb8AAACAZiKdvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "feel",
      "messages",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No, I don’t think so",
    "question": " But do you feel that your messages, your rhetoric, are dangerous and divisive for this country? How do you feel they’re ….",
    "question_vector": "VVVVMKxqoT+rqqoqCZBwv1VVVTVs7Kk/AAAAcIldqL+rqqpqJiKwP6uqqtrNYKK/VVVV9e6BtL9VVVWVbH6XP6uqqqqBQoG/AAAA3OAqsj+rqqrKW1qSv6uqqqo6MVG/VVVVFf4Xkj8AAACAAGl8P1VVVe1CC7A/AAAAAGhbVL8AAADAeI6nvwAAAMCd4pC/AAAAAFpcuD8AAAAAuRS1vwAAAPDgk6a/q6qqsqVFwD9VVVXdH5qyPwAAAFC1ebA/AAAAYIP5vz+rqqoKzAzSvwAAAHiq+7W/q6qqKrgElD8AAABop6i4PwAAAEDDGau/VVVVxd8h4z9VVVVVTELAP1VVVVU76ma/q6qqqpiRuL9VVVXVQua3v6uqqiqe4nu/AAAAFrzjor+rqqp8rYqtv1VVVUEOZLy/q6qqSsNIp78AAAAAKL1cv1VVVZU2kI8/VVVVFZhknD+rqqoqz6ClP1VVVU0Ra6A/VVVV/bKDqj8AAAD4QC+9vwAAAPQhTqA/q6qqWh4Anb8AAACAZiKdvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "feel",
      "messages",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " With the Muslim thing I think it’s a serious problem",
    "question": " But do you feel that your messages, your rhetoric, are dangerous and divisive for this country? How do you feel they’re ….",
    "question_vector": "VVVVMKxqoT+rqqoqCZBwv1VVVTVs7Kk/AAAAcIldqL+rqqpqJiKwP6uqqtrNYKK/VVVV9e6BtL9VVVWVbH6XP6uqqqqBQoG/AAAA3OAqsj+rqqrKW1qSv6uqqqo6MVG/VVVVFf4Xkj8AAACAAGl8P1VVVe1CC7A/AAAAAGhbVL8AAADAeI6nvwAAAMCd4pC/AAAAAFpcuD8AAAAAuRS1vwAAAPDgk6a/q6qqsqVFwD9VVVXdH5qyPwAAAFC1ebA/AAAAYIP5vz+rqqoKzAzSvwAAAHiq+7W/q6qqKrgElD8AAABop6i4PwAAAEDDGau/VVVVxd8h4z9VVVVVTELAP1VVVVU76ma/q6qqqpiRuL9VVVXVQua3v6uqqiqe4nu/AAAAFrzjor+rqqp8rYqtv1VVVUEOZLy/q6qqSsNIp78AAAAAKL1cv1VVVZU2kI8/VVVVFZhknD+rqqoqz6ClP1VVVU0Ra6A/VVVV/bKDqj8AAAD4QC+9vwAAAPQhTqA/q6qqWh4Anb8AAACAZiKdvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "feel",
      "messages",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’ve had Muslims call and tell me you’re right with the Muslim thing, I think it’s a serious problem",
    "question": " But do you feel that your messages, your rhetoric, are dangerous and divisive for this country? How do you feel they’re ….",
    "question_vector": "VVVVMKxqoT+rqqoqCZBwv1VVVTVs7Kk/AAAAcIldqL+rqqpqJiKwP6uqqtrNYKK/VVVV9e6BtL9VVVWVbH6XP6uqqqqBQoG/AAAA3OAqsj+rqqrKW1qSv6uqqqo6MVG/VVVVFf4Xkj8AAACAAGl8P1VVVe1CC7A/AAAAAGhbVL8AAADAeI6nvwAAAMCd4pC/AAAAAFpcuD8AAAAAuRS1vwAAAPDgk6a/q6qqsqVFwD9VVVXdH5qyPwAAAFC1ebA/AAAAYIP5vz+rqqoKzAzSvwAAAHiq+7W/q6qqKrgElD8AAABop6i4PwAAAEDDGau/VVVVxd8h4z9VVVVVTELAP1VVVVU76ma/q6qqqpiRuL9VVVXVQua3v6uqqiqe4nu/AAAAFrzjor+rqqp8rYqtv1VVVUEOZLy/q6qqSsNIp78AAAAAKL1cv1VVVZU2kI8/VVVVFZhknD+rqqoqz6ClP1VVVU0Ra6A/VVVV/bKDqj8AAAD4QC+9vwAAAPQhTqA/q6qqWh4Anb8AAACAZiKdvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "feel",
      "messages",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "  And it’s a problem that has to be addressed",
    "question": " But do you feel that your messages, your rhetoric, are dangerous and divisive for this country? How do you feel they’re ….",
    "question_vector": "VVVVMKxqoT+rqqoqCZBwv1VVVTVs7Kk/AAAAcIldqL+rqqpqJiKwP6uqqtrNYKK/VVVV9e6BtL9VVVWVbH6XP6uqqqqBQoG/AAAA3OAqsj+rqqrKW1qSv6uqqqo6MVG/VVVVFf4Xkj8AAACAAGl8P1VVVe1CC7A/AAAAAGhbVL8AAADAeI6nvwAAAMCd4pC/AAAAAFpcuD8AAAAAuRS1vwAAAPDgk6a/q6qqsqVFwD9VVVXdH5qyPwAAAFC1ebA/AAAAYIP5vz+rqqoKzAzSvwAAAHiq+7W/q6qqKrgElD8AAABop6i4PwAAAEDDGau/VVVVxd8h4z9VVVVVTELAP1VVVVU76ma/q6qqqpiRuL9VVVXVQua3v6uqqiqe4nu/AAAAFrzjor+rqqp8rYqtv1VVVUEOZLy/q6qqSsNIp78AAAAAKL1cv1VVVZU2kI8/VVVVFZhknD+rqqoqz6ClP1VVVU0Ra6A/VVVV/bKDqj8AAAD4QC+9vwAAAPQhTqA/q6qqWh4Anb8AAACAZiKdvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "feel",
      "messages",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean, there’s tremendous hatred",
    "question": " But do you feel that your messages, your rhetoric, are dangerous and divisive for this country? How do you feel they’re ….",
    "question_vector": "VVVVMKxqoT+rqqoqCZBwv1VVVTVs7Kk/AAAAcIldqL+rqqpqJiKwP6uqqtrNYKK/VVVV9e6BtL9VVVWVbH6XP6uqqqqBQoG/AAAA3OAqsj+rqqrKW1qSv6uqqqo6MVG/VVVVFf4Xkj8AAACAAGl8P1VVVe1CC7A/AAAAAGhbVL8AAADAeI6nvwAAAMCd4pC/AAAAAFpcuD8AAAAAuRS1vwAAAPDgk6a/q6qqsqVFwD9VVVXdH5qyPwAAAFC1ebA/AAAAYIP5vz+rqqoKzAzSvwAAAHiq+7W/q6qqKrgElD8AAABop6i4PwAAAEDDGau/VVVVxd8h4z9VVVVVTELAP1VVVVU76ma/q6qqqpiRuL9VVVXVQua3v6uqqiqe4nu/AAAAFrzjor+rqqp8rYqtv1VVVUEOZLy/q6qqSsNIp78AAAAAKL1cv1VVVZU2kI8/VVVVFZhknD+rqqoqz6ClP1VVVU0Ra6A/VVVV/bKDqj8AAAD4QC+9vwAAAPQhTqA/q6qqWh4Anb8AAACAZiKdvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "feel",
      "messages",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Even the, even the guy they caught in Paris",
    "question": " But do you feel that your messages, your rhetoric, are dangerous and divisive for this country? How do you feel they’re ….",
    "question_vector": "VVVVMKxqoT+rqqoqCZBwv1VVVTVs7Kk/AAAAcIldqL+rqqpqJiKwP6uqqtrNYKK/VVVV9e6BtL9VVVWVbH6XP6uqqqqBQoG/AAAA3OAqsj+rqqrKW1qSv6uqqqo6MVG/VVVVFf4Xkj8AAACAAGl8P1VVVe1CC7A/AAAAAGhbVL8AAADAeI6nvwAAAMCd4pC/AAAAAFpcuD8AAAAAuRS1vwAAAPDgk6a/q6qqsqVFwD9VVVXdH5qyPwAAAFC1ebA/AAAAYIP5vz+rqqoKzAzSvwAAAHiq+7W/q6qqKrgElD8AAABop6i4PwAAAEDDGau/VVVVxd8h4z9VVVVVTELAP1VVVVU76ma/q6qqqpiRuL9VVVXVQua3v6uqqiqe4nu/AAAAFrzjor+rqqp8rYqtv1VVVUEOZLy/q6qqSsNIp78AAAAAKL1cv1VVVZU2kI8/VVVVFZhknD+rqqoqz6ClP1VVVU0Ra6A/VVVV/bKDqj8AAAD4QC+9vwAAAPQhTqA/q6qqWh4Anb8AAACAZiKdvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "feel",
      "messages",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " He was being hid out by other Muslims, and everybody is after him, and he’s living right next to where he grew up",
    "question": " But do you feel that your messages, your rhetoric, are dangerous and divisive for this country? How do you feel they’re ….",
    "question_vector": "VVVVMKxqoT+rqqoqCZBwv1VVVTVs7Kk/AAAAcIldqL+rqqpqJiKwP6uqqtrNYKK/VVVV9e6BtL9VVVWVbH6XP6uqqqqBQoG/AAAA3OAqsj+rqqrKW1qSv6uqqqo6MVG/VVVVFf4Xkj8AAACAAGl8P1VVVe1CC7A/AAAAAGhbVL8AAADAeI6nvwAAAMCd4pC/AAAAAFpcuD8AAAAAuRS1vwAAAPDgk6a/q6qqsqVFwD9VVVXdH5qyPwAAAFC1ebA/AAAAYIP5vz+rqqoKzAzSvwAAAHiq+7W/q6qqKrgElD8AAABop6i4PwAAAEDDGau/VVVVxd8h4z9VVVVVTELAP1VVVVU76ma/q6qqqpiRuL9VVVXVQua3v6uqqiqe4nu/AAAAFrzjor+rqqp8rYqtv1VVVUEOZLy/q6qqSsNIp78AAAAAKL1cv1VVVZU2kI8/VVVVFZhknD+rqqoqz6ClP1VVVU0Ra6A/VVVV/bKDqj8AAAD4QC+9vwAAAPQhTqA/q6qqWh4Anb8AAACAZiKdvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "feel",
      "messages",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "  There’s a serious, serious problem with the Muslims and it’s got to be addressed",
    "question": " But do you feel that your messages, your rhetoric, are dangerous and divisive for this country? How do you feel they’re ….",
    "question_vector": "VVVVMKxqoT+rqqoqCZBwv1VVVTVs7Kk/AAAAcIldqL+rqqpqJiKwP6uqqtrNYKK/VVVV9e6BtL9VVVWVbH6XP6uqqqqBQoG/AAAA3OAqsj+rqqrKW1qSv6uqqqo6MVG/VVVVFf4Xkj8AAACAAGl8P1VVVe1CC7A/AAAAAGhbVL8AAADAeI6nvwAAAMCd4pC/AAAAAFpcuD8AAAAAuRS1vwAAAPDgk6a/q6qqsqVFwD9VVVXdH5qyPwAAAFC1ebA/AAAAYIP5vz+rqqoKzAzSvwAAAHiq+7W/q6qqKrgElD8AAABop6i4PwAAAEDDGau/VVVVxd8h4z9VVVVVTELAP1VVVVU76ma/q6qqqpiRuL9VVVXVQua3v6uqqiqe4nu/AAAAFrzjor+rqqp8rYqtv1VVVUEOZLy/q6qqSsNIp78AAAAAKL1cv1VVVZU2kI8/VVVVFZhknD+rqqoqz6ClP1VVVU0Ra6A/VVVV/bKDqj8AAAD4QC+9vwAAAPQhTqA/q6qqWh4Anb8AAACAZiKdvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "feel",
      "messages",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " It’s temporary, and it’s got to be addressed",
    "question": " But do you feel that your messages, your rhetoric, are dangerous and divisive for this country? How do you feel they’re ….",
    "question_vector": "VVVVMKxqoT+rqqoqCZBwv1VVVTVs7Kk/AAAAcIldqL+rqqpqJiKwP6uqqtrNYKK/VVVV9e6BtL9VVVWVbH6XP6uqqqqBQoG/AAAA3OAqsj+rqqrKW1qSv6uqqqo6MVG/VVVVFf4Xkj8AAACAAGl8P1VVVe1CC7A/AAAAAGhbVL8AAADAeI6nvwAAAMCd4pC/AAAAAFpcuD8AAAAAuRS1vwAAAPDgk6a/q6qqsqVFwD9VVVXdH5qyPwAAAFC1ebA/AAAAYIP5vz+rqqoKzAzSvwAAAHiq+7W/q6qqKrgElD8AAABop6i4PwAAAEDDGau/VVVVxd8h4z9VVVVVTELAP1VVVVU76ma/q6qqqpiRuL9VVVXVQua3v6uqqiqe4nu/AAAAFrzjor+rqqp8rYqtv1VVVUEOZLy/q6qqSsNIp78AAAAAKL1cv1VVVZU2kI8/VVVVFZhknD+rqqoqz6ClP1VVVU0Ra6A/VVVV/bKDqj8AAAD4QC+9vwAAAPQhTqA/q6qqWh4Anb8AAACAZiKdvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "feel",
      "messages",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And you know you may think of it as negative",
    "question": " But do you feel that your messages, your rhetoric, are dangerous and divisive for this country? How do you feel they’re ….",
    "question_vector": "VVVVMKxqoT+rqqoqCZBwv1VVVTVs7Kk/AAAAcIldqL+rqqpqJiKwP6uqqtrNYKK/VVVV9e6BtL9VVVWVbH6XP6uqqqqBQoG/AAAA3OAqsj+rqqrKW1qSv6uqqqo6MVG/VVVVFf4Xkj8AAACAAGl8P1VVVe1CC7A/AAAAAGhbVL8AAADAeI6nvwAAAMCd4pC/AAAAAFpcuD8AAAAAuRS1vwAAAPDgk6a/q6qqsqVFwD9VVVXdH5qyPwAAAFC1ebA/AAAAYIP5vz+rqqoKzAzSvwAAAHiq+7W/q6qqKrgElD8AAABop6i4PwAAAEDDGau/VVVVxd8h4z9VVVVVTELAP1VVVVU76ma/q6qqqpiRuL9VVVXVQua3v6uqqiqe4nu/AAAAFrzjor+rqqp8rYqtv1VVVUEOZLy/q6qqSsNIp78AAAAAKL1cv1VVVZU2kI8/VVVVFZhknD+rqqoqz6ClP1VVVU0Ra6A/VVVV/bKDqj8AAAD4QC+9vwAAAPQhTqA/q6qqWh4Anb8AAACAZiKdvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "feel",
      "messages",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Many people think it’s very positive",
    "question": " But do you feel that your messages, your rhetoric, are dangerous and divisive for this country? How do you feel they’re ….",
    "question_vector": "VVVVMKxqoT+rqqoqCZBwv1VVVTVs7Kk/AAAAcIldqL+rqqpqJiKwP6uqqtrNYKK/VVVV9e6BtL9VVVWVbH6XP6uqqqqBQoG/AAAA3OAqsj+rqqrKW1qSv6uqqqo6MVG/VVVVFf4Xkj8AAACAAGl8P1VVVe1CC7A/AAAAAGhbVL8AAADAeI6nvwAAAMCd4pC/AAAAAFpcuD8AAAAAuRS1vwAAAPDgk6a/q6qqsqVFwD9VVVXdH5qyPwAAAFC1ebA/AAAAYIP5vz+rqqoKzAzSvwAAAHiq+7W/q6qqKrgElD8AAABop6i4PwAAAEDDGau/VVVVxd8h4z9VVVVVTELAP1VVVVU76ma/q6qqqpiRuL9VVVXVQua3v6uqqiqe4nu/AAAAFrzjor+rqqp8rYqtv1VVVUEOZLy/q6qqSsNIp78AAAAAKL1cv1VVVZU2kI8/VVVVFZhknD+rqqoqz6ClP1VVVU0Ra6A/VVVV/bKDqj8AAAD4QC+9vwAAAPQhTqA/q6qqWh4Anb8AAACAZiKdvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "feel",
      "messages",
      "country"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We do, if it’s illegals, in other words, if it’s everybody, but people that are legally living here, I’m doing very well",
    "question": " I think some of the polls are saying you’re doing [in the] negatives.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAKI0KqL8AAADhJeyivwAAAEI3BL0/AAAA8Kaolr8AAACAo16kPwAAAOCbuJi/AAAA0JuFub8AAADgkVuZPwAAAOhYWcC/AAAAQCu7j78AAACgUOq8vwAAALhol8G/AAAA5rR+tb8AAAD0LYGdPwAAAJgjvrg/AAAACHx0tj8AAADwxSq0PwAAAHgXgb+/AAAAsKwyhb8AAABQ86++vwAAACAQ67C/AAAA3Iftqz8AAAB4wtDAPwAAACDbL6k/AAAAYEaSwj8AAABIfczSvwAAADCZO8S/AAAA4Es3lD8AAABAv0yUPwAAAEAtz6M/AAAAEOXA3j8AAAAwtp3CPwAAAHht1cC/AAAAwDL2xL8AAAAA4ye3vwAAAEAOEcW/AAAA8L/mmb8AAACAXlmxPwAAAICK556/AAAA4CQXvr8AAABgmja7vwAAAEinb4I/AAAA6CJlsb8AAAC472etPwAAABB3uaG/AAAA4LrlpD8AAADw8amyvwAAAFDkNLc/AADAt4t1vj8AAACI6O21Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "polls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " In other words, people that are here, like Hispanics that are in the country, I’m doing very well",
    "question": " I think some of the polls are saying you’re doing [in the] negatives.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAKI0KqL8AAADhJeyivwAAAEI3BL0/AAAA8Kaolr8AAACAo16kPwAAAOCbuJi/AAAA0JuFub8AAADgkVuZPwAAAOhYWcC/AAAAQCu7j78AAACgUOq8vwAAALhol8G/AAAA5rR+tb8AAAD0LYGdPwAAAJgjvrg/AAAACHx0tj8AAADwxSq0PwAAAHgXgb+/AAAAsKwyhb8AAABQ86++vwAAACAQ67C/AAAA3Iftqz8AAAB4wtDAPwAAACDbL6k/AAAAYEaSwj8AAABIfczSvwAAADCZO8S/AAAA4Es3lD8AAABAv0yUPwAAAEAtz6M/AAAAEOXA3j8AAAAwtp3CPwAAAHht1cC/AAAAwDL2xL8AAAAA4ye3vwAAAEAOEcW/AAAA8L/mmb8AAACAXlmxPwAAAICK556/AAAA4CQXvr8AAABgmja7vwAAAEinb4I/AAAA6CJlsb8AAAC472etPwAAABB3uaG/AAAA4LrlpD8AAADw8amyvwAAAFDkNLc/AADAt4t1vj8AAACI6O21Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "polls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " People that vote",
    "question": " I think some of the polls are saying you’re doing [in the] negatives.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAKI0KqL8AAADhJeyivwAAAEI3BL0/AAAA8Kaolr8AAACAo16kPwAAAOCbuJi/AAAA0JuFub8AAADgkVuZPwAAAOhYWcC/AAAAQCu7j78AAACgUOq8vwAAALhol8G/AAAA5rR+tb8AAAD0LYGdPwAAAJgjvrg/AAAACHx0tj8AAADwxSq0PwAAAHgXgb+/AAAAsKwyhb8AAABQ86++vwAAACAQ67C/AAAA3Iftqz8AAAB4wtDAPwAAACDbL6k/AAAAYEaSwj8AAABIfczSvwAAADCZO8S/AAAA4Es3lD8AAABAv0yUPwAAAEAtz6M/AAAAEOXA3j8AAAAwtp3CPwAAAHht1cC/AAAAwDL2xL8AAAAA4ye3vwAAAEAOEcW/AAAA8L/mmb8AAACAXlmxPwAAAICK556/AAAA4CQXvr8AAABgmja7vwAAAEinb4I/AAAA6CJlsb8AAAC472etPwAAABB3uaG/AAAA4LrlpD8AAADw8amyvwAAAFDkNLc/AADAt4t1vj8AAACI6O21Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "polls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Like people leaving voting booths and all, I’m doing very well with them",
    "question": " I think some of the polls are saying you’re doing [in the] negatives.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAKI0KqL8AAADhJeyivwAAAEI3BL0/AAAA8Kaolr8AAACAo16kPwAAAOCbuJi/AAAA0JuFub8AAADgkVuZPwAAAOhYWcC/AAAAQCu7j78AAACgUOq8vwAAALhol8G/AAAA5rR+tb8AAAD0LYGdPwAAAJgjvrg/AAAACHx0tj8AAADwxSq0PwAAAHgXgb+/AAAAsKwyhb8AAABQ86++vwAAACAQ67C/AAAA3Iftqz8AAAB4wtDAPwAAACDbL6k/AAAAYEaSwj8AAABIfczSvwAAADCZO8S/AAAA4Es3lD8AAABAv0yUPwAAAEAtz6M/AAAAEOXA3j8AAAAwtp3CPwAAAHht1cC/AAAAwDL2xL8AAAAA4ye3vwAAAEAOEcW/AAAA8L/mmb8AAACAXlmxPwAAAICK556/AAAA4CQXvr8AAABgmja7vwAAAEinb4I/AAAA6CJlsb8AAAC472etPwAAABB3uaG/AAAA4LrlpD8AAADw8amyvwAAAFDkNLc/AADAt4t1vj8AAACI6O21Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "polls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I want to be inclusive, but at the same time, people should come here legally",
    "question": " I think some of the polls are saying you’re doing [in the] negatives.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAKI0KqL8AAADhJeyivwAAAEI3BL0/AAAA8Kaolr8AAACAo16kPwAAAOCbuJi/AAAA0JuFub8AAADgkVuZPwAAAOhYWcC/AAAAQCu7j78AAACgUOq8vwAAALhol8G/AAAA5rR+tb8AAAD0LYGdPwAAAJgjvrg/AAAACHx0tj8AAADwxSq0PwAAAHgXgb+/AAAAsKwyhb8AAABQ86++vwAAACAQ67C/AAAA3Iftqz8AAAB4wtDAPwAAACDbL6k/AAAAYEaSwj8AAABIfczSvwAAADCZO8S/AAAA4Es3lD8AAABAv0yUPwAAAEAtz6M/AAAAEOXA3j8AAAAwtp3CPwAAAHht1cC/AAAAwDL2xL8AAAAA4ye3vwAAAEAOEcW/AAAA8L/mmb8AAACAXlmxPwAAAICK556/AAAA4CQXvr8AAABgmja7vwAAAEinb4I/AAAA6CJlsb8AAAC472etPwAAABB3uaG/AAAA4LrlpD8AAADw8amyvwAAAFDkNLc/AADAt4t1vj8AAACI6O21Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "polls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They should be here legally",
    "question": " I think some of the polls are saying you’re doing [in the] negatives.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAKI0KqL8AAADhJeyivwAAAEI3BL0/AAAA8Kaolr8AAACAo16kPwAAAOCbuJi/AAAA0JuFub8AAADgkVuZPwAAAOhYWcC/AAAAQCu7j78AAACgUOq8vwAAALhol8G/AAAA5rR+tb8AAAD0LYGdPwAAAJgjvrg/AAAACHx0tj8AAADwxSq0PwAAAHgXgb+/AAAAsKwyhb8AAABQ86++vwAAACAQ67C/AAAA3Iftqz8AAAB4wtDAPwAAACDbL6k/AAAAYEaSwj8AAABIfczSvwAAADCZO8S/AAAA4Es3lD8AAABAv0yUPwAAAEAtz6M/AAAAEOXA3j8AAAAwtp3CPwAAAHht1cC/AAAAwDL2xL8AAAAA4ye3vwAAAEAOEcW/AAAA8L/mmb8AAACAXlmxPwAAAICK556/AAAA4CQXvr8AAABgmja7vwAAAEinb4I/AAAA6CJlsb8AAAC472etPwAAABB3uaG/AAAA4LrlpD8AAADw8amyvwAAAFDkNLc/AADAt4t1vj8AAACI6O21Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "polls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I think the reason I’m doing, that I will do well, especially once I get started, don’t forget I haven’t even focused on Hillary yet",
    "question": " I think some of the polls are saying you’re doing [in the] negatives.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAKI0KqL8AAADhJeyivwAAAEI3BL0/AAAA8Kaolr8AAACAo16kPwAAAOCbuJi/AAAA0JuFub8AAADgkVuZPwAAAOhYWcC/AAAAQCu7j78AAACgUOq8vwAAALhol8G/AAAA5rR+tb8AAAD0LYGdPwAAAJgjvrg/AAAACHx0tj8AAADwxSq0PwAAAHgXgb+/AAAAsKwyhb8AAABQ86++vwAAACAQ67C/AAAA3Iftqz8AAAB4wtDAPwAAACDbL6k/AAAAYEaSwj8AAABIfczSvwAAADCZO8S/AAAA4Es3lD8AAABAv0yUPwAAAEAtz6M/AAAAEOXA3j8AAAAwtp3CPwAAAHht1cC/AAAAwDL2xL8AAAAA4ye3vwAAAEAOEcW/AAAA8L/mmb8AAACAXlmxPwAAAICK556/AAAA4CQXvr8AAABgmja7vwAAAEinb4I/AAAA6CJlsb8AAAC472etPwAAABB3uaG/AAAA4LrlpD8AAADw8amyvwAAAFDkNLc/AADAt4t1vj8AAACI6O21Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "polls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And, and as you know, you know I’ve had polls that are against me, but I’ve had many polls that say I’d beat Hillary, but they’re not that, that, they don’t mean  anything now because it’s too early",
    "question": " I think some of the polls are saying you’re doing [in the] negatives.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAKI0KqL8AAADhJeyivwAAAEI3BL0/AAAA8Kaolr8AAACAo16kPwAAAOCbuJi/AAAA0JuFub8AAADgkVuZPwAAAOhYWcC/AAAAQCu7j78AAACgUOq8vwAAALhol8G/AAAA5rR+tb8AAAD0LYGdPwAAAJgjvrg/AAAACHx0tj8AAADwxSq0PwAAAHgXgb+/AAAAsKwyhb8AAABQ86++vwAAACAQ67C/AAAA3Iftqz8AAAB4wtDAPwAAACDbL6k/AAAAYEaSwj8AAABIfczSvwAAADCZO8S/AAAA4Es3lD8AAABAv0yUPwAAAEAtz6M/AAAAEOXA3j8AAAAwtp3CPwAAAHht1cC/AAAAwDL2xL8AAAAA4ye3vwAAAEAOEcW/AAAA8L/mmb8AAACAXlmxPwAAAICK556/AAAA4CQXvr8AAABgmja7vwAAAEinb4I/AAAA6CJlsb8AAAC472etPwAAABB3uaG/AAAA4LrlpD8AAADw8amyvwAAAFDkNLc/AADAt4t1vj8AAACI6O21Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "polls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Because I haven’t hit her",
    "question": " I think some of the polls are saying you’re doing [in the] negatives.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAKI0KqL8AAADhJeyivwAAAEI3BL0/AAAA8Kaolr8AAACAo16kPwAAAOCbuJi/AAAA0JuFub8AAADgkVuZPwAAAOhYWcC/AAAAQCu7j78AAACgUOq8vwAAALhol8G/AAAA5rR+tb8AAAD0LYGdPwAAAJgjvrg/AAAACHx0tj8AAADwxSq0PwAAAHgXgb+/AAAAsKwyhb8AAABQ86++vwAAACAQ67C/AAAA3Iftqz8AAAB4wtDAPwAAACDbL6k/AAAAYEaSwj8AAABIfczSvwAAADCZO8S/AAAA4Es3lD8AAABAv0yUPwAAAEAtz6M/AAAAEOXA3j8AAAAwtp3CPwAAAHht1cC/AAAAwDL2xL8AAAAA4ye3vwAAAEAOEcW/AAAA8L/mmb8AAACAXlmxPwAAAICK556/AAAA4CQXvr8AAABgmja7vwAAAEinb4I/AAAA6CJlsb8AAAC472etPwAAABB3uaG/AAAA4LrlpD8AAADw8amyvwAAAFDkNLc/AADAt4t1vj8AAACI6O21Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "polls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’ve only hit her once, and that was eight weeks ago, but, I haven’t started on Hillary yet, and when I do I think I’ll be able to make my  points",
    "question": " I think some of the polls are saying you’re doing [in the] negatives.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAKI0KqL8AAADhJeyivwAAAEI3BL0/AAAA8Kaolr8AAACAo16kPwAAAOCbuJi/AAAA0JuFub8AAADgkVuZPwAAAOhYWcC/AAAAQCu7j78AAACgUOq8vwAAALhol8G/AAAA5rR+tb8AAAD0LYGdPwAAAJgjvrg/AAAACHx0tj8AAADwxSq0PwAAAHgXgb+/AAAAsKwyhb8AAABQ86++vwAAACAQ67C/AAAA3Iftqz8AAAB4wtDAPwAAACDbL6k/AAAAYEaSwj8AAABIfczSvwAAADCZO8S/AAAA4Es3lD8AAABAv0yUPwAAAEAtz6M/AAAAEOXA3j8AAAAwtp3CPwAAAHht1cC/AAAAwDL2xL8AAAAA4ye3vwAAAEAOEcW/AAAA8L/mmb8AAACAXlmxPwAAAICK556/AAAA4CQXvr8AAABgmja7vwAAAEinb4I/AAAA6CJlsb8AAAC472etPwAAABB3uaG/AAAA4LrlpD8AAADw8amyvwAAAFDkNLc/AADAt4t1vj8AAACI6O21Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "polls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean, you know, but, but I think that just to try and answer your question: Uh, I am the least racist person that you will ever meet",
    "question": " I think some of the polls are saying you’re doing [in the] negatives.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAKI0KqL8AAADhJeyivwAAAEI3BL0/AAAA8Kaolr8AAACAo16kPwAAAOCbuJi/AAAA0JuFub8AAADgkVuZPwAAAOhYWcC/AAAAQCu7j78AAACgUOq8vwAAALhol8G/AAAA5rR+tb8AAAD0LYGdPwAAAJgjvrg/AAAACHx0tj8AAADwxSq0PwAAAHgXgb+/AAAAsKwyhb8AAABQ86++vwAAACAQ67C/AAAA3Iftqz8AAAB4wtDAPwAAACDbL6k/AAAAYEaSwj8AAABIfczSvwAAADCZO8S/AAAA4Es3lD8AAABAv0yUPwAAAEAtz6M/AAAAEOXA3j8AAAAwtp3CPwAAAHht1cC/AAAAwDL2xL8AAAAA4ye3vwAAAEAOEcW/AAAA8L/mmb8AAACAXlmxPwAAAICK556/AAAA4CQXvr8AAABgmja7vwAAAEinb4I/AAAA6CJlsb8AAAC472etPwAAABB3uaG/AAAA4LrlpD8AAADw8amyvwAAAFDkNLc/AADAt4t1vj8AAACI6O21Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "polls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Okay",
    "question": " I think some of the polls are saying you’re doing [in the] negatives.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAKI0KqL8AAADhJeyivwAAAEI3BL0/AAAA8Kaolr8AAACAo16kPwAAAOCbuJi/AAAA0JuFub8AAADgkVuZPwAAAOhYWcC/AAAAQCu7j78AAACgUOq8vwAAALhol8G/AAAA5rR+tb8AAAD0LYGdPwAAAJgjvrg/AAAACHx0tj8AAADwxSq0PwAAAHgXgb+/AAAAsKwyhb8AAABQ86++vwAAACAQ67C/AAAA3Iftqz8AAAB4wtDAPwAAACDbL6k/AAAAYEaSwj8AAABIfczSvwAAADCZO8S/AAAA4Es3lD8AAABAv0yUPwAAAEAtz6M/AAAAEOXA3j8AAAAwtp3CPwAAAHht1cC/AAAAwDL2xL8AAAAA4ye3vwAAAEAOEcW/AAAA8L/mmb8AAACAXlmxPwAAAICK556/AAAA4CQXvr8AAABgmja7vwAAAEinb4I/AAAA6CJlsb8AAAC472etPwAAABB3uaG/AAAA4LrlpD8AAADw8amyvwAAAFDkNLc/AADAt4t1vj8AAACI6O21Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "polls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " That I can tell you",
    "question": " I think some of the polls are saying you’re doing [in the] negatives.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAKI0KqL8AAADhJeyivwAAAEI3BL0/AAAA8Kaolr8AAACAo16kPwAAAOCbuJi/AAAA0JuFub8AAADgkVuZPwAAAOhYWcC/AAAAQCu7j78AAACgUOq8vwAAALhol8G/AAAA5rR+tb8AAAD0LYGdPwAAAJgjvrg/AAAACHx0tj8AAADwxSq0PwAAAHgXgb+/AAAAsKwyhb8AAABQ86++vwAAACAQ67C/AAAA3Iftqz8AAAB4wtDAPwAAACDbL6k/AAAAYEaSwj8AAABIfczSvwAAADCZO8S/AAAA4Es3lD8AAABAv0yUPwAAAEAtz6M/AAAAEOXA3j8AAAAwtp3CPwAAAHht1cC/AAAAwDL2xL8AAAAA4ye3vwAAAEAOEcW/AAAA8L/mmb8AAACAXlmxPwAAAICK556/AAAA4CQXvr8AAABgmja7vwAAAEinb4I/AAAA6CJlsb8AAAC472etPwAAABB3uaG/AAAA4LrlpD8AAADw8amyvwAAAFDkNLc/AADAt4t1vj8AAACI6O21Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "polls"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well, first of all, if you look at some polls that have come out, I’m doing very well with African Americans",
    "question": " Uh, yeah, I mean speaking again of the system of what a lot of people would say are some of the uglier components of your campaign; a lot of people have said you’ve been running a very divisive campaign as far as racial divides, you’ve noted you know your comments about Muslims, about Mexicans, immigrants and such. You have information that the country is becoming browner, is becoming younger, is becoming blacker. What in your vision of president, in your presidency, how would you bridge these divides and how will you address a– how are you going to run on a message of inclusion of all Americans?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAMEPPqz8AAADAYO+BPwAAAE5LALM/AAAAyBQsrb8AAADgYAuiPwAAAA4e5Xa/AAAAkHlXer8AAAD8/SalvwAAAICQAZq/AAAAkB7ImT8AAAAQ16ONvwAAAACdjVA/AAAAjIcMg78AAABA4PiovwAAALCtELY/AAAALB3Sqj8AAICE502lPwAAAA4zArQ/AAAA6DbIgz8AAADuh3HBvwAAABxgQa+/AAAAQCmHiz8AAADg8amWPwAAAE5Td6Q/AAAAalScuz8AAABIIxjTvwAAADglyL2/AAAAwKMacT8AAACV5tnBPwAAAIDZV6u/AAAAUCfL5T8AAADAeUu8PwAAANA3vZS/AAAA0LOhuL8AAADrxzugvwAAAAC7gDk/AAAA7Ov6iT8AAAC4PyaVvwAAADhfIKA/AAAAcEuzhz8AAIAmPZi1vwAAgPCo1oc/AAAA/glOqT8AAADI2oPDPwAAAOh50ae/AAAAsKsKiz8AAAA6AYWhvwAAAM4drpo/AAAAgBaPar8AAABUzUKsPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mean",
      "system",
      "people",
      "lot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’m doing, actually if you look at the polls, a lot of the polls that came out, in the, um, what do they call it? Exit polls, like from Nevada and other places, I’m doing very well with Hispanics",
    "question": " Uh, yeah, I mean speaking again of the system of what a lot of people would say are some of the uglier components of your campaign; a lot of people have said you’ve been running a very divisive campaign as far as racial divides, you’ve noted you know your comments about Muslims, about Mexicans, immigrants and such. You have information that the country is becoming browner, is becoming younger, is becoming blacker. What in your vision of president, in your presidency, how would you bridge these divides and how will you address a– how are you going to run on a message of inclusion of all Americans?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAMEPPqz8AAADAYO+BPwAAAE5LALM/AAAAyBQsrb8AAADgYAuiPwAAAA4e5Xa/AAAAkHlXer8AAAD8/SalvwAAAICQAZq/AAAAkB7ImT8AAAAQ16ONvwAAAACdjVA/AAAAjIcMg78AAABA4PiovwAAALCtELY/AAAALB3Sqj8AAICE502lPwAAAA4zArQ/AAAA6DbIgz8AAADuh3HBvwAAABxgQa+/AAAAQCmHiz8AAADg8amWPwAAAE5Td6Q/AAAAalScuz8AAABIIxjTvwAAADglyL2/AAAAwKMacT8AAACV5tnBPwAAAIDZV6u/AAAAUCfL5T8AAADAeUu8PwAAANA3vZS/AAAA0LOhuL8AAADrxzugvwAAAAC7gDk/AAAA7Ov6iT8AAAC4PyaVvwAAADhfIKA/AAAAcEuzhz8AAIAmPZi1vwAAgPCo1oc/AAAA/glOqT8AAADI2oPDPwAAAOh50ae/AAAAsKsKiz8AAAA6AYWhvwAAAM4drpo/AAAAgBaPar8AAABUzUKsPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mean",
      "system",
      "people",
      "lot"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Good, yes, yes",
    "question": " Jamie Riley, letters and local opinions.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoAusz78AAADADNaMvwAAAMC+GJE/AAAAINfSqz8AAADgPpy+PwAAACCsaJg/AAAAoHGj0r8AAAAAPn2iPwAAAOCRv7m/AAAAgNAZxb8AAAAAlD6vvwAAAMAy9sI/AAAAYOJ40b8AAADgrtjSvwAAAABIEck/AAAAwCMGoT8AAACgV+9yPwAAAAAwQIQ/AAAAAJeAwb8AAABAoVvJvwAAAOAFTsu/AAAAgMFGxj8AAABAWq1JvwAAAGD3WcS/AAAAIJEtqD8AAABAtB3JvwAAAECJA7g/AAAAYDYnOT8AAADAmmujPwAAACBVLsO/AAAAIN3Exz8AAABgl0aKvwAAAKD1f38/AAAAYDamxr8AAAAAFHq5PwAAAMAgY4y/AAAAQO9AtD8AAABAkvhsPwAAAIC4rMQ/AAAAIEIoub8AAADguAV9vwAAACDRBMA/AAAAYPsex78AAABge8exvwAAAOAQtKg/AAAA4ESGpj8AAAAA8p6hPwAAAIAsALi/AAAAYLIPw78AAAAgBR3XPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Riley"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Hi, Christine",
    "question": " Christine Emba.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgKLckL8AAABg8q46PwAAAIBBZcQ/AAAAAIresr8AAADAb3DUvwAAAGAKn8m/AAAA4KCYuj8AAACAZta0vwAAAKDFh8s/AAAAAMgBY78AAABAneegvwAAAECyE6w/AAAA4JKEoz8AAADATsmvPwAAAOCzA8i/AAAAYAo7xr8AAABAwcLCvwAAAGA8uNY/AAAAwLrMyz8AAABgBH/DPwAAAGBfLpU/AAAAYFfItL8AAAAgPfabPwAAAEC0DLE/AAAAQFd5hL8AAAAgaGZ9PwAAACAwHbs/AAAA4FTwur8AAAAA+HjWvwAAACBS/aE/AAAAgFdLXr8AAABgCN6kPwAAACD7G5A/AAAAwOc4qz8AAACgT9anvwAAAEA7c3s/AAAAYIk+x78AAACAyYezPwAAACBjtag/AAAAIPzzyL8AAAAgKZeOPwAAAMC4NcS/AAAAAHDggD8AAADAHP2lPwAAAMCjJ8e/AAAAQEp0wr8AAACgIRPRPwAAAMD3Kb8/AAAAAOA2xb8AAACgy57GPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Emba.."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Yes",
    "question": " Mike Larabee, I’m the op-ed editor.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYK//tD8AAADAEKDDvwAAAECcJj+/AAAAoALQu78AAABgkoysvwAAAMCS6rq/AAAAAHTRoD8AAAAAkBuxvwAAACCtXsU/AAAAgKykwT8AAADA0haSPwAAAMCMkJC/AAAAADC3tj8AAAAgADOcPwAAAGDzh6y/AAAAYOE40D8AAABgGyugPwAAAADSS5W/AAAAoFIcub8AAABApPe7PwAAAEBjfoM/AAAAQJ7GwT8AAACgVTqbPwAAAEAXhq2/AAAAgImEpj8AAABgR87UPwAAAKBbp8Q/AAAAQEUnrD8AAAAADTe2vwAAAMDF3pq/AAAA4FcG1L8AAADgUyC6vwAAAGDqVNA/AAAAINF7tL8AAABgtNOSvwAAACAfz6u/AAAAgCIouD8AAABgUnfKvwAAAOAOhcQ/AAAAQIyRrD8AAABAswubvwAAAIAs2rI/AAAAoFyKzr8AAADAC7d5PwAAAED19sE/AAAAIJfror8AAABADiLSPwAAAABFoau/AAAAoKHq1b8AAADgxJDRPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Larabee"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Hi, James",
    "question": " James Downie, digital opinions editor.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQHU+x78AAABAe3fBvwAAAMBRPa8/AAAAACQSlz8AAACg7zS0vwAAAGCduLS/AAAAIBXayL8AAAAgCz+VvwAAAOAqlbU/AAAAwGsPv78AAAAgHg64vwAAAABuyNQ/AAAA4BEe2b8AAABAgZarPwAAAMARiIM/AAAAgEtor78AAAAgwKy5PwAAAOAyib2/AAAAoL3qdr8AAAAAB+iwPwAAAGCb+se/AAAAYGl3wz8AAADAlu/FPwAAAGDAuKW/AAAAQPdjmj8AAAAgFNHAPwAAAAA40MA/AAAAIDMQWz8AAACgvq2fvwAAAGCB0aU/AAAAYK5LwL8AAAAAAmHMvwAAAKDAMsU/AAAAgCXJvT8AAACgjSi+vwAAAAC7q1A/AAAAIDjJtj8AAAAgDMmWPwAAAOB7PNI/AAAAgL9cxj8AAADgMlqvPwAAACCUZqo/AAAAgJeLxr8AAADAovvMPwAAAKAnpcW/AAAAACXtuz8AAACAytrAvwAAAGB0+ag/AAAAYLS9ob8AAABAB9rMPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Downie"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "  Good",
    "question": " Jackson Diehl.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoEpywL8AAADAxiqpvwAAAKC//Y2/AAAAoNfNs78AAAAAaPV+vwAAACDzccQ/AAAAoEzEvb8AAADA0GKzvwAAAIApi56/AAAAAIsa0r8AAACg6vy5vwAAAACe4sY/AAAAgF2px78AAAAAd6LNvwAAAICv5MI/AAAAoKSpmb8AAACgbgqzPwAAACCFHJy/AAAAQFXKpD8AAADgXYS4vwAAAGAov2O/AAAAwNh7tL8AAACgjr2ivwAAAKCBusG/AAAAIMnypT8AAADAQiA6vwAAAMCwA5U/AAAAwN5Qqz8AAADAWOxhvwAAAODjjrE/AAAAgOvH2L8AAABAiirTvwAAACCI1S+/AAAAwEQsxT8AAACAMabAvwAAAMDcisG/AAAAQI1ymL8AAACgoWySPwAAAACvvc4/AAAAQNTKhb8AAABA3YrTPwAAAKDVX68/AAAAAAbwtb8AAADg8o7CvwAAACBcANA/AAAAwOb6qL8AAACAAZ+1PwAAAMCLu7U/AAAAQOIFwL8AAACAcavPPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Diehl.."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Right, right",
    "question": "  Fred Ryan.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwCa+tL8AAACgxLCivwAAAGCzC5W/AAAAoFX5qT8AAADAH2+7PwAAAGD1Qbw/AAAAoM4L178AAABAUEKvvwAAAGD2vqQ/AAAAwI0gv78AAACAd4+6vwAAAADbcrA/AAAAoKOZ0r8AAACA9lSovwAAAABbz7Q/AAAAIITXrr8AAABgbiHIPwAAAOAxKIC/AAAA4JuStb8AAADAbqSyvwAAAMC5S6S/AAAAwA05xj8AAAAAUzbJPwAAAID26MO/AAAAIOsLcz8AAAAAooO2vwAAAIBDpqy/AAAAYO2muL8AAADAqoC3vwAAACBUc7S/AAAAQDZQyT8AAADANCnBvwAAAMCela6/AAAAIFlwqb8AAAAAbIapPwAAAOApI8C/AAAAAMKbq78AAACA3IzBPwAAAIACz8o/AAAAgPHKob8AAABANyGwvwAAAOCz/b0/AAAA4CrxzL8AAACgUP7MvwAAAKCUOMI/AAAAgAN2kj8AAABAYTO0vwAAAID9Lsa/AAAA4C5gwr8AAAAAMyvbPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Fred"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Right",
    "question": " Ruth Marcus.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoBc1xb8AAACAbJDJPwAAAGA+NMG/AAAAoPMuRr8AAADA1v7OPwAAAOCbwso/AAAAAKGpxb8AAACAlk5vPwAAAOBOCJs/AAAA4PzTor8AAADA35G+vwAAAKB2DcY/AAAAgIWVtr8AAACAARq/PwAAAADCfsk/AAAAACuRsL8AAABglSeFvwAAAOBoy8a/AAAAINEqoT8AAACge6TCPwAAAGDJW5Q/AAAA4Ab1sz8AAAAgCbmhPwAAAOBSwKy/AAAAgKLitT8AAAAgJsHNvwAAAEAF568/AAAAgA5Kqb8AAADAVlWpvwAAAGAaTMW/AAAAwGgLqT8AAADAZ026vwAAAOBO5Mo/AAAAYIlzfb8AAAAAt+K/vwAAAMCPqsG/AAAAIHRVvj8AAACgnZfIPwAAAEB3BMQ/AAAAAB9/uD8AAABgGXLEvwAAAKARhcA/AAAA4FbFqL8AAADgzGKzPwAAAEDxJcS/AAAAQMaOtz8AAADgM9TRvwAAAICivtW/AAAAIKC3wb8AAACAuHDIPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Ruth"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Right",
    "question": " Steve Stromberg, editorial writer.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAInGyj8AAABgk0e2vwAAAEC/37A/AAAAwG7XzL8AAADAKsCyPwAAAABaoH8/AAAAAFY2w78AAABgM5HFvwAAAIBzbr4/AAAA4CyJs78AAACgm6zAPwAAACCdw7W/AAAAYGvQxL8AAAAA+arDvwAAAGBwHsY/AAAAAAAosD8AAAAAOMLMPwAAACBCXpa/AAAAgHRutj8AAABAQ4+pvwAAAMAVfMq/AAAAgFK9tT8AAADgfDzQvwAAAODMwbM/AAAAIHoSrT8AAADAdHbPPwAAAED7YsU/AAAAoI7ewT8AAADAJrGDvwAAACDyC6k/AAAAAJ1HzL8AAAAgpuyIvwAAAKDbvLY/AAAAAG7Ppz8AAADgIqS0vwAAAIDhy6e/AAAAILP3yD8AAABgUdzCvwAAAKA3iI8/AAAAQELL0D8AAACAYkjCPwAAAICve8I/AAAAAPzJmb8AAADAAXrLvwAAAACuRbg/AAAAYI+srr8AAAAAcJSYvwAAAABmT8o/AAAAoIKtyb8AAADguZvHPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Stromberg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Yes, I know Charles",
    "question": " I’m Charles …",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgPp1sD8AAABgtIrLPwAAAADRRLO/AAAAoJ95u78AAACgE6WXPwAAAKAtTrE/AAAAQLLbzr8AAAAA4+JzPwAAAACQq8O/AAAAYCKZwb8AAABAkeW8vwAAAOD0QNI/AAAAwKAuwb8AAAAgCrLNvwAAACAt5kW/AAAAYCeZnr8AAADgD76XPwAAAOD8jcO/AAAAwMZIxb8AAADg+Ie9vwAAAMAapbY/AAAAgBr4sT8AAABgM5qdvwAAAABKMsC/AAAAIDQbpb8AAABAWVPTvwAAAID44rC/AAAA4ODCyL8AAACAIPmavwAAAOAeEMc/AAAAAGMYyj8AAACAu5LCvwAAAABFkr6/AAAAAEMqub8AAACAMnjFPwAAAIBDoL+/AAAAoNDhrr8AAACgFV6yPwAAAEB6b6A/AAAA4ANJwT8AAACAEj/BPwAAAICLlNE/AAAA4D+6sr8AAADguhS0vwAAAKBQz6q/AAAAgOPRoD8AAABA8QnAvwAAAGDGedG/AAAAADOLt78AAABgUt3GPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Charles"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Hi, Tom",
    "question": " Tom Toles.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgNaIxL8AAADgZ1bMvwAAAKCqO8g/AAAA4J9Wwb8AAACgQkPPvwAAAACUPcU/AAAAQOF2uT8AAAAgrtjFvwAAAECIg6O/AAAAIGeKvb8AAABAXPLGvwAAAMAg8Zm/AAAAwDM7sz8AAABA75TFPwAAAIBqJ72/AAAAoGvatj8AAACAi+WgvwAAAIA4zaM/AAAAAOpho78AAADAqw66PwAAAGAQaqM/AAAA4LUgqz8AAACAbS7APwAAAKBBaII/AAAAoDORwT8AAADg3dLCPwAAAEAzmsG/AAAAgI0Tub8AAACA8E7UvwAAAEDGXqE/AAAA4OxC178AAABgK/GqPwAAAOAHS8o/AAAAoMFktj8AAABAns2WPwAAAACMdLY/AAAAoEFhmj8AAADgVMOiPwAAACCLJ6y/AAAA4Ejnwb8AAACgjrS2PwAAAMA45rQ/AAAAoCsVwb8AAADA6AbQPwAAAICuiZw/AAAA4G/dsb8AAADgknPRPwAAAKCZCLs/AAAAoHm9sL8AAAAAnLnFPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Toles.."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Okay",
    "question": " I’m Jo-Ann Armao. I cover D.C. events. I  want to ask you a question about what you think about D.C. voting rights or statehood.",
    "question_vector": "AAAA4MVTkb8AAABk16G6PwAAADxiGbC/AAAA6e2tqT8AAABwCEyZPwAAAOjZ2bQ/AAAA4gHkn78AAACcgTekvwAAADQuWbI/AAAAL2FoqL8AAADMdCG1vwAAAPBd1pK/AAAAnCCjq78AAAAIDiR+PwAAAKhK0sg/AAAAUF2xjL8AAABgH46jPwAAACWIibG/AAAA4C8Qiz8AAACLBE24vwAAYGJML7A/AADA04UhsT8AAACofOWsPwAAACBvvnQ/AAAAgPnBnT8AAACMMijSvwAAAGSt37y/AAAAgJ+lpL8AAACAJtubPwAAAACg4lq/AAAASEgB4z8AAADwyFmOPwAA6GyfWbW/AAAACeBnxL8AAABQCQ+8vwAAAKAUeXI/AAAAcA+Rjj8AAAB27iKivwAAAORTtr2/AAAA6ApBpL8AAABYtx6ivwAAwOiwFlY/AAAA8ndRsD8AAABAsBu3PwAAAJSvGKq/AAAA6CIylr8AAAC2gXOsvwAAAPnTkbE/AACgzz3Nqr8AAABQ6TVlvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "cover",
      "events.",
      "question",
      "rights"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’ll talk about that",
    "question": " I’m Jo-Ann Armao. I cover D.C. events. I  want to ask you a question about what you think about D.C. voting rights or statehood.",
    "question_vector": "AAAA4MVTkb8AAABk16G6PwAAADxiGbC/AAAA6e2tqT8AAABwCEyZPwAAAOjZ2bQ/AAAA4gHkn78AAACcgTekvwAAADQuWbI/AAAAL2FoqL8AAADMdCG1vwAAAPBd1pK/AAAAnCCjq78AAAAIDiR+PwAAAKhK0sg/AAAAUF2xjL8AAABgH46jPwAAACWIibG/AAAA4C8Qiz8AAACLBE24vwAAYGJML7A/AADA04UhsT8AAACofOWsPwAAACBvvnQ/AAAAgPnBnT8AAACMMijSvwAAAGSt37y/AAAAgJ+lpL8AAACAJtubPwAAAACg4lq/AAAASEgB4z8AAADwyFmOPwAA6GyfWbW/AAAACeBnxL8AAABQCQ+8vwAAAKAUeXI/AAAAcA+Rjj8AAAB27iKivwAAAORTtr2/AAAA6ApBpL8AAABYtx6ivwAAwOiwFlY/AAAA8ndRsD8AAABAsBu3PwAAAJSvGKq/AAAA6CIylr8AAAC2gXOsvwAAAPnTkbE/AACgzz3Nqr8AAABQ6TVlvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "cover",
      "events.",
      "question",
      "rights"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Okay we do",
    "question": " Yeah. You have a meeting you have to get to.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAGLfSwj8AAACA7VmtPwAAAOCMdKG/AAAAQAaVnD8AAAB8iXWrPwAAANg5G7K/AAAAgGFUwL8AAAAQwUmTPwAAAKD/M7i/AAAAdA6/uL8AAADQKmiavwAAAMT6EKK/AAAAsI9Lt78AAADg44epPwAAAGA2Zr8/AAAAAN10tj8AAADANlR9PwAAAAAc+bO/AAAAwCipkj8AAACqOQW3vwAAAKDe+aM/AAAAUEeKnj8AAAAw/7a8PwAAADANmp6/AAAAsG4Unb8AAABAqO/RvwAAAEA+MZc/AAAAYGakfz8AAAC63A3DvwAAAABakHg/AAAAAL3G5D8AAABAs6G7PwAAAGRDYby/AAAAoAXZuL8AAACg1TOOPwAAAIdYC7W/AAAAAM/IZD8AAAAQX/+kPwAAAAAHgqu/AAAAMFpDmj8AAAAAZL7DvwAAABhkOaA/AAAAAGtccb8AAACAazyRPwAAACgGAbU/AAAAbtEyqj8AAACohYy9vwAAANj6NcE/AAAATkDFsr8AAABY8wupvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "have",
      "meeting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’ll tell you one thing, this is a very good looking group of people here",
    "question": " This is about ISIS. You would not use a tactical nuclear weapon against ISIS?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIHipuj8AAAAg01KDPwAAAEy9Prc/AAAAfmQkmr8AAABQb3WmPwAAAKAOlpE/AAAA6AJcrz8AAADauznHvwAAAAqx6MI/AAAADJZ8wj8AAAB0qIDAPwAAABXewsc/AAAAQFmTfr8AAAAwk7aiPwAAAHRuKLy/AACA/Ckguz8AAAD+HRWrvwAAAHCm0rA/AAAAy/HboL8AAACk+AyyPwAAACDtDK0/AAAAIOgZlD8AAACYPWSsPwAAAMzCibS/AAAAsPqWpz8AAABj8izIvwAAAHrVPbO/AAAAwiN0rr8AAADgzWysvwAAABhzH7y/AAAAE0Fz0D8AAAAqYkG6vwAAAIDeSq6/AAAAgo/Ssr8AAADwv0GnPwAAALhyhLE/AAAAhMA9qT8AAABkUUeyvwAAAGAqpaC/AAAAuAEdjD8AAAAg12qsPwAAAKRxULG/AAAAYIudjT8AAAAlbSymPwAAAOiFxbg/AAAAQMCMbz8AAAAQF4CvPwAAABCsrae/AAAAAFtskD8AAIA5WDrGvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "use",
      "ISIS.",
      "weapon",
      "ISIS"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "  Could I just go around so I know who the hell I’m talking to?",
    "question": " This is about ISIS. You would not use a tactical nuclear weapon against ISIS?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIHipuj8AAAAg01KDPwAAAEy9Prc/AAAAfmQkmr8AAABQb3WmPwAAAKAOlpE/AAAA6AJcrz8AAADauznHvwAAAAqx6MI/AAAADJZ8wj8AAAB0qIDAPwAAABXewsc/AAAAQFmTfr8AAAAwk7aiPwAAAHRuKLy/AACA/Ckguz8AAAD+HRWrvwAAAHCm0rA/AAAAy/HboL8AAACk+AyyPwAAACDtDK0/AAAAIOgZlD8AAACYPWSsPwAAAMzCibS/AAAAsPqWpz8AAABj8izIvwAAAHrVPbO/AAAAwiN0rr8AAADgzWysvwAAABhzH7y/AAAAE0Fz0D8AAAAqYkG6vwAAAIDeSq6/AAAAgo/Ssr8AAADwv0GnPwAAALhyhLE/AAAAhMA9qT8AAABkUUeyvwAAAGAqpaC/AAAAuAEdjD8AAAAg12qsPwAAAKRxULG/AAAAYIudjT8AAAAlbSymPwAAAOiFxbg/AAAAQMCMbz8AAAAQF4CvPwAAABCsrae/AAAAAFtskD8AAIA5WDrGvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "use",
      "ISIS.",
      "weapon",
      "ISIS"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I don’t want to use, I don’t want to start the process of nuclear",
    "question": " You [MUFFLED] mentioned a few minutes earlier here that you would knock ISIS. You’ve mentioned it many times. You’ve also mentioned the risk of putting American troop in a danger area. If you could substantially reduce the risk of harm to ground troops, would you use a battlefield nuclear weapon to take out ISIS?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQDQKxj8AAABAT//FPwAAAGBoc6u/AAAA4MEqp78AAADgIIC3PwAAAIBlj5g/AAAAAAViwb8AAADAojCgvwAAAIAGRMm/AAAA4ARMv78AAABAyCi+vwAAAOD47cc/AAAAAHB5nj8AAAAAULrGvwAAAICiHNA/AAAAoCx3gj8AAACAlDe+vwAAACB/dLy/AAAA4NYHjL8AAAAguv6yPwAAAOA1+n2/AAAAQKNywr8AAACAqR3MPwAAAAAm1bE/AAAAoMUIxz8AAACATB/SvwAAAMA9Uc2/AAAAoDeAr78AAADg05CovwAAAMAtK4k/AAAAAB983j8AAACggZ3NvwAAAGCnSnA/AAAA4B51xr8AAACA1p+nPwAAAKADx6S/AAAAYHmMtD8AAAAApOymPwAAAMDKG8y/AAAAAEApwz8AAAAAAbilPwAAACCFX5w/AAAAgH1HuL8AAACg1EyyPwAAAMBpRbS/AAAA4Lsqnj8AAACgX/m1vwAAAADAi6w/AAAAwC94rb8AAAAA2GpZPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mentioned",
      "Youve",
      "mentioned",
      "Youve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Remember the one thing that everybody has said, I’m a counterpuncher",
    "question": " You [MUFFLED] mentioned a few minutes earlier here that you would knock ISIS. You’ve mentioned it many times. You’ve also mentioned the risk of putting American troop in a danger area. If you could substantially reduce the risk of harm to ground troops, would you use a battlefield nuclear weapon to take out ISIS?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQDQKxj8AAABAT//FPwAAAGBoc6u/AAAA4MEqp78AAADgIIC3PwAAAIBlj5g/AAAAAAViwb8AAADAojCgvwAAAIAGRMm/AAAA4ARMv78AAABAyCi+vwAAAOD47cc/AAAAAHB5nj8AAAAAULrGvwAAAICiHNA/AAAAoCx3gj8AAACAlDe+vwAAACB/dLy/AAAA4NYHjL8AAAAguv6yPwAAAOA1+n2/AAAAQKNywr8AAACAqR3MPwAAAAAm1bE/AAAAoMUIxz8AAACATB/SvwAAAMA9Uc2/AAAAoDeAr78AAADg05CovwAAAMAtK4k/AAAAAB983j8AAACggZ3NvwAAAGCnSnA/AAAA4B51xr8AAACA1p+nPwAAAKADx6S/AAAAYHmMtD8AAAAApOymPwAAAMDKG8y/AAAAAEApwz8AAAAAAbilPwAAACCFX5w/AAAAgH1HuL8AAACg1EyyPwAAAMBpRbS/AAAA4Lsqnj8AAACgX/m1vwAAAADAi6w/AAAAwC94rb8AAAAA2GpZPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mentioned",
      "Youve",
      "mentioned",
      "Youve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Rubio hit me",
    "question": " You [MUFFLED] mentioned a few minutes earlier here that you would knock ISIS. You’ve mentioned it many times. You’ve also mentioned the risk of putting American troop in a danger area. If you could substantially reduce the risk of harm to ground troops, would you use a battlefield nuclear weapon to take out ISIS?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQDQKxj8AAABAT//FPwAAAGBoc6u/AAAA4MEqp78AAADgIIC3PwAAAIBlj5g/AAAAAAViwb8AAADAojCgvwAAAIAGRMm/AAAA4ARMv78AAABAyCi+vwAAAOD47cc/AAAAAHB5nj8AAAAAULrGvwAAAICiHNA/AAAAoCx3gj8AAACAlDe+vwAAACB/dLy/AAAA4NYHjL8AAAAguv6yPwAAAOA1+n2/AAAAQKNywr8AAACAqR3MPwAAAAAm1bE/AAAAoMUIxz8AAACATB/SvwAAAMA9Uc2/AAAAoDeAr78AAADg05CovwAAAMAtK4k/AAAAAB983j8AAACggZ3NvwAAAGCnSnA/AAAA4B51xr8AAACA1p+nPwAAAKADx6S/AAAAYHmMtD8AAAAApOymPwAAAMDKG8y/AAAAAEApwz8AAAAAAbilPwAAACCFX5w/AAAAgH1HuL8AAACg1EyyPwAAAMBpRbS/AAAA4Lsqnj8AAACgX/m1vwAAAADAi6w/AAAAwC94rb8AAAAA2GpZPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mentioned",
      "Youve",
      "mentioned",
      "Youve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Bush hit me",
    "question": " You [MUFFLED] mentioned a few minutes earlier here that you would knock ISIS. You’ve mentioned it many times. You’ve also mentioned the risk of putting American troop in a danger area. If you could substantially reduce the risk of harm to ground troops, would you use a battlefield nuclear weapon to take out ISIS?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQDQKxj8AAABAT//FPwAAAGBoc6u/AAAA4MEqp78AAADgIIC3PwAAAIBlj5g/AAAAAAViwb8AAADAojCgvwAAAIAGRMm/AAAA4ARMv78AAABAyCi+vwAAAOD47cc/AAAAAHB5nj8AAAAAULrGvwAAAICiHNA/AAAAoCx3gj8AAACAlDe+vwAAACB/dLy/AAAA4NYHjL8AAAAguv6yPwAAAOA1+n2/AAAAQKNywr8AAACAqR3MPwAAAAAm1bE/AAAAoMUIxz8AAACATB/SvwAAAMA9Uc2/AAAAoDeAr78AAADg05CovwAAAMAtK4k/AAAAAB983j8AAACggZ3NvwAAAGCnSnA/AAAA4B51xr8AAACA1p+nPwAAAKADx6S/AAAAYHmMtD8AAAAApOymPwAAAMDKG8y/AAAAAEApwz8AAAAAAbilPwAAACCFX5w/AAAAgH1HuL8AAACg1EyyPwAAAMBpRbS/AAAA4Lsqnj8AAACgX/m1vwAAAADAi6w/AAAAwC94rb8AAAAA2GpZPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mentioned",
      "Youve",
      "mentioned",
      "Youve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " When I said low energy, he’s a low-energy individual, he hit me first",
    "question": " You [MUFFLED] mentioned a few minutes earlier here that you would knock ISIS. You’ve mentioned it many times. You’ve also mentioned the risk of putting American troop in a danger area. If you could substantially reduce the risk of harm to ground troops, would you use a battlefield nuclear weapon to take out ISIS?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQDQKxj8AAABAT//FPwAAAGBoc6u/AAAA4MEqp78AAADgIIC3PwAAAIBlj5g/AAAAAAViwb8AAADAojCgvwAAAIAGRMm/AAAA4ARMv78AAABAyCi+vwAAAOD47cc/AAAAAHB5nj8AAAAAULrGvwAAAICiHNA/AAAAoCx3gj8AAACAlDe+vwAAACB/dLy/AAAA4NYHjL8AAAAguv6yPwAAAOA1+n2/AAAAQKNywr8AAACAqR3MPwAAAAAm1bE/AAAAoMUIxz8AAACATB/SvwAAAMA9Uc2/AAAAoDeAr78AAADg05CovwAAAMAtK4k/AAAAAB983j8AAACggZ3NvwAAAGCnSnA/AAAA4B51xr8AAACA1p+nPwAAAKADx6S/AAAAYHmMtD8AAAAApOymPwAAAMDKG8y/AAAAAEApwz8AAAAAAbilPwAAACCFX5w/AAAAgH1HuL8AAACg1EyyPwAAAMBpRbS/AAAA4Lsqnj8AAACgX/m1vwAAAADAi6w/AAAAwC94rb8AAAAA2GpZPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mentioned",
      "Youve",
      "mentioned",
      "Youve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I spent, by the way he spent 18 million dollars’ worth of negative ads on me",
    "question": " You [MUFFLED] mentioned a few minutes earlier here that you would knock ISIS. You’ve mentioned it many times. You’ve also mentioned the risk of putting American troop in a danger area. If you could substantially reduce the risk of harm to ground troops, would you use a battlefield nuclear weapon to take out ISIS?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQDQKxj8AAABAT//FPwAAAGBoc6u/AAAA4MEqp78AAADgIIC3PwAAAIBlj5g/AAAAAAViwb8AAADAojCgvwAAAIAGRMm/AAAA4ARMv78AAABAyCi+vwAAAOD47cc/AAAAAHB5nj8AAAAAULrGvwAAAICiHNA/AAAAoCx3gj8AAACAlDe+vwAAACB/dLy/AAAA4NYHjL8AAAAguv6yPwAAAOA1+n2/AAAAQKNywr8AAACAqR3MPwAAAAAm1bE/AAAAoMUIxz8AAACATB/SvwAAAMA9Uc2/AAAAoDeAr78AAADg05CovwAAAMAtK4k/AAAAAB983j8AAACggZ3NvwAAAGCnSnA/AAAA4B51xr8AAACA1p+nPwAAAKADx6S/AAAAYHmMtD8AAAAApOymPwAAAMDKG8y/AAAAAEApwz8AAAAAAbilPwAAACCFX5w/AAAAgH1HuL8AAACg1EyyPwAAAMBpRbS/AAAA4Lsqnj8AAACgX/m1vwAAAADAi6w/AAAAwC94rb8AAAAA2GpZPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mentioned",
      "Youve",
      "mentioned",
      "Youve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " That’s putting [MUFFLED]…",
    "question": " You [MUFFLED] mentioned a few minutes earlier here that you would knock ISIS. You’ve mentioned it many times. You’ve also mentioned the risk of putting American troop in a danger area. If you could substantially reduce the risk of harm to ground troops, would you use a battlefield nuclear weapon to take out ISIS?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQDQKxj8AAABAT//FPwAAAGBoc6u/AAAA4MEqp78AAADgIIC3PwAAAIBlj5g/AAAAAAViwb8AAADAojCgvwAAAIAGRMm/AAAA4ARMv78AAABAyCi+vwAAAOD47cc/AAAAAHB5nj8AAAAAULrGvwAAAICiHNA/AAAAoCx3gj8AAACAlDe+vwAAACB/dLy/AAAA4NYHjL8AAAAguv6yPwAAAOA1+n2/AAAAQKNywr8AAACAqR3MPwAAAAAm1bE/AAAAoMUIxz8AAACATB/SvwAAAMA9Uc2/AAAAoDeAr78AAADg05CovwAAAMAtK4k/AAAAAB983j8AAACggZ3NvwAAAGCnSnA/AAAA4B51xr8AAACA1p+nPwAAAKADx6S/AAAAYHmMtD8AAAAApOymPwAAAMDKG8y/AAAAAEApwz8AAAAAAbilPwAAACCFX5w/AAAAgH1HuL8AAACg1EyyPwAAAMBpRbS/AAAA4Lsqnj8AAACgX/m1vwAAAADAi6w/AAAAwC94rb8AAAAA2GpZPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mentioned",
      "Youve",
      "mentioned",
      "Youve"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I did feel I should respond",
    "question": " Okay, let’s move on here. Let’s move on.",
    "question_vector": "q6qqStM3tT8AAACA/Kavv6uqqgpGpsc/AAAAACKgcb9VVVX937ijP1VVVdX54Li/AAAAAJWSt79VVVVVJdtUP6uqqqpZ/oo/q6qqbohTsj8AAABgWYGQv6uqqgYUBL8/AAAAAEJtlj+rqqpKgwO4P6uqqgKRP7A/VVVV9VFTxT+rqqrq9o+YP6uqquqI0LW/q6qqih4Wuz+rqqrKOqDMv1VVVXU6obU/AAAAANauiT+rqqoKiiC5v6uqKuDVBsc/AAAAyFZKvz+rqqqK/RLRvwAAAADgwKg/AAAAwBgsqL+rqqqKkM69P6uqquLFqMm/VVVVtVzQ4D9VVVUVDG26P1VVVWXzT8S/VVVV1R0xpL8AAABANLqxvwAAAAC2F3E/AAAAQC9fi7+rqqr6kMq0v1VVVTXeMaG/VVVV1fQwyL8AAABwHoW/PwAAAGazkqY/VVVVhSWpiT+rqqr6RyizPwAAANi7wJa/AAAAwGF5hD9VVVWNuUPFPwAAAMA6H6m/VVVVNUVdlr8AAABwP4G0Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Lets",
      "move"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Maybe I’m wrong",
    "question": " Okay, let’s move on here. Let’s move on.",
    "question_vector": "q6qqStM3tT8AAACA/Kavv6uqqgpGpsc/AAAAACKgcb9VVVX937ijP1VVVdX54Li/AAAAAJWSt79VVVVVJdtUP6uqqqpZ/oo/q6qqbohTsj8AAABgWYGQv6uqqgYUBL8/AAAAAEJtlj+rqqpKgwO4P6uqqgKRP7A/VVVV9VFTxT+rqqrq9o+YP6uqquqI0LW/q6qqih4Wuz+rqqrKOqDMv1VVVXU6obU/AAAAANauiT+rqqoKiiC5v6uqKuDVBsc/AAAAyFZKvz+rqqqK/RLRvwAAAADgwKg/AAAAwBgsqL+rqqqKkM69P6uqquLFqMm/VVVVtVzQ4D9VVVUVDG26P1VVVWXzT8S/VVVV1R0xpL8AAABANLqxvwAAAAC2F3E/AAAAQC9fi7+rqqr6kMq0v1VVVTXeMaG/VVVV1fQwyL8AAABwHoW/PwAAAGazkqY/VVVVhSWpiT+rqqr6RyizPwAAANi7wJa/AAAAwGF5hD9VVVWNuUPFPwAAAMA6H6m/VVVVNUVdlr8AAABwP4G0Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Lets",
      "move"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I don’t know",
    "question": " Okay, let’s move on here. Let’s move on.",
    "question_vector": "q6qqStM3tT8AAACA/Kavv6uqqgpGpsc/AAAAACKgcb9VVVX937ijP1VVVdX54Li/AAAAAJWSt79VVVVVJdtUP6uqqqpZ/oo/q6qqbohTsj8AAABgWYGQv6uqqgYUBL8/AAAAAEJtlj+rqqpKgwO4P6uqqgKRP7A/VVVV9VFTxT+rqqrq9o+YP6uqquqI0LW/q6qqih4Wuz+rqqrKOqDMv1VVVXU6obU/AAAAANauiT+rqqoKiiC5v6uqKuDVBsc/AAAAyFZKvz+rqqqK/RLRvwAAAADgwKg/AAAAwBgsqL+rqqqKkM69P6uqquLFqMm/VVVVtVzQ4D9VVVUVDG26P1VVVWXzT8S/VVVV1R0xpL8AAABANLqxvwAAAAC2F3E/AAAAQC9fi7+rqqr6kMq0v1VVVTXeMaG/VVVV1fQwyL8AAABwHoW/PwAAAGazkqY/VVVVhSWpiT+rqqr6RyizPwAAANi7wJa/AAAAwGF5hD9VVVWNuUPFPwAAAMA6H6m/VVVVNUVdlr8AAABwP4G0Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Lets",
      "move"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But I felt I should respond because everybody was talking about it",
    "question": " Okay, let’s move on here. Let’s move on.",
    "question_vector": "q6qqStM3tT8AAACA/Kavv6uqqgpGpsc/AAAAACKgcb9VVVX937ijP1VVVdX54Li/AAAAAJWSt79VVVVVJdtUP6uqqqpZ/oo/q6qqbohTsj8AAABgWYGQv6uqqgYUBL8/AAAAAEJtlj+rqqpKgwO4P6uqqgKRP7A/VVVV9VFTxT+rqqrq9o+YP6uqquqI0LW/q6qqih4Wuz+rqqrKOqDMv1VVVXU6obU/AAAAANauiT+rqqoKiiC5v6uqKuDVBsc/AAAAyFZKvz+rqqqK/RLRvwAAAADgwKg/AAAAwBgsqL+rqqqKkM69P6uqquLFqMm/VVVVtVzQ4D9VVVUVDG26P1VVVWXzT8S/VVVV1R0xpL8AAABANLqxvwAAAAC2F3E/AAAAQC9fi7+rqqr6kMq0v1VVVTXeMaG/VVVV1fQwyL8AAABwHoW/PwAAAGazkqY/VVVVhSWpiT+rqqr6RyizPwAAANi7wJa/AAAAwGF5hD9VVVWNuUPFPwAAAMA6H6m/VVVVNUVdlr8AAABwP4G0Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Lets",
      "move"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I don’t know if it was presidential, honestly, whether it is or not",
    "question": " You told us in the debate that you guaranteed there was not another problem. Was that presidential? And why did you decide to do that?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqiotGrz9VVVUFoDGVP1VVVZVWd5q/VVVVNQdukj+rqqrqal+YPwAAAIDToaw/q6qqKvuWpb+rqqpqP7l+PwAAAIBSx4O/VVVV8cYXuL8AAABoaDyxv1VVVZWz55q/VVVVWSUNvb8AAAAQyzmiP1VVVcXGPcI/q6qqgt+gsD+rqqqRm9WbP6uqqipemY2/q6qqMhLRrT9VVVWFZsyxv6uqqopqc4q/VVVVpZ7gtD+rqqrqyYmRP6uqqqp0yJ4/VVVVhfWswD+rqqrKoz3Yv6uqqor91Ys/AAAA4OWbsj9VVVXVoPGYv1VVVZerP7c/q6qqyg3c4D+rqqrKFDqSPwAAAOiY07q/AAAAeF3kw7+rqqqa4IC9v1VVVfUOI66/VVVV1UH3mb8AAAAAKNxdPwAAAMDkA6o/q6qq6ufylT9VVVU16Kauv1VVVb3Qvbs/q6qqOpJwq78AAABAXmOxPwAAAEDkB6s/AAAAUPmTpD9VVVXVdu+cv6uqquqmtsQ/VVVVVaP4kT+rqqpKK5iyPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate",
      "problem."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " He said, ‘Donald Trump has small hands and therefore he has small something else",
    "question": " You told us in the debate that you guaranteed there was not another problem. Was that presidential? And why did you decide to do that?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqiotGrz9VVVUFoDGVP1VVVZVWd5q/VVVVNQdukj+rqqrqal+YPwAAAIDToaw/q6qqKvuWpb+rqqpqP7l+PwAAAIBSx4O/VVVV8cYXuL8AAABoaDyxv1VVVZWz55q/VVVVWSUNvb8AAAAQyzmiP1VVVcXGPcI/q6qqgt+gsD+rqqqRm9WbP6uqqipemY2/q6qqMhLRrT9VVVWFZsyxv6uqqopqc4q/VVVVpZ7gtD+rqqrqyYmRP6uqqqp0yJ4/VVVVhfWswD+rqqrKoz3Yv6uqqor91Ys/AAAA4OWbsj9VVVXVoPGYv1VVVZerP7c/q6qqyg3c4D+rqqrKFDqSPwAAAOiY07q/AAAAeF3kw7+rqqqa4IC9v1VVVfUOI66/VVVV1UH3mb8AAAAAKNxdPwAAAMDkA6o/q6qq6ufylT9VVVU16Kauv1VVVb3Qvbs/q6qqOpJwq78AAABAXmOxPwAAAEDkB6s/AAAAUPmTpD9VVVXVdu+cv6uqquqmtsQ/VVVVVaP4kT+rqqpKK5iyPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate",
      "problem."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "’ I didn’t say that",
    "question": " You told us in the debate that you guaranteed there was not another problem. Was that presidential? And why did you decide to do that?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqiotGrz9VVVUFoDGVP1VVVZVWd5q/VVVVNQdukj+rqqrqal+YPwAAAIDToaw/q6qqKvuWpb+rqqpqP7l+PwAAAIBSx4O/VVVV8cYXuL8AAABoaDyxv1VVVZWz55q/VVVVWSUNvb8AAAAQyzmiP1VVVcXGPcI/q6qqgt+gsD+rqqqRm9WbP6uqqipemY2/q6qqMhLRrT9VVVWFZsyxv6uqqopqc4q/VVVVpZ7gtD+rqqrqyYmRP6uqqqp0yJ4/VVVVhfWswD+rqqrKoz3Yv6uqqor91Ys/AAAA4OWbsj9VVVXVoPGYv1VVVZerP7c/q6qqyg3c4D+rqqrKFDqSPwAAAOiY07q/AAAAeF3kw7+rqqqa4IC9v1VVVfUOI66/VVVV1UH3mb8AAAAAKNxdPwAAAMDkA6o/q6qq6ufylT9VVVU16Kauv1VVVb3Qvbs/q6qqOpJwq78AAABAXmOxPwAAAEDkB6s/AAAAUPmTpD9VVVXVdu+cv6uqquqmtsQ/VVVVVaP4kT+rqqpKK5iyPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate",
      "problem."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And all I did is when he failed, when he was failing, when he was, when Christie made him look bad, I gave him the– a little recap and I said,  and I said, and I had this big strong powerful hand ready to grab him, because I thought he was going to faint",
    "question": " You told us in the debate that you guaranteed there was not another problem. Was that presidential? And why did you decide to do that?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqiotGrz9VVVUFoDGVP1VVVZVWd5q/VVVVNQdukj+rqqrqal+YPwAAAIDToaw/q6qqKvuWpb+rqqpqP7l+PwAAAIBSx4O/VVVV8cYXuL8AAABoaDyxv1VVVZWz55q/VVVVWSUNvb8AAAAQyzmiP1VVVcXGPcI/q6qqgt+gsD+rqqqRm9WbP6uqqipemY2/q6qqMhLRrT9VVVWFZsyxv6uqqopqc4q/VVVVpZ7gtD+rqqrqyYmRP6uqqqp0yJ4/VVVVhfWswD+rqqrKoz3Yv6uqqor91Ys/AAAA4OWbsj9VVVXVoPGYv1VVVZerP7c/q6qqyg3c4D+rqqrKFDqSPwAAAOiY07q/AAAAeF3kw7+rqqqa4IC9v1VVVfUOI66/VVVV1UH3mb8AAAAAKNxdPwAAAMDkA6o/q6qq6ufylT9VVVU16Kauv1VVVb3Qvbs/q6qqOpJwq78AAABAXmOxPwAAAEDkB6s/AAAAUPmTpD9VVVXVdu+cv6uqquqmtsQ/VVVVVaP4kT+rqqpKK5iyPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate",
      "problem."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And everybody took it fine",
    "question": " You told us in the debate that you guaranteed there was not another problem. Was that presidential? And why did you decide to do that?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqiotGrz9VVVUFoDGVP1VVVZVWd5q/VVVVNQdukj+rqqrqal+YPwAAAIDToaw/q6qqKvuWpb+rqqpqP7l+PwAAAIBSx4O/VVVV8cYXuL8AAABoaDyxv1VVVZWz55q/VVVVWSUNvb8AAAAQyzmiP1VVVcXGPcI/q6qqgt+gsD+rqqqRm9WbP6uqqipemY2/q6qqMhLRrT9VVVWFZsyxv6uqqopqc4q/VVVVpZ7gtD+rqqrqyYmRP6uqqqp0yJ4/VVVVhfWswD+rqqrKoz3Yv6uqqor91Ys/AAAA4OWbsj9VVVXVoPGYv1VVVZerP7c/q6qqyg3c4D+rqqrKFDqSPwAAAOiY07q/AAAAeF3kw7+rqqqa4IC9v1VVVfUOI66/VVVV1UH3mb8AAAAAKNxdPwAAAMDkA6o/q6qq6ufylT9VVVU16Kauv1VVVb3Qvbs/q6qqOpJwq78AAABAXmOxPwAAAEDkB6s/AAAAUPmTpD9VVVXVdu+cv6uqquqmtsQ/VVVVVaP4kT+rqqpKK5iyPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate",
      "problem."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Whether it was presidential or not I can’t tell you",
    "question": " You told us in the debate that you guaranteed there was not another problem. Was that presidential? And why did you decide to do that?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqiotGrz9VVVUFoDGVP1VVVZVWd5q/VVVVNQdukj+rqqrqal+YPwAAAIDToaw/q6qqKvuWpb+rqqpqP7l+PwAAAIBSx4O/VVVV8cYXuL8AAABoaDyxv1VVVZWz55q/VVVVWSUNvb8AAAAQyzmiP1VVVcXGPcI/q6qqgt+gsD+rqqqRm9WbP6uqqipemY2/q6qqMhLRrT9VVVWFZsyxv6uqqopqc4q/VVVVpZ7gtD+rqqrqyYmRP6uqqqp0yJ4/VVVVhfWswD+rqqrKoz3Yv6uqqor91Ys/AAAA4OWbsj9VVVXVoPGYv1VVVZerP7c/q6qqyg3c4D+rqqrKFDqSPwAAAOiY07q/AAAAeF3kw7+rqqqa4IC9v1VVVfUOI66/VVVV1UH3mb8AAAAAKNxdPwAAAMDkA6o/q6qq6ufylT9VVVU16Kauv1VVVb3Qvbs/q6qqOpJwq78AAABAXmOxPwAAAEDkB6s/AAAAUPmTpD9VVVXVdu+cv6uqquqmtsQ/VVVVVaP4kT+rqqpKK5iyPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate",
      "problem."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I can just say that what he said was a lie",
    "question": " You told us in the debate that you guaranteed there was not another problem. Was that presidential? And why did you decide to do that?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqiotGrz9VVVUFoDGVP1VVVZVWd5q/VVVVNQdukj+rqqrqal+YPwAAAIDToaw/q6qqKvuWpb+rqqpqP7l+PwAAAIBSx4O/VVVV8cYXuL8AAABoaDyxv1VVVZWz55q/VVVVWSUNvb8AAAAQyzmiP1VVVcXGPcI/q6qqgt+gsD+rqqqRm9WbP6uqqipemY2/q6qqMhLRrT9VVVWFZsyxv6uqqopqc4q/VVVVpZ7gtD+rqqrqyYmRP6uqqqp0yJ4/VVVVhfWswD+rqqrKoz3Yv6uqqor91Ys/AAAA4OWbsj9VVVXVoPGYv1VVVZerP7c/q6qqyg3c4D+rqqrKFDqSPwAAAOiY07q/AAAAeF3kw7+rqqqa4IC9v1VVVfUOI66/VVVV1UH3mb8AAAAAKNxdPwAAAMDkA6o/q6qq6ufylT9VVVU16Kauv1VVVb3Qvbs/q6qqOpJwq78AAABAXmOxPwAAAEDkB6s/AAAAUPmTpD9VVVXVdu+cv6uqquqmtsQ/VVVVVaP4kT+rqqpKK5iyPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate",
      "problem."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And everybody, they wanted to do stories on my hands; after I said that, they never did",
    "question": " You told us in the debate that you guaranteed there was not another problem. Was that presidential? And why did you decide to do that?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqiotGrz9VVVUFoDGVP1VVVZVWd5q/VVVVNQdukj+rqqrqal+YPwAAAIDToaw/q6qqKvuWpb+rqqpqP7l+PwAAAIBSx4O/VVVV8cYXuL8AAABoaDyxv1VVVZWz55q/VVVVWSUNvb8AAAAQyzmiP1VVVcXGPcI/q6qqgt+gsD+rqqqRm9WbP6uqqipemY2/q6qqMhLRrT9VVVWFZsyxv6uqqopqc4q/VVVVpZ7gtD+rqqrqyYmRP6uqqqp0yJ4/VVVVhfWswD+rqqrKoz3Yv6uqqor91Ys/AAAA4OWbsj9VVVXVoPGYv1VVVZerP7c/q6qqyg3c4D+rqqrKFDqSPwAAAOiY07q/AAAAeF3kw7+rqqqa4IC9v1VVVfUOI66/VVVV1UH3mb8AAAAAKNxdPwAAAMDkA6o/q6qq6ufylT9VVVU16Kauv1VVVb3Qvbs/q6qqOpJwq78AAABAXmOxPwAAAEDkB6s/AAAAUPmTpD9VVVXVdu+cv6uqquqmtsQ/VVVVVaP4kT+rqqpKK5iyPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate",
      "problem."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And then I held up the hand, I showed people the hand",
    "question": " You told us in the debate that you guaranteed there was not another problem. Was that presidential? And why did you decide to do that?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqiotGrz9VVVUFoDGVP1VVVZVWd5q/VVVVNQdukj+rqqrqal+YPwAAAIDToaw/q6qqKvuWpb+rqqpqP7l+PwAAAIBSx4O/VVVV8cYXuL8AAABoaDyxv1VVVZWz55q/VVVVWSUNvb8AAAAQyzmiP1VVVcXGPcI/q6qqgt+gsD+rqqqRm9WbP6uqqipemY2/q6qqMhLRrT9VVVWFZsyxv6uqqopqc4q/VVVVpZ7gtD+rqqrqyYmRP6uqqqp0yJ4/VVVVhfWswD+rqqrKoz3Yv6uqqor91Ys/AAAA4OWbsj9VVVXVoPGYv1VVVZerP7c/q6qqyg3c4D+rqqrKFDqSPwAAAOiY07q/AAAAeF3kw7+rqqqa4IC9v1VVVfUOI66/VVVV1UH3mb8AAAAAKNxdPwAAAMDkA6o/q6qq6ufylT9VVVU16Kauv1VVVb3Qvbs/q6qqOpJwq78AAABAXmOxPwAAAEDkB6s/AAAAUPmTpD9VVVXVdu+cv6uqquqmtsQ/VVVVVaP4kT+rqqpKK5iyPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate",
      "problem."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You know, when I’ve got a big audience",
    "question": " You told us in the debate that you guaranteed there was not another problem. Was that presidential? And why did you decide to do that?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqiotGrz9VVVUFoDGVP1VVVZVWd5q/VVVVNQdukj+rqqrqal+YPwAAAIDToaw/q6qqKvuWpb+rqqpqP7l+PwAAAIBSx4O/VVVV8cYXuL8AAABoaDyxv1VVVZWz55q/VVVVWSUNvb8AAAAQyzmiP1VVVcXGPcI/q6qqgt+gsD+rqqqRm9WbP6uqqipemY2/q6qqMhLRrT9VVVWFZsyxv6uqqopqc4q/VVVVpZ7gtD+rqqrqyYmRP6uqqqp0yJ4/VVVVhfWswD+rqqrKoz3Yv6uqqor91Ys/AAAA4OWbsj9VVVXVoPGYv1VVVZerP7c/q6qqyg3c4D+rqqrKFDqSPwAAAOiY07q/AAAAeF3kw7+rqqqa4IC9v1VVVfUOI66/VVVV1UH3mb8AAAAAKNxdPwAAAMDkA6o/q6qq6ufylT9VVVU16Kauv1VVVb3Qvbs/q6qqOpJwq78AAABAXmOxPwAAAEDkB6s/AAAAUPmTpD9VVVXVdu+cv6uqquqmtsQ/VVVVVaP4kT+rqqpKK5iyPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate",
      "problem."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " So yeah, I think it’s not a question of presidential …",
    "question": " You told us in the debate that you guaranteed there was not another problem. Was that presidential? And why did you decide to do that?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqiotGrz9VVVUFoDGVP1VVVZVWd5q/VVVVNQdukj+rqqrqal+YPwAAAIDToaw/q6qqKvuWpb+rqqpqP7l+PwAAAIBSx4O/VVVV8cYXuL8AAABoaDyxv1VVVZWz55q/VVVVWSUNvb8AAAAQyzmiP1VVVcXGPcI/q6qqgt+gsD+rqqqRm9WbP6uqqipemY2/q6qqMhLRrT9VVVWFZsyxv6uqqopqc4q/VVVVpZ7gtD+rqqrqyYmRP6uqqqp0yJ4/VVVVhfWswD+rqqrKoz3Yv6uqqor91Ys/AAAA4OWbsj9VVVXVoPGYv1VVVZerP7c/q6qqyg3c4D+rqqrKFDqSPwAAAOiY07q/AAAAeF3kw7+rqqqa4IC9v1VVVfUOI66/VVVV1UH3mb8AAAAAKNxdPwAAAMDkA6o/q6qq6ufylT9VVVU16Kauv1VVVb3Qvbs/q6qqOpJwq78AAABAXmOxPwAAAEDkB6s/AAAAUPmTpD9VVVXVdu+cv6uqquqmtsQ/VVVVVaP4kT+rqqpKK5iyPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate",
      "problem."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And by saying that, I solved the problem",
    "question": " You told us in the debate ….",
    "question_vector": "AAAAILmMkj8AAACYmXaaPwAAABCtlqa/AAAAQMxflD8AAAAAiU6oPwAAAADEl2c/AAAAcMIdtb8AAACk/GOlPwAAANC9ram/AAAAujDOu78AAACSzhjAvwAAABhLybK/AAAARoFHs78AAABM/Tm0PwAAAFBA4L4/AAAAqDn/oj8AAABqbm10PwAAABC8rKS/AAAA7LbcoD8AAADQwCCtvwAAAAzZP6w/AAAAbIX9wj8AAACgKjioPwAAAIAFv4k/AAAAUC0cvj8AAACAW5HYvwAAANTmXqE/AAAA8GBDsz8AAAAQrzu9vwAAANMrobY/AAAAQLXn3T8AAAAglsaDPwAAAPBKNsO/AAAA1Nq4wr8AAADoATXCvwAAADBtWr6/AAAAAA5Peb8AAACAyAl9vwAAAACtx38/AAAAgK2ThD8AAAAQRrSgvwAAAI5SMcA/AAAASOgqtr8AAAAAXbuOPwAAAPAKtqs/AAAAwKlVpz8AAABgA4a4vwAAAGBY28I/AAAAAFCnQL8AAADYuzC5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Nobody questions",
    "question": " You told us in the debate ….",
    "question_vector": "AAAAILmMkj8AAACYmXaaPwAAABCtlqa/AAAAQMxflD8AAAAAiU6oPwAAAADEl2c/AAAAcMIdtb8AAACk/GOlPwAAANC9ram/AAAAujDOu78AAACSzhjAvwAAABhLybK/AAAARoFHs78AAABM/Tm0PwAAAFBA4L4/AAAAqDn/oj8AAABqbm10PwAAABC8rKS/AAAA7LbcoD8AAADQwCCtvwAAAAzZP6w/AAAAbIX9wj8AAACgKjioPwAAAIAFv4k/AAAAUC0cvj8AAACAW5HYvwAAANTmXqE/AAAA8GBDsz8AAAAQrzu9vwAAANMrobY/AAAAQLXn3T8AAAAglsaDPwAAAPBKNsO/AAAA1Nq4wr8AAADoATXCvwAAADBtWr6/AAAAAA5Peb8AAACAyAl9vwAAAACtx38/AAAAgK2ThD8AAAAQRrSgvwAAAI5SMcA/AAAASOgqtr8AAAAAXbuOPwAAAPAKtqs/AAAAwKlVpz8AAABgA4a4vwAAAGBY28I/AAAAAFCnQL8AAADYuzC5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Everyone held my hand",
    "question": " You told us in the debate ….",
    "question_vector": "AAAAILmMkj8AAACYmXaaPwAAABCtlqa/AAAAQMxflD8AAAAAiU6oPwAAAADEl2c/AAAAcMIdtb8AAACk/GOlPwAAANC9ram/AAAAujDOu78AAACSzhjAvwAAABhLybK/AAAARoFHs78AAABM/Tm0PwAAAFBA4L4/AAAAqDn/oj8AAABqbm10PwAAABC8rKS/AAAA7LbcoD8AAADQwCCtvwAAAAzZP6w/AAAAbIX9wj8AAACgKjioPwAAAIAFv4k/AAAAUC0cvj8AAACAW5HYvwAAANTmXqE/AAAA8GBDsz8AAAAQrzu9vwAAANMrobY/AAAAQLXn3T8AAAAglsaDPwAAAPBKNsO/AAAA1Nq4wr8AAADoATXCvwAAADBtWr6/AAAAAA5Peb8AAACAyAl9vwAAAACtx38/AAAAgK2ThD8AAAAQRrSgvwAAAI5SMcA/AAAASOgqtr8AAAAAXbuOPwAAAPAKtqs/AAAAwKlVpz8AAABgA4a4vwAAAGBY28I/AAAAAFCnQL8AAADYuzC5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I said look",
    "question": " You told us in the debate ….",
    "question_vector": "AAAAILmMkj8AAACYmXaaPwAAABCtlqa/AAAAQMxflD8AAAAAiU6oPwAAAADEl2c/AAAAcMIdtb8AAACk/GOlPwAAANC9ram/AAAAujDOu78AAACSzhjAvwAAABhLybK/AAAARoFHs78AAABM/Tm0PwAAAFBA4L4/AAAAqDn/oj8AAABqbm10PwAAABC8rKS/AAAA7LbcoD8AAADQwCCtvwAAAAzZP6w/AAAAbIX9wj8AAACgKjioPwAAAIAFv4k/AAAAUC0cvj8AAACAW5HYvwAAANTmXqE/AAAA8GBDsz8AAAAQrzu9vwAAANMrobY/AAAAQLXn3T8AAAAglsaDPwAAAPBKNsO/AAAA1Nq4wr8AAADoATXCvwAAADBtWr6/AAAAAA5Peb8AAACAyAl9vwAAAACtx38/AAAAgK2ThD8AAAAQRrSgvwAAAI5SMcA/AAAASOgqtr8AAAAAXbuOPwAAAPAKtqs/AAAAwKlVpz8AAABgA4a4vwAAAGBY28I/AAAAAFCnQL8AAADYuzC5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Take a look at that hand",
    "question": " You told us in the debate ….",
    "question_vector": "AAAAILmMkj8AAACYmXaaPwAAABCtlqa/AAAAQMxflD8AAAAAiU6oPwAAAADEl2c/AAAAcMIdtb8AAACk/GOlPwAAANC9ram/AAAAujDOu78AAACSzhjAvwAAABhLybK/AAAARoFHs78AAABM/Tm0PwAAAFBA4L4/AAAAqDn/oj8AAABqbm10PwAAABC8rKS/AAAA7LbcoD8AAADQwCCtvwAAAAzZP6w/AAAAbIX9wj8AAACgKjioPwAAAIAFv4k/AAAAUC0cvj8AAACAW5HYvwAAANTmXqE/AAAA8GBDsz8AAAAQrzu9vwAAANMrobY/AAAAQLXn3T8AAAAglsaDPwAAAPBKNsO/AAAA1Nq4wr8AAADoATXCvwAAADBtWr6/AAAAAA5Peb8AAACAyAl9vwAAAACtx38/AAAAgK2ThD8AAAAQRrSgvwAAAI5SMcA/AAAASOgqtr8AAAAAXbuOPwAAAPAKtqs/AAAAwKlVpz8AAABgA4a4vwAAAGBY28I/AAAAAFCnQL8AAADYuzC5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "told",
      "debate"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I don’t want people to go around thinking that I have a problem",
    "question": " You chose to raise it during a debate. Can you explain why you had no choice?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqSp3fmb8AAABAkB6uPwAAALo+G6m/q6qqykMUr7+rqqqqi/qyP6uqqp7I27U/VVVVxZ9Zwr+rqqou7NqiP1VVVTXga76/VVVVVQZiVD8AAAAY1R62vwAAAACAP1e/q6qqus8PmT9VVVWVR8+vPwAAACC4PbE/q6qq2kN+qj9VVVWVvwisP6uqqio+k7a/AAAAQJq/oz8AAABwoNnBvwAAAACzXGw/q6qqqiLeUD+rqqqqTBJ5v6uqqvJVDLM/q6qq8nxBsD8AAAAgHNnXv1VVVVURk6G/VVVVVQUHrL+rqqqq00ucv1VVVdXzLYU/AAAAsFzQ4D9VVVWFkKa2P6uqqgpbP8y/q6qqetvZx7+rqqqqQCZyP6uqqqrUjry/q6qqKtIYgT9VVVVVROC8P1VVVdWnxsC/q6qqWjBGwr+rqqpqHcqev1VVVU0qrpw/VVVVlYDGtr+rqqoCrg20P6uqqppj5KS/AAAAgK+rvz+rqqqKPFqwv1VVVRWka7A/AAAAAMbXcb8AAADoeizBPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "chose",
      "debate.",
      "choice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’m telling you, Ruth, I had so many people",
    "question": " You chose to raise it during a debate. Can you explain why you had no choice?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqSp3fmb8AAABAkB6uPwAAALo+G6m/q6qqykMUr7+rqqqqi/qyP6uqqp7I27U/VVVVxZ9Zwr+rqqou7NqiP1VVVTXga76/VVVVVQZiVD8AAAAY1R62vwAAAACAP1e/q6qqus8PmT9VVVWVR8+vPwAAACC4PbE/q6qq2kN+qj9VVVWVvwisP6uqqio+k7a/AAAAQJq/oz8AAABwoNnBvwAAAACzXGw/q6qqqiLeUD+rqqqqTBJ5v6uqqvJVDLM/q6qq8nxBsD8AAAAgHNnXv1VVVVURk6G/VVVVVQUHrL+rqqqq00ucv1VVVdXzLYU/AAAAsFzQ4D9VVVWFkKa2P6uqqgpbP8y/q6qqetvZx7+rqqqqQCZyP6uqqqrUjry/q6qqKtIYgT9VVVVVROC8P1VVVdWnxsC/q6qqWjBGwr+rqqpqHcqev1VVVU0qrpw/VVVVlYDGtr+rqqoCrg20P6uqqppj5KS/AAAAgK+rvz+rqqqKPFqwv1VVVRWka7A/AAAAAMbXcb8AAADoeizBPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "chose",
      "debate.",
      "choice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I would say 25, 30 people would tell me … every time I’d shake people’s hand, “Oh, you have nice hands",
    "question": " You chose to raise it during a debate. Can you explain why you had no choice?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqSp3fmb8AAABAkB6uPwAAALo+G6m/q6qqykMUr7+rqqqqi/qyP6uqqp7I27U/VVVVxZ9Zwr+rqqou7NqiP1VVVTXga76/VVVVVQZiVD8AAAAY1R62vwAAAACAP1e/q6qqus8PmT9VVVWVR8+vPwAAACC4PbE/q6qq2kN+qj9VVVWVvwisP6uqqio+k7a/AAAAQJq/oz8AAABwoNnBvwAAAACzXGw/q6qqqiLeUD+rqqqqTBJ5v6uqqvJVDLM/q6qq8nxBsD8AAAAgHNnXv1VVVVURk6G/VVVVVQUHrL+rqqqq00ucv1VVVdXzLYU/AAAAsFzQ4D9VVVWFkKa2P6uqqgpbP8y/q6qqetvZx7+rqqqqQCZyP6uqqqrUjry/q6qqKtIYgT9VVVVVROC8P1VVVdWnxsC/q6qqWjBGwr+rqqpqHcqev1VVVU0qrpw/VVVVlYDGtr+rqqoCrg20P6uqqppj5KS/AAAAgK+rvz+rqqqKPFqwv1VVVRWka7A/AAAAAMbXcb8AAADoeizBPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "chose",
      "debate.",
      "choice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” Why shouldn’t I? And, by the way, by saying that I solved the problem",
    "question": " You chose to raise it during a debate. Can you explain why you had no choice?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqSp3fmb8AAABAkB6uPwAAALo+G6m/q6qqykMUr7+rqqqqi/qyP6uqqp7I27U/VVVVxZ9Zwr+rqqou7NqiP1VVVTXga76/VVVVVQZiVD8AAAAY1R62vwAAAACAP1e/q6qqus8PmT9VVVWVR8+vPwAAACC4PbE/q6qq2kN+qj9VVVWVvwisP6uqqio+k7a/AAAAQJq/oz8AAABwoNnBvwAAAACzXGw/q6qqqiLeUD+rqqqqTBJ5v6uqqvJVDLM/q6qq8nxBsD8AAAAgHNnXv1VVVVURk6G/VVVVVQUHrL+rqqqq00ucv1VVVdXzLYU/AAAAsFzQ4D9VVVWFkKa2P6uqqgpbP8y/q6qqetvZx7+rqqqqQCZyP6uqqqrUjry/q6qqKtIYgT9VVVVVROC8P1VVVdWnxsC/q6qqWjBGwr+rqqpqHcqev1VVVU0qrpw/VVVVlYDGtr+rqqoCrg20P6uqqppj5KS/AAAAgK+rvz+rqqqKPFqwv1VVVRWka7A/AAAAAMbXcb8AAADoeizBPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "chose",
      "debate.",
      "choice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Nobody questions … I even held up my hands, and said, “Look, take a look at that hand",
    "question": " You chose to raise it during a debate. Can you explain why you had no choice?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqSp3fmb8AAABAkB6uPwAAALo+G6m/q6qqykMUr7+rqqqqi/qyP6uqqp7I27U/VVVVxZ9Zwr+rqqou7NqiP1VVVTXga76/VVVVVQZiVD8AAAAY1R62vwAAAACAP1e/q6qqus8PmT9VVVWVR8+vPwAAACC4PbE/q6qq2kN+qj9VVVWVvwisP6uqqio+k7a/AAAAQJq/oz8AAABwoNnBvwAAAACzXGw/q6qqqiLeUD+rqqqqTBJ5v6uqqvJVDLM/q6qq8nxBsD8AAAAgHNnXv1VVVVURk6G/VVVVVQUHrL+rqqqq00ucv1VVVdXzLYU/AAAAsFzQ4D9VVVWFkKa2P6uqqgpbP8y/q6qqetvZx7+rqqqqQCZyP6uqqqrUjry/q6qqKtIYgT9VVVVVROC8P1VVVdWnxsC/q6qqWjBGwr+rqqpqHcqev1VVVU0qrpw/VVVVlYDGtr+rqqoCrg20P6uqqppj5KS/AAAAgK+rvz+rqqqKPFqwv1VVVRWka7A/AAAAAMbXcb8AAADoeizBPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "chose",
      "debate.",
      "choice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "”",
    "question": " You chose to raise it during a debate. Can you explain why you had no choice?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqSp3fmb8AAABAkB6uPwAAALo+G6m/q6qqykMUr7+rqqqqi/qyP6uqqp7I27U/VVVVxZ9Zwr+rqqou7NqiP1VVVTXga76/VVVVVQZiVD8AAAAY1R62vwAAAACAP1e/q6qqus8PmT9VVVWVR8+vPwAAACC4PbE/q6qq2kN+qj9VVVWVvwisP6uqqio+k7a/AAAAQJq/oz8AAABwoNnBvwAAAACzXGw/q6qqqiLeUD+rqqqqTBJ5v6uqqvJVDLM/q6qq8nxBsD8AAAAgHNnXv1VVVVURk6G/VVVVVQUHrL+rqqqq00ucv1VVVdXzLYU/AAAAsFzQ4D9VVVWFkKa2P6uqqgpbP8y/q6qqetvZx7+rqqqqQCZyP6uqqqrUjry/q6qqKtIYgT9VVVVVROC8P1VVVdWnxsC/q6qqWjBGwr+rqqpqHcqev1VVVU0qrpw/VVVVlYDGtr+rqqoCrg20P6uqqppj5KS/AAAAgK+rvz+rqqqKPFqwv1VVVRWka7A/AAAAAMbXcb8AAADoeizBPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "chose",
      "debate.",
      "choice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I had no choice",
    "question": " You chose to respond.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwP7vjL8AAAAAqH6hPwAAAODv4m+/AAAAIAIQtr8AAABAUa/CPwAAAMBBDHo/AAAAYMnc0b8AAADgNgjAPwAAAMD/0s6/AAAAADrKrb8AAAAg66ekPwAAAGCJK7s/AAAAAKxYqz8AAAAACCiSvwAAAECG7LE/AAAAYKwavD8AAACArnmnPwAAAEAF7q6/AAAAoDEfjz8AAACgNRfEvwAAAOA9H5K/AAAAgJk4mj8AAADAqpSgPwAAAKCt9LA/AAAAYPMRpz8AAACgTLjYvwAAAGAEdbq/AAAAwLvPxr8AAACAuK29vwAAAOApbsi/AAAAgEA83j8AAACAMOy6PwAAAIAlC9G/AAAAgDybx78AAACgw/q8PwAAAMCClsG/AAAAIKLgrD8AAABgBFjCPwAAAMCHjsC/AAAAgHLrvr8AAACg35ikvwAAACC0GXQ/AAAAQGM2rL8AAABgNh6SvwAAAEB+2LK/AAAAIPwVtT8AAABgLUfFvwAAACD4xLC/AAAAgMZxrL8AAABArn7DPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "chose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No, I chose to respond",
    "question": " You chose to raise it …",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwP7vjL8AAAAAqH6hPwAAAODv4m+/AAAAIAIQtr8AAABAUa/CPwAAAMBBDHo/AAAAYMnc0b8AAADgNgjAPwAAAMD/0s6/AAAAADrKrb8AAAAg66ekPwAAAGCJK7s/AAAAAKxYqz8AAAAACCiSvwAAAECG7LE/AAAAYKwavD8AAACArnmnPwAAAEAF7q6/AAAAoDEfjz8AAACgNRfEvwAAAOA9H5K/AAAAgJk4mj8AAADAqpSgPwAAAKCt9LA/AAAAYPMRpz8AAACgTLjYvwAAAGAEdbq/AAAAwLvPxr8AAACAuK29vwAAAOApbsi/AAAAgEA83j8AAACAMOy6PwAAAIAlC9G/AAAAgDybx78AAACgw/q8PwAAAMCClsG/AAAAIKLgrD8AAABgBFjCPwAAAMCHjsC/AAAAgHLrvr8AAACg35ikvwAAACC0GXQ/AAAAQGM2rL8AAABgNh6SvwAAAEB+2LK/AAAAIPwVtT8AAABgLUfFvwAAACD4xLC/AAAAgMZxrL8AAABArn7DPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "chose"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " A hand with little fingers coming out of a stem",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Like, little",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Look at my hands",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They’re fine",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Nobody other than Graydon Carter years ago used to use that",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " My hands are normal hands",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " During a debate, he was losing, and he said, “Oh, he has small hands and therefore, you know what that means",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” This was not me",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " This was Rubio that said, “He has small hands and you know what that means",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” Okay? So, he started it",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " So, what I said a couple of days later … and what happened is I was on line shaking hands with supporters, and one of supporters got up and he said, “Mr",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Trump, you have strong hands",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You have good-sized hands",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” And then another one would say, “You have great hands, Mr",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Trump, I had no idea",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” I said, “What do you mean?” He said, “I thought you were like deformed, and I thought you had small hands",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” I had fifty people … Is that a correct statement? I mean people were writing, “How are Mr",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Trump’s hands?” My hands are fine",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You know, my hands are normal",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Slightly large, actually",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " In fact, I buy a slightly smaller than large glove, okay? No, but I did this because everybody was saying to me, “Oh, your hands are very nice",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They are normal",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” So Rubio, in a debate, said, because he had nothing else to say … now I was hitting him pretty hard",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " He wanted to do his Don Rickles stuff and it didn’t work out",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Obviously, it didn’t work too well",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But one of the things he said was “He has small hands and therefore, you know what that means, he has small something else",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” You can look it up",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I didn’t say it",
    "question": " You’re on the cover.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAIK9sr8AAAAgoxnUvwAAAACycbK/AAAAQPS80L8AAABgcNK5PwAAAIC89MG/AAAAoHJsmD8AAADA9RLHPwAAAADGo58/AAAAgNyrkT8AAAAg2PGzvwAAAICO0b8/AAAAwPWOk78AAAAAlyy0PwAAAICKBsI/AAAAAHa2yT8AAACARULCPwAAAMA6zaU/AAAAgC57tT8AAACg+9q4PwAAAIDCoLW/AAAAwHDApL8AAABg9TCqPwAAACDODM8/AAAAYG4Fvj8AAAAA756nvwAAAEDWKLK/AAAAoDf3tz8AAADAl1nYPwAAAOB4D5u/AAAAoFY9078AAABA2eKpPwAAAEBWb8C/AAAAAEIRxT8AAADg0CikvwAAAODj1Lo/AAAAIGJAqj8AAAAAK8aPPwAAAODb+qS/AAAA4Lr/mb8AAABgk4qovwAAAIBH88e/AAAAQEZrxL8AAACg1urWPwAAAMDAeJU/AAAAIEw1o78AAADgLSCuPwAAACC8i7c/AAAAYH4fwT8AAACAn2e4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Youre"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No, I had to do it",
    "question": " Do you regret having engaged in that?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoAigpz8AAADgwHq5PwAAAECwC8O/AAAAoLM3kL8AAADA7jW5PwAAAOCyl6w/AAAAAF9Yxj8AAABgNiLVPwAAAMCwHMC/AAAAYM+tij8AAACg2d+SvwAAACBsxsA/AAAAQMG4sb8AAABAWA/CvwAAAEB+gMU/AAAAQFihc78AAABAeMayvwAAAACESKe/AAAAQKnjsD8AAABAHA2uvwAAAGCpdrC/AAAAgDfJxj8AAADg6smyPwAAACCyG8C/AAAAYPOp0z8AAADg4qfUvwAAAGArnMK/AAAAYK+wtj8AAACADOa+PwAAAOBUPpC/AAAAgOiC0j8AAABAP23HPwAAAIAw13U/AAAAIKKjtb8AAACAZ3jFvwAAAEBUBMO/AAAAwOYywD8AAABA6HHMvwAAAOB+972/AAAAwDs/lz8AAABA78FyPwAAAABtKLC/AAAAgGhAqb8AAADAXtOlvwAAAEBHKbg/AAAA4G3rrT8AAADglwbJvwAAAIABGdQ/AAAAIIQBhj8AAABAIbiUPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "regret"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Look, this guy",
    "question": " Do you regret having engaged in that?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoAigpz8AAADgwHq5PwAAAECwC8O/AAAAoLM3kL8AAADA7jW5PwAAAOCyl6w/AAAAAF9Yxj8AAABgNiLVPwAAAMCwHMC/AAAAYM+tij8AAACg2d+SvwAAACBsxsA/AAAAQMG4sb8AAABAWA/CvwAAAEB+gMU/AAAAQFihc78AAABAeMayvwAAAACESKe/AAAAQKnjsD8AAABAHA2uvwAAAGCpdrC/AAAAgDfJxj8AAADg6smyPwAAACCyG8C/AAAAYPOp0z8AAADg4qfUvwAAAGArnMK/AAAAYK+wtj8AAACADOa+PwAAAOBUPpC/AAAAgOiC0j8AAABAP23HPwAAAIAw13U/AAAAIKKjtb8AAACAZ3jFvwAAAEBUBMO/AAAAwOYywD8AAABA6HHMvwAAAOB+972/AAAAwDs/lz8AAABA78FyPwAAAABtKLC/AAAAgGhAqb8AAADAXtOlvwAAAEBHKbg/AAAA4G3rrT8AAADglwbJvwAAAIABGdQ/AAAAIIQBhj8AAABAIbiUPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "regret"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Here’s my hands",
    "question": " Do you regret having engaged in that?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoAigpz8AAADgwHq5PwAAAECwC8O/AAAAoLM3kL8AAADA7jW5PwAAAOCyl6w/AAAAAF9Yxj8AAABgNiLVPwAAAMCwHMC/AAAAYM+tij8AAACg2d+SvwAAACBsxsA/AAAAQMG4sb8AAABAWA/CvwAAAEB+gMU/AAAAQFihc78AAABAeMayvwAAAACESKe/AAAAQKnjsD8AAABAHA2uvwAAAGCpdrC/AAAAgDfJxj8AAADg6smyPwAAACCyG8C/AAAAYPOp0z8AAADg4qfUvwAAAGArnMK/AAAAYK+wtj8AAACADOa+PwAAAOBUPpC/AAAAgOiC0j8AAABAP23HPwAAAIAw13U/AAAAIKKjtb8AAACAZ3jFvwAAAEBUBMO/AAAAwOYywD8AAABA6HHMvwAAAOB+972/AAAAwDs/lz8AAABA78FyPwAAAABtKLC/AAAAgGhAqb8AAADAXtOlvwAAAEBHKbg/AAAA4G3rrT8AAADglwbJvwAAAIABGdQ/AAAAIIQBhj8AAABAIbiUPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "regret"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Now I have my hands, I hear, on the New Yorker, a picture of my hands",
    "question": " Do you regret having engaged in that?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoAigpz8AAADgwHq5PwAAAECwC8O/AAAAoLM3kL8AAADA7jW5PwAAAOCyl6w/AAAAAF9Yxj8AAABgNiLVPwAAAMCwHMC/AAAAYM+tij8AAACg2d+SvwAAACBsxsA/AAAAQMG4sb8AAABAWA/CvwAAAEB+gMU/AAAAQFihc78AAABAeMayvwAAAACESKe/AAAAQKnjsD8AAABAHA2uvwAAAGCpdrC/AAAAgDfJxj8AAADg6smyPwAAACCyG8C/AAAAYPOp0z8AAADg4qfUvwAAAGArnMK/AAAAYK+wtj8AAACADOa+PwAAAOBUPpC/AAAAgOiC0j8AAABAP23HPwAAAIAw13U/AAAAIKKjtb8AAACAZ3jFvwAAAEBUBMO/AAAAwOYywD8AAABA6HHMvwAAAOB+972/AAAAwDs/lz8AAABA78FyPwAAAABtKLC/AAAAgGhAqb8AAADAXtOlvwAAAEBHKbg/AAAA4G3rrT8AAADglwbJvwAAAIABGdQ/AAAAIIQBhj8AAABAIbiUPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "regret"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No …",
    "question": " Just back to the campaign. You are smart and you went to a good school. Yet you are up there and talking about your hands and the size of private …",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgGuzp78AAAAAIHFPv6uqqqqUTIu/VVVVvbukwr8AAABA4oCnP1VVVRU0l4g/VVVVlWHqvL+rqqqKT1Spv1VVVTVRRJ+/q6qqKkKztr9VVVX9gw3Bv6uqqgrLb6m/AACAIe7Hs78AAADQa/KzvwAAAOA/RZC/q6qqAi9Wsr8AAADgNbyov6uqqiqITaI/q6qqCioblL9VVVVVdhOAv6uqqqpodqQ/VVVV9evUtj+rqqpqHS+bPwAAAICrYKi/q6qqZmKvpb9VVVX1aCrXv1VVVZ1jFoa/VVVVdaHfkr+rqqpKq4ybv1VVVXUObbO/q6qqqjF34T9VVVUlNvm3P1VVVZ067rm/AAAAIISgtr9VVVVVNE+dvwAAAOiFJbA/AAAAwMp6p7+rqqrqKwyhP1VVVVXDNos/AAAAoInKtL+rqqoIch2xv1VVVVWJZG2/VVVVhZUVsr8AAACAASqfP6uqquaEnps/AAAAANGqnL9VVVVV+ySiv6uqqq7U/rW/AAAAcBOOn78AAAAAYr6Nvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "campaign.",
      "school.",
      "hands"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No, not while I am president",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No, not while I’m president",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " That is two phases",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Right now, look, you know, I went to a great school, I was a good student and all",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I am an intelligent person",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " My uncle, I would say my uncle was one of the brilliant people",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " He was at MIT for 35 years",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " As a great scientist and engineer, actually more than anything else",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Dr",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " John Trump, a great guy",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’m an intelligent person",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I understand what is going on",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Right now, I had 17 people who started out",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They are almost all gone",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " If I were going to do that in a different fashion I think I probably wouldn’t be sitting here",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You would be interviewing somebody else",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But it is hard to act presidential when you are being … I mean, actually I think it is presidential because it is winning",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And winning is a pretty good thing for this country because we don’t win any more",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I say it all the time",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We do not win any more",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " This country doesn’t win",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We don’t win with trade",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We don’t win with … We can’t even beat ISIS",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And by the way, just to answer the rest of that question, I would knock the hell out of ISIS in some form",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I would rather not do it with our troops, you understand that",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Very important",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Because I think saying that is very important because I was against the war in Iraq, although they found a clip talking to Howard Stern, I said, “Well…” It was very unenthusiastic",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Before they want in, I was totally against the war",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I was against it for years",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I actually had a delegation sent from the White House to talk to me because I guess I get a disproportionate amount of publicity",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I was just against the war",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I thought it would destabilize the Middle East, and it did",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But we have to knock out ISIS",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We are living like in medieval times",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Who ever heard of the heads chopped off?",
    "question": " Would you do that while you are president?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well, it means that I’ll start spending on them",
    "question": " So, what does it mean, “They better watch out”?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA4CXnjT8AAADgiedNvwAAAEComaw/AAAAYBM9qT8AAACgKxG+PwAAAEDB6tC/AAAAgHeLvL8AAABgC+12vwAAAGC8asA/AAAAwMD9uL8AAADAtaWgvwAAAOBgrZk/AAAAAFKYob8AAAAgkeXCPwAAAIAwg88/AAAA4P0FtT8AAADAPAR3PwAAAAAABoq/AAAA4OOdwb8AAABgA8fJvwAAAIBEVLE/AAAAAM8gwj8AAACANhWsPwAAAGB8krw/AAAAAOa4tz8AAABgY9HVvwAAACDg4MW/AAAAoEoCpD8AAABgQmOyPwAAAABN88i/AAAAIOnJ4T8AAABAdELIPwAAAIBOYpm/AAAA4J1Kwr8AAABAuGzCvwAAAGBaU6k/AAAAQMfsrz8AAADA15W8vwAAAICis7m/AAAAoD9btL8AAADg8peMvwAAAEAGs70/AAAAYBC8oj8AAAAAsUGqPwAAAEBK67g/AAAAAEzedT8AAAAgHYxBvwAAAKD1ZsG/AAAAoHoVs78AAADAfKm3Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’ll start taking ads telling them all what a rotten job they’re doing with the Chicago Cubs",
    "question": " So, what does it mean, “They better watch out”?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA4CXnjT8AAADgiedNvwAAAEComaw/AAAAYBM9qT8AAACgKxG+PwAAAEDB6tC/AAAAgHeLvL8AAABgC+12vwAAAGC8asA/AAAAwMD9uL8AAADAtaWgvwAAAOBgrZk/AAAAAFKYob8AAAAgkeXCPwAAAIAwg88/AAAA4P0FtT8AAADAPAR3PwAAAAAABoq/AAAA4OOdwb8AAABgA8fJvwAAAIBEVLE/AAAAAM8gwj8AAACANhWsPwAAAGB8krw/AAAAAOa4tz8AAABgY9HVvwAAACDg4MW/AAAAoEoCpD8AAABgQmOyPwAAAABN88i/AAAAIOnJ4T8AAABAdELIPwAAAIBOYpm/AAAA4J1Kwr8AAABAuGzCvwAAAGBaU6k/AAAAQMfsrz8AAADA15W8vwAAAICis7m/AAAAoD9btL8AAADg8peMvwAAAEAGs70/AAAAYBC8oj8AAAAAsUGqPwAAAEBK67g/AAAAAEzedT8AAAAgHYxBvwAAAKD1ZsG/AAAAoHoVs78AAADAfKm3Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean, they are spending on me",
    "question": " So, what does it mean, “They better watch out”?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA4CXnjT8AAADgiedNvwAAAEComaw/AAAAYBM9qT8AAACgKxG+PwAAAEDB6tC/AAAAgHeLvL8AAABgC+12vwAAAGC8asA/AAAAwMD9uL8AAADAtaWgvwAAAOBgrZk/AAAAAFKYob8AAAAgkeXCPwAAAIAwg88/AAAA4P0FtT8AAADAPAR3PwAAAAAABoq/AAAA4OOdwb8AAABgA8fJvwAAAIBEVLE/AAAAAM8gwj8AAACANhWsPwAAAGB8krw/AAAAAOa4tz8AAABgY9HVvwAAACDg4MW/AAAAoEoCpD8AAABgQmOyPwAAAABN88i/AAAAIOnJ4T8AAABAdELIPwAAAIBOYpm/AAAA4J1Kwr8AAABAuGzCvwAAAGBaU6k/AAAAQMfsrz8AAADA15W8vwAAAICis7m/AAAAoD9btL8AAADg8peMvwAAAEAGs70/AAAAYBC8oj8AAAAAsUGqPwAAAEBK67g/AAAAAEzedT8AAAAgHYxBvwAAAKD1ZsG/AAAAoHoVs78AAADAfKm3Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean, so am I allowed to say that? I’ll start doing ads about their baseball team",
    "question": " So, what does it mean, “They better watch out”?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA4CXnjT8AAADgiedNvwAAAEComaw/AAAAYBM9qT8AAACgKxG+PwAAAEDB6tC/AAAAgHeLvL8AAABgC+12vwAAAGC8asA/AAAAwMD9uL8AAADAtaWgvwAAAOBgrZk/AAAAAFKYob8AAAAgkeXCPwAAAIAwg88/AAAA4P0FtT8AAADAPAR3PwAAAAAABoq/AAAA4OOdwb8AAABgA8fJvwAAAIBEVLE/AAAAAM8gwj8AAACANhWsPwAAAGB8krw/AAAAAOa4tz8AAABgY9HVvwAAACDg4MW/AAAAoEoCpD8AAABgQmOyPwAAAABN88i/AAAAIOnJ4T8AAABAdELIPwAAAIBOYpm/AAAA4J1Kwr8AAABAuGzCvwAAAGBaU6k/AAAAQMfsrz8AAADA15W8vwAAAICis7m/AAAAoD9btL8AAADg8peMvwAAAEAGs70/AAAAYBC8oj8AAAAAsUGqPwAAAEBK67g/AAAAAEzedT8AAAAgHYxBvwAAAKD1ZsG/AAAAoHoVs78AAADAfKm3Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " That it’s not properly run or that they haven’t done a good job in the brokerage business lately",
    "question": " So, what does it mean, “They better watch out”?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA4CXnjT8AAADgiedNvwAAAEComaw/AAAAYBM9qT8AAACgKxG+PwAAAEDB6tC/AAAAgHeLvL8AAABgC+12vwAAAGC8asA/AAAAwMD9uL8AAADAtaWgvwAAAOBgrZk/AAAAAFKYob8AAAAgkeXCPwAAAIAwg88/AAAA4P0FtT8AAADAPAR3PwAAAAAABoq/AAAA4OOdwb8AAABgA8fJvwAAAIBEVLE/AAAAAM8gwj8AAACANhWsPwAAAGB8krw/AAAAAOa4tz8AAABgY9HVvwAAACDg4MW/AAAAoEoCpD8AAABgQmOyPwAAAABN88i/AAAAIOnJ4T8AAABAdELIPwAAAIBOYpm/AAAA4J1Kwr8AAABAuGzCvwAAAGBaU6k/AAAAQMfsrz8AAADA15W8vwAAAICis7m/AAAAoD9btL8AAADg8peMvwAAAEAGs70/AAAAYBC8oj8AAAAAsUGqPwAAAEBK67g/AAAAAEzedT8AAAAgHYxBvwAAAKD1ZsG/AAAAoHoVs78AAADAfKm3Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Look, they are spending vicious … I don’t even know these people",
    "question": " I’d like to come back to the campaign. You said a few weeks ago after a family in Chicago gave some money to a PAC opposing you, you said, “They better watch out. They have a lot to hide.” What should they watch out for?",
    "question_vector": "AAAArHKhmT8AABCzlmiwPwAAAADldJ6/AAAACO4qpD8AAABwTIm4PwAAACDDYJW/AAAAMCg9zL8AAADbjSmdvwAAAKAsP4i/AAAABMO4sL8AAABcQma5vwAAAPCqLYy/AAAAUI3coL8AAACAoctyvwAAgLcXKb4/AAAAMEnQqb8AAAAixmWvvwAAAJBDUIG/AAAAHuEUur8AAACAzFx9vwAAIEKAgq0/AAAA3BY+oz8AAADA2St5vwAAACTfTqA/AAAARAjro78AAADwo1HVvwAAAOiRhq+/AAAAHEEnpL8AAAAqDdGwPwAAANAHEKy/AAAA2LXY3j8AAADYrxmzPwAAAGg8SKS/AAAAmH6EwL8AAACMymKyvwAAAML4F5W/AAAAbP2dq78AAADw+WGJvwAAAAAaSWM/AAAAlPA/qb8AAADeJ+2rvwAAAMjE26I/AAAAXbUXqb8AAADIusWdPwAAADj9U60/AAAAaPCqkj8AAJAWSnK7vwAAADsDYLy/AAAAoMs0nb8AAAANvKO6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch",
      "campaign.",
      "Chicago",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Those Ricketts",
    "question": " I’d like to come back to the campaign. You said a few weeks ago after a family in Chicago gave some money to a PAC opposing you, you said, “They better watch out. They have a lot to hide.” What should they watch out for?",
    "question_vector": "AAAArHKhmT8AABCzlmiwPwAAAADldJ6/AAAACO4qpD8AAABwTIm4PwAAACDDYJW/AAAAMCg9zL8AAADbjSmdvwAAAKAsP4i/AAAABMO4sL8AAABcQma5vwAAAPCqLYy/AAAAUI3coL8AAACAoctyvwAAgLcXKb4/AAAAMEnQqb8AAAAixmWvvwAAAJBDUIG/AAAAHuEUur8AAACAzFx9vwAAIEKAgq0/AAAA3BY+oz8AAADA2St5vwAAACTfTqA/AAAARAjro78AAADwo1HVvwAAAOiRhq+/AAAAHEEnpL8AAAAqDdGwPwAAANAHEKy/AAAA2LXY3j8AAADYrxmzPwAAAGg8SKS/AAAAmH6EwL8AAACMymKyvwAAAML4F5W/AAAAbP2dq78AAADw+WGJvwAAAAAaSWM/AAAAlPA/qb8AAADeJ+2rvwAAAMjE26I/AAAAXbUXqb8AAADIusWdPwAAADj9U60/AAAAaPCqkj8AAJAWSnK7vwAAADsDYLy/AAAAoMs0nb8AAAANvKO6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch",
      "campaign.",
      "Chicago",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I actually said they ought to focus on the Chicago Cubs and, you know, stop playing around",
    "question": " I’d like to come back to the campaign. You said a few weeks ago after a family in Chicago gave some money to a PAC opposing you, you said, “They better watch out. They have a lot to hide.” What should they watch out for?",
    "question_vector": "AAAArHKhmT8AABCzlmiwPwAAAADldJ6/AAAACO4qpD8AAABwTIm4PwAAACDDYJW/AAAAMCg9zL8AAADbjSmdvwAAAKAsP4i/AAAABMO4sL8AAABcQma5vwAAAPCqLYy/AAAAUI3coL8AAACAoctyvwAAgLcXKb4/AAAAMEnQqb8AAAAixmWvvwAAAJBDUIG/AAAAHuEUur8AAACAzFx9vwAAIEKAgq0/AAAA3BY+oz8AAADA2St5vwAAACTfTqA/AAAARAjro78AAADwo1HVvwAAAOiRhq+/AAAAHEEnpL8AAAAqDdGwPwAAANAHEKy/AAAA2LXY3j8AAADYrxmzPwAAAGg8SKS/AAAAmH6EwL8AAACMymKyvwAAAML4F5W/AAAAbP2dq78AAADw+WGJvwAAAAAaSWM/AAAAlPA/qb8AAADeJ+2rvwAAAMjE26I/AAAAXbUXqb8AAADIusWdPwAAADj9U60/AAAAaPCqkj8AAJAWSnK7vwAAADsDYLy/AAAAoMs0nb8AAAANvKO6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch",
      "campaign.",
      "Chicago",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They spent millions of dollars fighting me in Florida",
    "question": " I’d like to come back to the campaign. You said a few weeks ago after a family in Chicago gave some money to a PAC opposing you, you said, “They better watch out. They have a lot to hide.” What should they watch out for?",
    "question_vector": "AAAArHKhmT8AABCzlmiwPwAAAADldJ6/AAAACO4qpD8AAABwTIm4PwAAACDDYJW/AAAAMCg9zL8AAADbjSmdvwAAAKAsP4i/AAAABMO4sL8AAABcQma5vwAAAPCqLYy/AAAAUI3coL8AAACAoctyvwAAgLcXKb4/AAAAMEnQqb8AAAAixmWvvwAAAJBDUIG/AAAAHuEUur8AAACAzFx9vwAAIEKAgq0/AAAA3BY+oz8AAADA2St5vwAAACTfTqA/AAAARAjro78AAADwo1HVvwAAAOiRhq+/AAAAHEEnpL8AAAAqDdGwPwAAANAHEKy/AAAA2LXY3j8AAADYrxmzPwAAAGg8SKS/AAAAmH6EwL8AAACMymKyvwAAAML4F5W/AAAAbP2dq78AAADw+WGJvwAAAAAaSWM/AAAAlPA/qb8AAADeJ+2rvwAAAMjE26I/AAAAXbUXqb8AAADIusWdPwAAADj9U60/AAAAaPCqkj8AAJAWSnK7vwAAADsDYLy/AAAAoMs0nb8AAAANvKO6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch",
      "campaign.",
      "Chicago",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And out of 68 counties, I won 66",
    "question": " I’d like to come back to the campaign. You said a few weeks ago after a family in Chicago gave some money to a PAC opposing you, you said, “They better watch out. They have a lot to hide.” What should they watch out for?",
    "question_vector": "AAAArHKhmT8AABCzlmiwPwAAAADldJ6/AAAACO4qpD8AAABwTIm4PwAAACDDYJW/AAAAMCg9zL8AAADbjSmdvwAAAKAsP4i/AAAABMO4sL8AAABcQma5vwAAAPCqLYy/AAAAUI3coL8AAACAoctyvwAAgLcXKb4/AAAAMEnQqb8AAAAixmWvvwAAAJBDUIG/AAAAHuEUur8AAACAzFx9vwAAIEKAgq0/AAAA3BY+oz8AAADA2St5vwAAACTfTqA/AAAARAjro78AAADwo1HVvwAAAOiRhq+/AAAAHEEnpL8AAAAqDdGwPwAAANAHEKy/AAAA2LXY3j8AAADYrxmzPwAAAGg8SKS/AAAAmH6EwL8AAACMymKyvwAAAML4F5W/AAAAbP2dq78AAADw+WGJvwAAAAAaSWM/AAAAlPA/qb8AAADeJ+2rvwAAAMjE26I/AAAAXbUXqb8AAADIusWdPwAAADj9U60/AAAAaPCqkj8AAJAWSnK7vwAAADsDYLy/AAAAoMs0nb8AAAANvKO6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch",
      "campaign.",
      "Chicago",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I won by 20 points, almost 20 points",
    "question": " I’d like to come back to the campaign. You said a few weeks ago after a family in Chicago gave some money to a PAC opposing you, you said, “They better watch out. They have a lot to hide.” What should they watch out for?",
    "question_vector": "AAAArHKhmT8AABCzlmiwPwAAAADldJ6/AAAACO4qpD8AAABwTIm4PwAAACDDYJW/AAAAMCg9zL8AAADbjSmdvwAAAKAsP4i/AAAABMO4sL8AAABcQma5vwAAAPCqLYy/AAAAUI3coL8AAACAoctyvwAAgLcXKb4/AAAAMEnQqb8AAAAixmWvvwAAAJBDUIG/AAAAHuEUur8AAACAzFx9vwAAIEKAgq0/AAAA3BY+oz8AAADA2St5vwAAACTfTqA/AAAARAjro78AAADwo1HVvwAAAOiRhq+/AAAAHEEnpL8AAAAqDdGwPwAAANAHEKy/AAAA2LXY3j8AAADYrxmzPwAAAGg8SKS/AAAAmH6EwL8AAACMymKyvwAAAML4F5W/AAAAbP2dq78AAADw+WGJvwAAAAAaSWM/AAAAlPA/qb8AAADeJ+2rvwAAAMjE26I/AAAAXbUXqb8AAADIusWdPwAAADj9U60/AAAAaPCqkj8AAJAWSnK7vwAAADsDYLy/AAAAoMs0nb8AAAANvKO6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch",
      "campaign.",
      "Chicago",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Against, everybody thought he was a popular sitting senator",
    "question": " I’d like to come back to the campaign. You said a few weeks ago after a family in Chicago gave some money to a PAC opposing you, you said, “They better watch out. They have a lot to hide.” What should they watch out for?",
    "question_vector": "AAAArHKhmT8AABCzlmiwPwAAAADldJ6/AAAACO4qpD8AAABwTIm4PwAAACDDYJW/AAAAMCg9zL8AAADbjSmdvwAAAKAsP4i/AAAABMO4sL8AAABcQma5vwAAAPCqLYy/AAAAUI3coL8AAACAoctyvwAAgLcXKb4/AAAAMEnQqb8AAAAixmWvvwAAAJBDUIG/AAAAHuEUur8AAACAzFx9vwAAIEKAgq0/AAAA3BY+oz8AAADA2St5vwAAACTfTqA/AAAARAjro78AAADwo1HVvwAAAOiRhq+/AAAAHEEnpL8AAAAqDdGwPwAAANAHEKy/AAAA2LXY3j8AAADYrxmzPwAAAGg8SKS/AAAAmH6EwL8AAACMymKyvwAAAML4F5W/AAAAbP2dq78AAADw+WGJvwAAAAAaSWM/AAAAlPA/qb8AAADeJ+2rvwAAAMjE26I/AAAAXbUXqb8AAADIusWdPwAAADj9U60/AAAAaPCqkj8AAJAWSnK7vwAAADsDYLy/AAAAoMs0nb8AAAANvKO6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch",
      "campaign.",
      "Chicago",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I had $38 million dollars spent on me in Florida over a short period of time",
    "question": " I’d like to come back to the campaign. You said a few weeks ago after a family in Chicago gave some money to a PAC opposing you, you said, “They better watch out. They have a lot to hide.” What should they watch out for?",
    "question_vector": "AAAArHKhmT8AABCzlmiwPwAAAADldJ6/AAAACO4qpD8AAABwTIm4PwAAACDDYJW/AAAAMCg9zL8AAADbjSmdvwAAAKAsP4i/AAAABMO4sL8AAABcQma5vwAAAPCqLYy/AAAAUI3coL8AAACAoctyvwAAgLcXKb4/AAAAMEnQqb8AAAAixmWvvwAAAJBDUIG/AAAAHuEUur8AAACAzFx9vwAAIEKAgq0/AAAA3BY+oz8AAADA2St5vwAAACTfTqA/AAAARAjro78AAADwo1HVvwAAAOiRhq+/AAAAHEEnpL8AAAAqDdGwPwAAANAHEKy/AAAA2LXY3j8AAADYrxmzPwAAAGg8SKS/AAAAmH6EwL8AAACMymKyvwAAAML4F5W/AAAAbP2dq78AAADw+WGJvwAAAAAaSWM/AAAAlPA/qb8AAADeJ+2rvwAAAMjE26I/AAAAXbUXqb8AAADIusWdPwAAADj9U60/AAAAaPCqkj8AAJAWSnK7vwAAADsDYLy/AAAAoMs0nb8AAAANvKO6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch",
      "campaign.",
      "Chicago",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " $38 million",
    "question": " I’d like to come back to the campaign. You said a few weeks ago after a family in Chicago gave some money to a PAC opposing you, you said, “They better watch out. They have a lot to hide.” What should they watch out for?",
    "question_vector": "AAAArHKhmT8AABCzlmiwPwAAAADldJ6/AAAACO4qpD8AAABwTIm4PwAAACDDYJW/AAAAMCg9zL8AAADbjSmdvwAAAKAsP4i/AAAABMO4sL8AAABcQma5vwAAAPCqLYy/AAAAUI3coL8AAACAoctyvwAAgLcXKb4/AAAAMEnQqb8AAAAixmWvvwAAAJBDUIG/AAAAHuEUur8AAACAzFx9vwAAIEKAgq0/AAAA3BY+oz8AAADA2St5vwAAACTfTqA/AAAARAjro78AAADwo1HVvwAAAOiRhq+/AAAAHEEnpL8AAAAqDdGwPwAAANAHEKy/AAAA2LXY3j8AAADYrxmzPwAAAGg8SKS/AAAAmH6EwL8AAACMymKyvwAAAML4F5W/AAAAbP2dq78AAADw+WGJvwAAAAAaSWM/AAAAlPA/qb8AAADeJ+2rvwAAAMjE26I/AAAAXbUXqb8AAADIusWdPwAAADj9U60/AAAAaPCqkj8AAJAWSnK7vwAAADsDYLy/AAAAoMs0nb8AAAANvKO6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch",
      "campaign.",
      "Chicago",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And, you know, the Ricketts, I don’t even know these people",
    "question": " I’d like to come back to the campaign. You said a few weeks ago after a family in Chicago gave some money to a PAC opposing you, you said, “They better watch out. They have a lot to hide.” What should they watch out for?",
    "question_vector": "AAAArHKhmT8AABCzlmiwPwAAAADldJ6/AAAACO4qpD8AAABwTIm4PwAAACDDYJW/AAAAMCg9zL8AAADbjSmdvwAAAKAsP4i/AAAABMO4sL8AAABcQma5vwAAAPCqLYy/AAAAUI3coL8AAACAoctyvwAAgLcXKb4/AAAAMEnQqb8AAAAixmWvvwAAAJBDUIG/AAAAHuEUur8AAACAzFx9vwAAIEKAgq0/AAAA3BY+oz8AAADA2St5vwAAACTfTqA/AAAARAjro78AAADwo1HVvwAAAOiRhq+/AAAAHEEnpL8AAAAqDdGwPwAAANAHEKy/AAAA2LXY3j8AAADYrxmzPwAAAGg8SKS/AAAAmH6EwL8AAACMymKyvwAAAML4F5W/AAAAbP2dq78AAADw+WGJvwAAAAAaSWM/AAAAlPA/qb8AAADeJ+2rvwAAAMjE26I/AAAAXbUXqb8AAADIusWdPwAAADj9U60/AAAAaPCqkj8AAJAWSnK7vwAAADsDYLy/AAAAoMs0nb8AAAANvKO6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "watch",
      "campaign.",
      "Chicago",
      "family"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think that we are not in the position that we used to be",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think we were a very powerful, very wealthy country",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And we’re a poor country now",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We’re a debtor nation",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " How you going to get rid – let me ask you – how are you going get rid of $21 trillion in debt? You’re going to be at 21 trillion in a matter of minutes because of that new omnibus budget",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " So they passed that ridiculous omnibus budget",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " How you going to get rid of that debt",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We’re spending that to protect other countries",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We’re not spending it on ourselves",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Because we have, we have armor-plated vehicles that are obsolete",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " The best ones are given to the enemy",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We give them to our allies over in the Middle East",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " A bullet shot in the air and they immediately run and the enemy takes over",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I have a friend whose son is in his third, his third tour over in Iraq",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " He’s over in, I mean he’s a very special kid, he’s a great kid",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But he’s over in the Middle East, and, uh, Afghanistan, different parts of the Middle East, actually",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And he said to me, I said to him what do you think",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And he said, it’s so sad",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " He said the enemy has our equipment – the new version — and we have all the old version, and the enemy has our equipment, because they get into a fight with the so-called people like the Freedom Fighters, you know the whole Syrian deal, where we’re sending billions and billions of dollars worth, and they capture the equipment",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " In most cases the shots are fired and everybody leaves",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And these are the people we’re backing",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And we don’t know if it’s going to be another Saddam Hussein deal, in other words, let’s get rid of Assad with these people and these people end up being worse",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Okay? But he said, they have better equipment",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " It’s our equipment",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They have, I guess we send 2,300 Humvees over, all armor-plated",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " So we have wounded warriors, with no legs, with no arms, because they were driving in stuff without the armor",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And the enemy has most of the new ones we sent over that they captured",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And he said, it’s so discouraging when they see that the enemy has better equipment than we have – and it’s our equipment",
    "question": " So you don’t think the US gains from being the force that sort of that helps keep the peace in the Pacific?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA+BpXlz8AAAC/vDyUPwAAADgjDYy/AAAAXFsvoD8AAADwyNiyPwAAAEg5162/AAAA5nrrs78AAACAQX9tvwAAAFwL0pi/AAAA2GlVlr8AAABgeNaGvwAAAMCDoX6/AAAA8FCns78AAACWwyiAvwAAALCGCZC/AAAAWHY8sT8AAABAJsq1PwAAAKgSPrO/AAAAtmloor8AAABUqg6yvwAAANhSOaU/AAAAmMQWoT8AAADwNyqQvwAAAJ6jl7O/AAAADKfMpj8AAADEhu/LvwAAAIiOBqu/AAAAsCiFlL8AAAAYCRCsPwAAAOBWPqQ/AAAA2KNx4T8AAACMFbO1PwAAAHC5vqq/AAAA2Olymb8AAAAgxMmjvwAAALClnca/AAAA5lNZwL8AAADIC26mvwAAAJBX+5m/AAAA2NBmqL8AAADo0gTCvwAAgBt337G/AAAAEO6Vpj8AAAAUGQOwvwAAAED54mY/AAAAWAUkoD8AAACeujKcvwAAADCas6o/AACA8C8AkL8AAAAAeuWKPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "gains",
      "peace",
      "Pacific"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Personally I don’t think so",
    "question": " Well I guess the question is, does the United States gain anything by having bases?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAaOnDkL8AAAAAPu8ovwAAAKT/nok/AAAAPLMahL8AAAAMauvBPwAAADYBppQ/AAAAXNhJpL8AAIBtug+mPwAAAFCY/Zy/AAAAALDKSz8AAAA4rRqqvwAAAJhKKqo/AAAALhRxsr8AAAAiu6+kvwAAAN6OlMc/AAAAeXgfuz8AAABE2SyyPwAAALC+eqa/AAAA5GSnmj8AAABcKdu7vwAAAHC/baK/AAAAANRaoT8AAADsLMa0PwAAADxV8p4/AAAAvkM5wj8AAADg8f7avwAAAEza58G/AAAA4BLHkz8AAEC2p7fCPwAAABa/+L6/AAAAaDAL4T8AAADkXSWiPwAAADhodLi/AAAA2idWvr8AAIAtjoKfvwAAAIhFmb2/AAAAoNr5ir8AAADSkMalPwAAACh6RqK/AAAAnO7Qsr8AAACYiJOrvwAAAKiAhXY/AAAAnsr+sj8AAAAomNm4PwAAAFQL6KC/AAAApiJ4pT8AAABgai2RvwAAAPxXwLs/AABA35belb8AAADgdwzAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "guess",
      "question",
      "States",
      "anything"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I personally don’t think so",
    "question": " Well I guess the question is, does the United States gain anything by having bases?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAaOnDkL8AAAAAPu8ovwAAAKT/nok/AAAAPLMahL8AAAAMauvBPwAAADYBppQ/AAAAXNhJpL8AAIBtug+mPwAAAFCY/Zy/AAAAALDKSz8AAAA4rRqqvwAAAJhKKqo/AAAALhRxsr8AAAAiu6+kvwAAAN6OlMc/AAAAeXgfuz8AAABE2SyyPwAAALC+eqa/AAAA5GSnmj8AAABcKdu7vwAAAHC/baK/AAAAANRaoT8AAADsLMa0PwAAADxV8p4/AAAAvkM5wj8AAADg8f7avwAAAEza58G/AAAA4BLHkz8AAEC2p7fCPwAAABa/+L6/AAAAaDAL4T8AAADkXSWiPwAAADhodLi/AAAA2idWvr8AAIAtjoKfvwAAAIhFmb2/AAAAoNr5ir8AAADSkMalPwAAACh6RqK/AAAAnO7Qsr8AAACYiJOrvwAAAKiAhXY/AAAAnsr+sj8AAAAomNm4PwAAAFQL6KC/AAAApiJ4pT8AAABgai2RvwAAAPxXwLs/AABA35belb8AAADgdwzAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "guess",
      "question",
      "States",
      "anything"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Look",
    "question": " Well I guess the question is, does the United States gain anything by having bases?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAaOnDkL8AAAAAPu8ovwAAAKT/nok/AAAAPLMahL8AAAAMauvBPwAAADYBppQ/AAAAXNhJpL8AAIBtug+mPwAAAFCY/Zy/AAAAALDKSz8AAAA4rRqqvwAAAJhKKqo/AAAALhRxsr8AAAAiu6+kvwAAAN6OlMc/AAAAeXgfuz8AAABE2SyyPwAAALC+eqa/AAAA5GSnmj8AAABcKdu7vwAAAHC/baK/AAAAANRaoT8AAADsLMa0PwAAADxV8p4/AAAAvkM5wj8AAADg8f7avwAAAEza58G/AAAA4BLHkz8AAEC2p7fCPwAAABa/+L6/AAAAaDAL4T8AAADkXSWiPwAAADhodLi/AAAA2idWvr8AAIAtjoKfvwAAAIhFmb2/AAAAoNr5ir8AAADSkMalPwAAACh6RqK/AAAAnO7Qsr8AAACYiJOrvwAAAKiAhXY/AAAAnsr+sj8AAAAomNm4PwAAAFQL6KC/AAAApiJ4pT8AAABgai2RvwAAAPxXwLs/AABA35belb8AAADgdwzAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "guess",
      "question",
      "States",
      "anything"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I have great relationships with South Korea",
    "question": " Well I guess the question is, does the United States gain anything by having bases?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAaOnDkL8AAAAAPu8ovwAAAKT/nok/AAAAPLMahL8AAAAMauvBPwAAADYBppQ/AAAAXNhJpL8AAIBtug+mPwAAAFCY/Zy/AAAAALDKSz8AAAA4rRqqvwAAAJhKKqo/AAAALhRxsr8AAAAiu6+kvwAAAN6OlMc/AAAAeXgfuz8AAABE2SyyPwAAALC+eqa/AAAA5GSnmj8AAABcKdu7vwAAAHC/baK/AAAAANRaoT8AAADsLMa0PwAAADxV8p4/AAAAvkM5wj8AAADg8f7avwAAAEza58G/AAAA4BLHkz8AAEC2p7fCPwAAABa/+L6/AAAAaDAL4T8AAADkXSWiPwAAADhodLi/AAAA2idWvr8AAIAtjoKfvwAAAIhFmb2/AAAAoNr5ir8AAADSkMalPwAAACh6RqK/AAAAnO7Qsr8AAACYiJOrvwAAAKiAhXY/AAAAnsr+sj8AAAAomNm4PwAAAFQL6KC/AAAApiJ4pT8AAABgai2RvwAAAPxXwLs/AABA35belb8AAADgdwzAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "guess",
      "question",
      "States",
      "anything"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I have buildings in South Korea",
    "question": " Well I guess the question is, does the United States gain anything by having bases?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAaOnDkL8AAAAAPu8ovwAAAKT/nok/AAAAPLMahL8AAAAMauvBPwAAADYBppQ/AAAAXNhJpL8AAIBtug+mPwAAAFCY/Zy/AAAAALDKSz8AAAA4rRqqvwAAAJhKKqo/AAAALhRxsr8AAAAiu6+kvwAAAN6OlMc/AAAAeXgfuz8AAABE2SyyPwAAALC+eqa/AAAA5GSnmj8AAABcKdu7vwAAAHC/baK/AAAAANRaoT8AAADsLMa0PwAAADxV8p4/AAAAvkM5wj8AAADg8f7avwAAAEza58G/AAAA4BLHkz8AAEC2p7fCPwAAABa/+L6/AAAAaDAL4T8AAADkXSWiPwAAADhodLi/AAAA2idWvr8AAIAtjoKfvwAAAIhFmb2/AAAAoNr5ir8AAADSkMalPwAAACh6RqK/AAAAnO7Qsr8AAACYiJOrvwAAAKiAhXY/AAAAnsr+sj8AAAAomNm4PwAAAFQL6KC/AAAApiJ4pT8AAABgai2RvwAAAPxXwLs/AABA35belb8AAADgdwzAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "guess",
      "question",
      "States",
      "anything"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But that’s a wealthy country",
    "question": " Well I guess the question is, does the United States gain anything by having bases?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAaOnDkL8AAAAAPu8ovwAAAKT/nok/AAAAPLMahL8AAAAMauvBPwAAADYBppQ/AAAAXNhJpL8AAIBtug+mPwAAAFCY/Zy/AAAAALDKSz8AAAA4rRqqvwAAAJhKKqo/AAAALhRxsr8AAAAiu6+kvwAAAN6OlMc/AAAAeXgfuz8AAABE2SyyPwAAALC+eqa/AAAA5GSnmj8AAABcKdu7vwAAAHC/baK/AAAAANRaoT8AAADsLMa0PwAAADxV8p4/AAAAvkM5wj8AAADg8f7avwAAAEza58G/AAAA4BLHkz8AAEC2p7fCPwAAABa/+L6/AAAAaDAL4T8AAADkXSWiPwAAADhodLi/AAAA2idWvr8AAIAtjoKfvwAAAIhFmb2/AAAAoNr5ir8AAADSkMalPwAAACh6RqK/AAAAnO7Qsr8AAACYiJOrvwAAAKiAhXY/AAAAnsr+sj8AAAAomNm4PwAAAFQL6KC/AAAApiJ4pT8AAABgai2RvwAAAPxXwLs/AABA35belb8AAADgdwzAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "guess",
      "question",
      "States",
      "anything"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They make the ships, they make the televisions, they make the air conditioning",
    "question": " Well I guess the question is, does the United States gain anything by having bases?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAaOnDkL8AAAAAPu8ovwAAAKT/nok/AAAAPLMahL8AAAAMauvBPwAAADYBppQ/AAAAXNhJpL8AAIBtug+mPwAAAFCY/Zy/AAAAALDKSz8AAAA4rRqqvwAAAJhKKqo/AAAALhRxsr8AAAAiu6+kvwAAAN6OlMc/AAAAeXgfuz8AAABE2SyyPwAAALC+eqa/AAAA5GSnmj8AAABcKdu7vwAAAHC/baK/AAAAANRaoT8AAADsLMa0PwAAADxV8p4/AAAAvkM5wj8AAADg8f7avwAAAEza58G/AAAA4BLHkz8AAEC2p7fCPwAAABa/+L6/AAAAaDAL4T8AAADkXSWiPwAAADhodLi/AAAA2idWvr8AAIAtjoKfvwAAAIhFmb2/AAAAoNr5ir8AAADSkMalPwAAACh6RqK/AAAAnO7Qsr8AAACYiJOrvwAAAKiAhXY/AAAAnsr+sj8AAAAomNm4PwAAAFQL6KC/AAAApiJ4pT8AAABgai2RvwAAAPxXwLs/AABA35belb8AAADgdwzAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "guess",
      "question",
      "States",
      "anything"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They make tremendous amounts of products",
    "question": " Well I guess the question is, does the United States gain anything by having bases?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAaOnDkL8AAAAAPu8ovwAAAKT/nok/AAAAPLMahL8AAAAMauvBPwAAADYBppQ/AAAAXNhJpL8AAIBtug+mPwAAAFCY/Zy/AAAAALDKSz8AAAA4rRqqvwAAAJhKKqo/AAAALhRxsr8AAAAiu6+kvwAAAN6OlMc/AAAAeXgfuz8AAABE2SyyPwAAALC+eqa/AAAA5GSnmj8AAABcKdu7vwAAAHC/baK/AAAAANRaoT8AAADsLMa0PwAAADxV8p4/AAAAvkM5wj8AAADg8f7avwAAAEza58G/AAAA4BLHkz8AAEC2p7fCPwAAABa/+L6/AAAAaDAL4T8AAADkXSWiPwAAADhodLi/AAAA2idWvr8AAIAtjoKfvwAAAIhFmb2/AAAAoNr5ir8AAADSkMalPwAAACh6RqK/AAAAnO7Qsr8AAACYiJOrvwAAAKiAhXY/AAAAnsr+sj8AAAAomNm4PwAAAFQL6KC/AAAApiJ4pT8AAABgai2RvwAAAPxXwLs/AABA35belb8AAADgdwzAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "guess",
      "question",
      "States",
      "anything"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " It’s a huge, it’s a massive industrial complex country",
    "question": " Well I guess the question is, does the United States gain anything by having bases?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAaOnDkL8AAAAAPu8ovwAAAKT/nok/AAAAPLMahL8AAAAMauvBPwAAADYBppQ/AAAAXNhJpL8AAIBtug+mPwAAAFCY/Zy/AAAAALDKSz8AAAA4rRqqvwAAAJhKKqo/AAAALhRxsr8AAAAiu6+kvwAAAN6OlMc/AAAAeXgfuz8AAABE2SyyPwAAALC+eqa/AAAA5GSnmj8AAABcKdu7vwAAAHC/baK/AAAAANRaoT8AAADsLMa0PwAAADxV8p4/AAAAvkM5wj8AAADg8f7avwAAAEza58G/AAAA4BLHkz8AAEC2p7fCPwAAABa/+L6/AAAAaDAL4T8AAADkXSWiPwAAADhodLi/AAAA2idWvr8AAIAtjoKfvwAAAIhFmb2/AAAAoNr5ir8AAADSkMalPwAAACh6RqK/AAAAnO7Qsr8AAACYiJOrvwAAAKiAhXY/AAAAnsr+sj8AAAAomNm4PwAAAFQL6KC/AAAApiJ4pT8AAABgai2RvwAAAPxXwLs/AABA35belb8AAADgdwzAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "guess",
      "question",
      "States",
      "anything"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And —",
    "question": " Well I guess the question is, does the United States gain anything by having bases?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAaOnDkL8AAAAAPu8ovwAAAKT/nok/AAAAPLMahL8AAAAMauvBPwAAADYBppQ/AAAAXNhJpL8AAIBtug+mPwAAAFCY/Zy/AAAAALDKSz8AAAA4rRqqvwAAAJhKKqo/AAAALhRxsr8AAAAiu6+kvwAAAN6OlMc/AAAAeXgfuz8AAABE2SyyPwAAALC+eqa/AAAA5GSnmj8AAABcKdu7vwAAAHC/baK/AAAAANRaoT8AAADsLMa0PwAAADxV8p4/AAAAvkM5wj8AAADg8f7avwAAAEza58G/AAAA4BLHkz8AAEC2p7fCPwAAABa/+L6/AAAAaDAL4T8AAADkXSWiPwAAADhodLi/AAAA2idWvr8AAIAtjoKfvwAAAIhFmb2/AAAAoNr5ir8AAADSkMalPwAAACh6RqK/AAAAnO7Qsr8AAACYiJOrvwAAAKiAhXY/AAAAnsr+sj8AAAAomNm4PwAAAFQL6KC/AAAApiJ4pT8AAABgai2RvwAAAPxXwLs/AABA35belb8AAADgdwzAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "guess",
      "question",
      "States",
      "anything"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " 50 percent?",
    "question": "  You know, well, they say and I think this is on public record, it’s basically 50 percent of the non-personnel cost is paid by South Korea and Japan.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgHQPkr8AAAC8NQVPvwAAAAh9v8Y/AACAtlVulb8AAABAGPOSPwAAAHCqGJ4/AAAAZL7Sv78AAHhOgGO3vwAAAFAec5A/AAAA6NfTuD8AAADQWLeZvwAAwMMP77q/AAAAaPn6kr8AAAAIZg+3vwAAAARYmMc/AAAAcA3ilj8AAADwCz1yPwAAABALSqi/AAAAyPh7s78AAACIvoy4vwAAABBU9ac/AAAAgPGTmb8AAADgAFiFPwAAAMLa27m/AAAAAKa6gL8AAACuETDQvwAAAOpxprC/AAAAFnNMrr8AAAD8GHCkPwAAAPjKg6E/AAAAyJMi4z8AAABqdKG5PwAAAJC6UqE/AAAAMDY0oz8AAACBebaaPwAAgIqVy8C/AAAAwOSJer8AAADQg/2uPwAAAEA4S68/AAAAWEr4tr8AAAA2tCm5vwAAAIgv/XS/AAAAJJ9pvT8AAADJpjyzPwAAAHCk/ai/AAAAQDtyib8AAIBATn6yvwAAAJ7gX7c/AAAAUBMsjz8AAACkaHadPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "record",
      "cost",
      "percent"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No, I don’t want to pull it out",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " NATO was set up at a different time",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " NATO was set up when we were a richer country",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We’re not a rich country",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We’re borrowing, we’re borrowing all of this money",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We’re borrowing money from China, which is a sort of an amazing situation",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But things are a much different thing",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " NATO is costing us a fortune and yes, we’re protecting Europe but we’re spending a lot of money",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Number 1, I think the distribution of costs has to be changed",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think NATO as a concept is good, but it is not as good as it was when it first evolved",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I think we bear the, you know, not only financially, we bear the biggest brunt of it",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Obama has been stronger on the Ukraine than all the other countries put together, and those other countries right next door to the Ukraine",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I just say we have, I’m not even knocking it, I’m just saying I don’t think it’s fair, we’re not treated fair",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I don’t think we’re treated fair, Charles, anywhere",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " If you look everything we have",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You know, South Korea is very rich",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Great industrial country",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And yet we’re not reimbursed fairly for what we do",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We’re constantly, you know, sending our ships, sending our planes, doing our war games, doing other",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We’re reimbursed a fraction of what this is all costing",
    "question": " As you know, the whole theory of NATO from the beginning  was to keep the United States involved in the long term in Europe to balance, to promote a balance of power in that region so we wouldn’t have a repeat of World War I and World War 2. And it seems to be like what you’re saying is very similar to what President Obama said to Jeffrey Goldberg, in that we have allies that become free riders. So it seems like there’s some convergence with the president there. What concerns me about both is that to some extent it was always thought to be in our interest that we, yes, we would take some of the burden on, yes, even if the net-net was not 100 percent, even steven, with the Germans. So I’d like to hear you say very specifically, you know, with respect to NATO, what is your ask of these other countries? Right, you’ve painted it in very broad terms, but do you have a percent of GDP that they should be spending on defense? Tell me more. Because it’s not that you want to pull the U.S. out.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAFFcGtj8AAAAg2XqKPwAAAAAbpqK/AAAAhKOMt78AAADgjreoPwAAAGRlZqw/AAAAMCPgr78AAABzUmWivwAAAOjkAry/AAAAIHb0r78AAIDrOIayPwAAAHD4U5S/AAAA0CYvwr8AAADQ3chyvwAAAJS+YK0/AAAAjqh1nz8AAADQs3OXvwAAAGgUeKC/AAAAhhVLvL8AAAAwJhOHPwAAAIIAx6A/AAAAHwESjL8AAACAm1+JvwAA4M4PRaW/AAAAeC4Lqj8AAAAAyyvSvwAAAAbrWLO/AAAAgF63h78AAABUfxamPwAAAOhVM7Q/AAAAVC4z4T8AAMBEas60vwAAgG3ZS76/AAAA6NFWwr8AAADgr3aOvwAAAAwL2LK/AAAAUMlBnz8AAAAoW2GoPwAAAFKoB6+/AAAASfXAsD8AAABwIf+evwAAANBPLam/AAAAQBnCgb8AAADIjWeyvwAAAGyfGqm/AAAAYCRUhj8AAABgIZOjPwAAANQx8bA/AAAAUKqyrr8AAACwe4OJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "was",
      "NATO",
      "beginning",
      "theory"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Yes",
    "question": " Can I ask you…Just going back to NATO, because…",
    "question_vector": "AAAA8P4Owz8AAAAwdz2bvwAAABin/KU/AAAA0J3Eub8AAADo7q7BPwAAAMzJibC/AAAAAPuOZT8AAABY0QvBPwAAANCKv7S/AAAAiPJ4xb8AAAAAgqtZPwAAAADYv4o/AAAAYIPRpL8AAABY97mcPwAAAKQwi7g/AAAA+C0ttz8AAACgPR2jPwAAAADGUrG/AAAARM+rtz8AAABEOUC7vwAAAAAIZWq/AACAQJumrz8AAACAciyXvwAAAEDYl6E/AAAAAJpNjT8AAACwRZ3WvwAAAABePG+/AAAAABKBZL8AAAAg24aiPwAAAFD2cLW/AAAAoIRg2z8AAAAQnfjAPwAAABBaDM+/AAAA6D5Rsr8AAADo3xyqvwAAAGA3uqq/AAAA6DYaqz8AAAAAEVSyvwAAABDYPrS/AAAAgOYqgz8AAACgg+ypPwAAALDsE7E/AAAAMOKcuz8AAADw2/e/vwAAAOjMYqU/AAAAMOLsqT8AAAAAFu6uvwAAAAD76sw/AACArPW4wL8AAADgqFDBPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "ask",
      "youJust",
      "NATO"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well I’ll give you, I’ll give you an example",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " President Obama, when he left Iraq, gave a specific date – we’re going to be out",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I thought that was a terrible thing to do",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "  And the enemy pulled back, because they don’t want die",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "  Despite what you read, you know, they don’t want to die — and they just pulled back, and after we left, all hell broke out, right? And I’ll give you another example that I think was terrible: when they sent, a few months ago, they sent fifty troops in",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You know, fifty elite troops",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Now, why do we have to have a news conference to announce that we’re sending fifty troops? So those troops now have targets on their back",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And…you shouldn’t do it",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "  We’re so predictable: “Ladies and gentlemen, we’re sending fifty troops into Iraq or Syria",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And these are our elite troops",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And they’re going to do this and that and that and this",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” And those troops now are being hunted",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " If you didn’t send them, they wouldn’t – if you didn’t say that, they wouldn’t know",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean, there are times when you just can’t be… You talk too much",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We talk too much",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I guess they thought that was good politically, to say we’re sending fifty troops? I don’t think it was good",
    "question": " This theory of unpredictability, I want to push a little bit, I mean – there are many people who think that North Korea invaded South Korea precisely because Acheson wasn’t clear that we would defend South Korea. So I’m curious, does ambiguity sometimes have dangers?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA0DHMmz8AAACAmyR+vwAAAARGKLC/AAAAULS9nL8AAADg/wWtPwAAAOAj9IE/AAAAeYxUuD8AAADAfBGHvwAAAPizabK/AAAAtkM5wj8AAADgb416PwAAAIx4ZbE/AAAArMFcub8AAAAAjGoPPwAAAAiTL64/AAAAYHgfvj8AAADkow26PwAAAIAJH3c/AAAAaN0XjD8AAADQjWTCvwAAAIAVlrK/AAAAcJkjkD8AAADAjv5+vwAAAFBpcIw/AAAAxBSHwj8AAAC0nafNvwAAAKjwxci/AAAAIHD4sj8AAABDAxnGPwAAANDl1qA/AAAARBbx2D8AAABwNI+sPwAAAOAaEJu/AAAA3P6JwL8AABCYPtucvwAAAEiB7am/AAAAyJVSub8AAAA0usuYPwAAAMCTIGA/AAAA4EiwqL8AAMAN7z+bvwAAAFiYZ5c/AAAAABvsqL8AAABYCy3DPwAAANgcnnW/AAAA2DkegD8AAAAEUDLAPwAAADjCQ7w/AAAAkM8Ojz8AAABQs86sPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want",
      "unpredictability",
      "theory",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well, I, you know, again, I don’t like to tell you what I’d do, because I don’t want to… You understand what I’m saying, Fred? If I… Okay, if I say ‘Well, we should go in and do this or that or that,’ I don’t want to, I don’t want to sort of… red flag all over it",
    "question": " So, if they occupied what the Japanese call the Senkaku Islands, is that something the United States…",
    "question_vector": "VVVVVZkTbL8AAAAQxOmZPwAAAOBagJO/q6qquvsFsD8AAABgJ622PwAAANhUIK4/q6pq0/x7rL8AAAB+6AuivwAAAECRA5y/VVVV1e6Jpr+rqqp6swm6P6uqqqohx4s/AAAAMJprpz8AAABAos+ZP6uqqurJlKg/q6qqdg0VpT+rqqqqf5V+v6uqqirBIak/AAAAeI/mpr9VVVUlfuuUP1VVVVUBg6U/AAAA4OUjs78AAAAI07aWv1VVVfVsHIQ/q6qqSryNoz+rqqrK1JTYv6uqqmprtKC/q6qqKj/GmL8AAADwZLWIv6uqqqqgxZS/AAAA8MsT5D+rqqrCwx2tvwAAAABg63s/VVVVlT24rL8AAAAAYPkzP6uqqrKaGba/VVVVtZtzmr9VVVVV1eRBPwAAAHCKOL+/q6qqyrXvrb8AAACqOveyv6uqqoqBUZW/AAAA0O67wT8AAAAQoBi4v6uqqio+Uqw/q6qqykQJoz9VVVXdlIGxvwAAAKCeiqY/q6qqKhjri79VVVUVV2WXPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "Japanese",
      "States"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I do think this: It’s an unbelievable thing that they’ve done, it’s unbelievable aggression, it’s unbelievable lack of respect for this country",
    "question": " So, if they occupied what the Japanese call the Senkaku Islands, is that something the United States…",
    "question_vector": "VVVVVZkTbL8AAAAQxOmZPwAAAOBagJO/q6qquvsFsD8AAABgJ622PwAAANhUIK4/q6pq0/x7rL8AAAB+6AuivwAAAECRA5y/VVVV1e6Jpr+rqqp6swm6P6uqqqohx4s/AAAAMJprpz8AAABAos+ZP6uqqurJlKg/q6qqdg0VpT+rqqqqf5V+v6uqqirBIak/AAAAeI/mpr9VVVUlfuuUP1VVVVUBg6U/AAAA4OUjs78AAAAI07aWv1VVVfVsHIQ/q6qqSryNoz+rqqrK1JTYv6uqqmprtKC/q6qqKj/GmL8AAADwZLWIv6uqqqqgxZS/AAAA8MsT5D+rqqrCwx2tvwAAAABg63s/VVVVlT24rL8AAAAAYPkzP6uqqrKaGba/VVVVtZtzmr9VVVVV1eRBPwAAAHCKOL+/q6qqyrXvrb8AAACqOveyv6uqqoqBUZW/AAAA0O67wT8AAAAQoBi4v6uqqio+Uqw/q6qqykQJoz9VVVXdlIGxvwAAAKCeiqY/q6qqKhjri79VVVUVV2WXPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "Japanese",
      "States"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We, well, you start making it tougher",
    "question": " What would you do?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They’re selling their products to us for… you know, with no tax, no nothing",
    "question": " What would you do?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " By the way, we can’t deal with them, but they can deal with us",
    "question": " What would you do?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " See, we are free trade",
    "question": " What would you do?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " The story is, and I have so many people that deal with China –they can easily sell their product here",
    "question": " What would you do?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No tax, no nothing, just ‘come on, bring it all in, you know, bring in your apples, bring in everything you make’ and no taxes whatsoever, right? If you want to deal with China, it’s just the opposite",
    "question": " What would you do?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You can’t do that",
    "question": " What would you do?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " In other words, if you want to, if you’re a manufacturer, you want to go into China? It’s very hard to get your product in, and if you get it in you have to pay a very big tax",
    "question": " What would you do?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think so, yeah",
    "question": " Could you use trade to cause them to retreat in the South China Sea?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwOrPrT9VVVUpJcanPwAAAGDaAq+/AAAAIG1Xqj+rqqoqMDVwv1VVVVVVBI6/AAAA8MsFub8AAADAwYa+v1VVVfVWAKo/AAAAYGito78AAACwlGypP1VVVVU5B70/q6qqCpQNuT9VVVWl/cWrPwAAAADLHX+/VVVVVZI1qT8AAAB4SHitPwAAAMCZpJ+/q6qq/DZsu79VVVXzTsqzv6uqqlL9ibU/VVVVOQaJs7+rqqpKAmuhP1VVVcU76bK/VVVV1esDgD8AAABgN77Pv1VVVeUqxrI/AAAAsKeinT8AAAAwT23CP6uqqoo7TZS/AAAAYF2w4z9VVVXVoHJ7v6uqqvozkrK/AAAAAGQGUb9VVVX8nKedv1VVVRXvoYy/q6qqSkx9sb9VVVWFe6yhv1VVVSXeXbS/q6qq6q9JtT8AAACgzEejvwAAAABIrnC/VVVVhYOixz8AAAAAAI9Dv6uqqir/EKg/AAAAAOxWgz8AAACwcr2gv6uqqmodIKs/q6qqqhyHdr9VVVWdin2uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "use",
      "trade",
      "Sea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think so",
    "question": " Could you use trade to cause them to retreat in the South China Sea?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwOrPrT9VVVUpJcanPwAAAGDaAq+/AAAAIG1Xqj+rqqoqMDVwv1VVVVVVBI6/AAAA8MsFub8AAADAwYa+v1VVVfVWAKo/AAAAYGito78AAACwlGypP1VVVVU5B70/q6qqCpQNuT9VVVWl/cWrPwAAAADLHX+/VVVVVZI1qT8AAAB4SHitPwAAAMCZpJ+/q6qq/DZsu79VVVXzTsqzv6uqqlL9ibU/VVVVOQaJs7+rqqpKAmuhP1VVVcU76bK/VVVV1esDgD8AAABgN77Pv1VVVeUqxrI/AAAAsKeinT8AAAAwT23CP6uqqoo7TZS/AAAAYF2w4z9VVVXVoHJ7v6uqqvozkrK/AAAAAGQGUb9VVVX8nKedv1VVVRXvoYy/q6qqSkx9sb9VVVWFe6yhv1VVVSXeXbS/q6qq6q9JtT8AAACgzEejvwAAAABIrnC/VVVVhYOixz8AAAAAAI9Dv6uqqir/EKg/AAAAAOxWgz8AAACwcr2gv6uqqmodIKs/q6qqqhyHdr9VVVWdin2uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "use",
      "trade",
      "Sea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well I know China very well, because I deal with China all the time",
    "question": " So what do you think China’s aims are in the South China Sea?",
    "question_vector": "VVVVfYPuuj8AAAB1Qe2zPwAAAEBnOX6/VVVV1QSVbb8AAABQ/GOsP6uqqr5NAai/VVVVlTNoob8AAAAw5Ruyv6uqqiqKJKs/q6qqqnEydT9VVVWVK0GRP6uqqkpRf6o/q6qqqprLTb8AAAD4GXadPwAAAADgkUa/q6qq2h3ksD8AAACABrjGPwAAAOBDOqc/AAAAhApBtr9VVVW52VKlv6uqquovRIs/VVVV5Vyqmj8AAACAScWSP6uqqgq4fKC/VVVV1R5uuj+rqqo6RzzRv1VVVVWnYqO/VVVVVVNqYz8AAABwy223P1VVVYa7VKW/VVVVFZmn4T8AAAAweHW7P1VVVcWTir6/q6qq6j6Hpr8AAMBJpNKxvwAAAFDJTK+/AAAAUOFHtb9VVVW1fLaTvwAAAOBGnaK/q6qqaoEtpr8AAABggSisv1VVVYeXMba/VVVVfWxjwD+rqqpqNRClv6uqqmqQZ5M/q6qqSjnaoj9VVVXVlJ91v6uqqipCfKs/VVVVpbDXaj+rqqo2FLCVPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "aims",
      "Sea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’ve done very well",
    "question": " So what do you think China’s aims are in the South China Sea?",
    "question_vector": "VVVVfYPuuj8AAAB1Qe2zPwAAAEBnOX6/VVVV1QSVbb8AAABQ/GOsP6uqqr5NAai/VVVVlTNoob8AAAAw5Ruyv6uqqiqKJKs/q6qqqnEydT9VVVWVK0GRP6uqqkpRf6o/q6qqqprLTb8AAAD4GXadPwAAAADgkUa/q6qq2h3ksD8AAACABrjGPwAAAOBDOqc/AAAAhApBtr9VVVW52VKlv6uqquovRIs/VVVV5Vyqmj8AAACAScWSP6uqqgq4fKC/VVVV1R5uuj+rqqo6RzzRv1VVVVWnYqO/VVVVVVNqYz8AAABwy223P1VVVYa7VKW/VVVVFZmn4T8AAAAweHW7P1VVVcWTir6/q6qq6j6Hpr8AAMBJpNKxvwAAAFDJTK+/AAAAUOFHtb9VVVW1fLaTvwAAAOBGnaK/q6qqaoEtpr8AAABggSisv1VVVYeXMba/VVVVfWxjwD+rqqpqNRClv6uqqmqQZ5M/q6qqSjnaoj9VVVXVlJ91v6uqqipCfKs/VVVVpbDXaj+rqqo2FLCVPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "aims",
      "Sea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " China’s unbelievably ambitious",
    "question": " So what do you think China’s aims are in the South China Sea?",
    "question_vector": "VVVVfYPuuj8AAAB1Qe2zPwAAAEBnOX6/VVVV1QSVbb8AAABQ/GOsP6uqqr5NAai/VVVVlTNoob8AAAAw5Ruyv6uqqiqKJKs/q6qqqnEydT9VVVWVK0GRP6uqqkpRf6o/q6qqqprLTb8AAAD4GXadPwAAAADgkUa/q6qq2h3ksD8AAACABrjGPwAAAOBDOqc/AAAAhApBtr9VVVW52VKlv6uqquovRIs/VVVV5Vyqmj8AAACAScWSP6uqqgq4fKC/VVVV1R5uuj+rqqo6RzzRv1VVVVWnYqO/VVVVVVNqYz8AAABwy223P1VVVYa7VKW/VVVVFZmn4T8AAAAweHW7P1VVVcWTir6/q6qq6j6Hpr8AAMBJpNKxvwAAAFDJTK+/AAAAUOFHtb9VVVW1fLaTvwAAAOBGnaK/q6qqaoEtpr8AAABggSisv1VVVYeXMba/VVVVfWxjwD+rqqpqNRClv6uqqmqQZ5M/q6qqSjnaoj9VVVXVlJ91v6uqqipCfKs/VVVVpbDXaj+rqqo2FLCVPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "aims",
      "Sea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " China is, uh… I mean, when I deal with China, you know, I have the Bank of America building, I’ve done some great deals with China",
    "question": " So what do you think China’s aims are in the South China Sea?",
    "question_vector": "VVVVfYPuuj8AAAB1Qe2zPwAAAEBnOX6/VVVV1QSVbb8AAABQ/GOsP6uqqr5NAai/VVVVlTNoob8AAAAw5Ruyv6uqqiqKJKs/q6qqqnEydT9VVVWVK0GRP6uqqkpRf6o/q6qqqprLTb8AAAD4GXadPwAAAADgkUa/q6qq2h3ksD8AAACABrjGPwAAAOBDOqc/AAAAhApBtr9VVVW52VKlv6uqquovRIs/VVVV5Vyqmj8AAACAScWSP6uqqgq4fKC/VVVV1R5uuj+rqqo6RzzRv1VVVVWnYqO/VVVVVVNqYz8AAABwy223P1VVVYa7VKW/VVVVFZmn4T8AAAAweHW7P1VVVcWTir6/q6qq6j6Hpr8AAMBJpNKxvwAAAFDJTK+/AAAAUOFHtb9VVVW1fLaTvwAAAOBGnaK/q6qqaoEtpr8AAABggSisv1VVVYeXMba/VVVVfWxjwD+rqqpqNRClv6uqqmqQZ5M/q6qqSjnaoj9VVVXVlJ91v6uqqipCfKs/VVVVpbDXaj+rqqo2FLCVPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "aims",
      "Sea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I do deals with them all the time on, you know, selling apartments, and, you know, people say ‘oh that’s not the same thing",
    "question": " So what do you think China’s aims are in the South China Sea?",
    "question_vector": "VVVVfYPuuj8AAAB1Qe2zPwAAAEBnOX6/VVVV1QSVbb8AAABQ/GOsP6uqqr5NAai/VVVVlTNoob8AAAAw5Ruyv6uqqiqKJKs/q6qqqnEydT9VVVWVK0GRP6uqqkpRf6o/q6qqqprLTb8AAAD4GXadPwAAAADgkUa/q6qq2h3ksD8AAACABrjGPwAAAOBDOqc/AAAAhApBtr9VVVW52VKlv6uqquovRIs/VVVV5Vyqmj8AAACAScWSP6uqqgq4fKC/VVVV1R5uuj+rqqo6RzzRv1VVVVWnYqO/VVVVVVNqYz8AAABwy223P1VVVYa7VKW/VVVVFZmn4T8AAAAweHW7P1VVVcWTir6/q6qq6j6Hpr8AAMBJpNKxvwAAAFDJTK+/AAAAUOFHtb9VVVW1fLaTvwAAAOBGnaK/q6qqaoEtpr8AAABggSisv1VVVYeXMba/VVVVfWxjwD+rqqpqNRClv6uqqmqQZ5M/q6qqSjnaoj9VVVXVlJ91v6uqqipCfKs/VVVVpbDXaj+rqqo2FLCVPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "aims",
      "Sea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "’ The level of… uh, the largest bank in the world, 400 million customers, is a tenant of mine in New York, in Manhattan",
    "question": " So what do you think China’s aims are in the South China Sea?",
    "question_vector": "VVVVfYPuuj8AAAB1Qe2zPwAAAEBnOX6/VVVV1QSVbb8AAABQ/GOsP6uqqr5NAai/VVVVlTNoob8AAAAw5Ruyv6uqqiqKJKs/q6qqqnEydT9VVVWVK0GRP6uqqkpRf6o/q6qqqprLTb8AAAD4GXadPwAAAADgkUa/q6qq2h3ksD8AAACABrjGPwAAAOBDOqc/AAAAhApBtr9VVVW52VKlv6uqquovRIs/VVVV5Vyqmj8AAACAScWSP6uqqgq4fKC/VVVV1R5uuj+rqqo6RzzRv1VVVVWnYqO/VVVVVVNqYz8AAABwy223P1VVVYa7VKW/VVVVFZmn4T8AAAAweHW7P1VVVcWTir6/q6qq6j6Hpr8AAMBJpNKxvwAAAFDJTK+/AAAAUOFHtb9VVVW1fLaTvwAAAOBGnaK/q6qqaoEtpr8AAABggSisv1VVVYeXMba/VVVVfWxjwD+rqqpqNRClv6uqqmqQZ5M/q6qqSjnaoj9VVVXVlJ91v6uqqipCfKs/VVVVpbDXaj+rqqo2FLCVPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "aims",
      "Sea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " The biggest bank in China",
    "question": " So what do you think China’s aims are in the South China Sea?",
    "question_vector": "VVVVfYPuuj8AAAB1Qe2zPwAAAEBnOX6/VVVV1QSVbb8AAABQ/GOsP6uqqr5NAai/VVVVlTNoob8AAAAw5Ruyv6uqqiqKJKs/q6qqqnEydT9VVVWVK0GRP6uqqkpRf6o/q6qqqprLTb8AAAD4GXadPwAAAADgkUa/q6qq2h3ksD8AAACABrjGPwAAAOBDOqc/AAAAhApBtr9VVVW52VKlv6uqquovRIs/VVVV5Vyqmj8AAACAScWSP6uqqgq4fKC/VVVV1R5uuj+rqqo6RzzRv1VVVVWnYqO/VVVVVVNqYz8AAABwy223P1VVVYa7VKW/VVVVFZmn4T8AAAAweHW7P1VVVcWTir6/q6qq6j6Hpr8AAMBJpNKxvwAAAFDJTK+/AAAAUOFHtb9VVVW1fLaTvwAAAOBGnaK/q6qqaoEtpr8AAABggSisv1VVVYeXMba/VVVVfWxjwD+rqqpqNRClv6uqqmqQZ5M/q6qqSjnaoj9VVVXVlJ91v6uqqipCfKs/VVVVpbDXaj+rqqo2FLCVPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "aims",
      "Sea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " The biggest bank in the world",
    "question": " So what do you think China’s aims are in the South China Sea?",
    "question_vector": "VVVVfYPuuj8AAAB1Qe2zPwAAAEBnOX6/VVVV1QSVbb8AAABQ/GOsP6uqqr5NAai/VVVVlTNoob8AAAAw5Ruyv6uqqiqKJKs/q6qqqnEydT9VVVWVK0GRP6uqqkpRf6o/q6qqqprLTb8AAAD4GXadPwAAAADgkUa/q6qq2h3ksD8AAACABrjGPwAAAOBDOqc/AAAAhApBtr9VVVW52VKlv6uqquovRIs/VVVV5Vyqmj8AAACAScWSP6uqqgq4fKC/VVVV1R5uuj+rqqo6RzzRv1VVVVWnYqO/VVVVVVNqYz8AAABwy223P1VVVYa7VKW/VVVVFZmn4T8AAAAweHW7P1VVVcWTir6/q6qq6j6Hpr8AAMBJpNKxvwAAAFDJTK+/AAAAUOFHtb9VVVW1fLaTvwAAAOBGnaK/q6qqaoEtpr8AAABggSisv1VVVYeXMba/VVVVfWxjwD+rqqpqNRClv6uqqmqQZ5M/q6qqSjnaoj9VVVXVlJ91v6uqqipCfKs/VVVVpbDXaj+rqqo2FLCVPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "aims",
      "Sea"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Yeah, I would defend the areas with the oil",
    "question": " With U.S. troops?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIDqUyT8AAABA9GzIvwAAAICu+ME/AAAAIKpQw78AAABgceKzPwAAACDRXMO/AAAAAAlTlj8AAABA6k/EPwAAAACdpru/AAAAAGNr1b8AAAAABrVKPwAAAGC4qsi/AAAAwNCrez8AAABAYJvAvwAAAEDZh6K/AAAAYFNfi78AAADALo2lPwAAAOCUWGE/AAAA4FjHub8AAABg+Z+YvwAAAIB+1aW/AAAAQOxgrj8AAAAAvAaePwAAAKBwxri/AAAAAJc0sr8AAAAg9CzRvwAAAECxppU/AAAAYKwQrb8AAAAAz/C0PwAAACDjR7Y/AAAAAHks4D8AAABAXhiiPwAAAADJLcm/AAAAQFSkhz8AAAAA3Ad+PwAAAGApocM/AAAAgMXqob8AAABgLVu4vwAAAIDOAsu/AAAAgMPgqz8AAAAgVsGCPwAAACARMLE/AAAAYD6IwD8AAABAt3nKvwAAAOBOMqo/AAAAoOJhwr8AAABgR3S2vwAAAIC0waQ/AAAAQITXyb8AAADgCq+5vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "troops"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "  And I would have taken out a lot of oil",
    "question": " With U.S. troops?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIDqUyT8AAABA9GzIvwAAAICu+ME/AAAAIKpQw78AAABgceKzPwAAACDRXMO/AAAAAAlTlj8AAABA6k/EPwAAAACdpru/AAAAAGNr1b8AAAAABrVKPwAAAGC4qsi/AAAAwNCrez8AAABAYJvAvwAAAEDZh6K/AAAAYFNfi78AAADALo2lPwAAAOCUWGE/AAAA4FjHub8AAABg+Z+YvwAAAIB+1aW/AAAAQOxgrj8AAAAAvAaePwAAAKBwxri/AAAAAJc0sr8AAAAg9CzRvwAAAECxppU/AAAAYKwQrb8AAAAAz/C0PwAAACDjR7Y/AAAAAHks4D8AAABAXhiiPwAAAADJLcm/AAAAQFSkhz8AAAAA3Ad+PwAAAGApocM/AAAAgMXqob8AAABgLVu4vwAAAIDOAsu/AAAAgMPgqz8AAAAgVsGCPwAAACARMLE/AAAAYD6IwD8AAABAt3nKvwAAAOBOMqo/AAAAoOJhwr8AAABgR3S2vwAAAIC0waQ/AAAAQITXyb8AAADgCq+5vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "troops"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And, uh, I would have kept it",
    "question": " With U.S. troops?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIDqUyT8AAABA9GzIvwAAAICu+ME/AAAAIKpQw78AAABgceKzPwAAACDRXMO/AAAAAAlTlj8AAABA6k/EPwAAAACdpru/AAAAAGNr1b8AAAAABrVKPwAAAGC4qsi/AAAAwNCrez8AAABAYJvAvwAAAEDZh6K/AAAAYFNfi78AAADALo2lPwAAAOCUWGE/AAAA4FjHub8AAABg+Z+YvwAAAIB+1aW/AAAAQOxgrj8AAAAAvAaePwAAAKBwxri/AAAAAJc0sr8AAAAg9CzRvwAAAECxppU/AAAAYKwQrb8AAAAAz/C0PwAAACDjR7Y/AAAAAHks4D8AAABAXhiiPwAAAADJLcm/AAAAQFSkhz8AAAAA3Ad+PwAAAGApocM/AAAAgMXqob8AAABgLVu4vwAAAIDOAsu/AAAAgMPgqz8AAAAgVsGCPwAAACARMLE/AAAAYD6IwD8AAABAt3nKvwAAAOBOMqo/AAAAoOJhwr8AAABgR3S2vwAAAIC0waQ/AAAAQITXyb8AAADgCq+5vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "troops"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean, I would have kept it, because, look: Iran has the oil, and they’re going to have the oil, well, the stuff they don’t have, because Iran is taking over Iraq as sure as you’re sitting there",
    "question": " With U.S. troops?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIDqUyT8AAABA9GzIvwAAAICu+ME/AAAAIKpQw78AAABgceKzPwAAACDRXMO/AAAAAAlTlj8AAABA6k/EPwAAAACdpru/AAAAAGNr1b8AAAAABrVKPwAAAGC4qsi/AAAAwNCrez8AAABAYJvAvwAAAEDZh6K/AAAAYFNfi78AAADALo2lPwAAAOCUWGE/AAAA4FjHub8AAABg+Z+YvwAAAIB+1aW/AAAAQOxgrj8AAAAAvAaePwAAAKBwxri/AAAAAJc0sr8AAAAg9CzRvwAAAECxppU/AAAAYKwQrb8AAAAAz/C0PwAAACDjR7Y/AAAAAHks4D8AAABAXhiiPwAAAADJLcm/AAAAQFSkhz8AAAAA3Ad+PwAAAGApocM/AAAAgMXqob8AAABgLVu4vwAAAIDOAsu/AAAAgMPgqz8AAAAgVsGCPwAAACARMLE/AAAAYD6IwD8AAABAt3nKvwAAAOBOMqo/AAAAoOJhwr8AAABgR3S2vwAAAIC0waQ/AAAAQITXyb8AAADgCq+5vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "troops"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I’ve been very good on this stuff",
    "question": " With U.S. troops?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIDqUyT8AAABA9GzIvwAAAICu+ME/AAAAIKpQw78AAABgceKzPwAAACDRXMO/AAAAAAlTlj8AAABA6k/EPwAAAACdpru/AAAAAGNr1b8AAAAABrVKPwAAAGC4qsi/AAAAwNCrez8AAABAYJvAvwAAAEDZh6K/AAAAYFNfi78AAADALo2lPwAAAOCUWGE/AAAA4FjHub8AAABg+Z+YvwAAAIB+1aW/AAAAQOxgrj8AAAAAvAaePwAAAKBwxri/AAAAAJc0sr8AAAAg9CzRvwAAAECxppU/AAAAYKwQrb8AAAAAz/C0PwAAACDjR7Y/AAAAAHks4D8AAABAXhiiPwAAAADJLcm/AAAAQFSkhz8AAAAA3Ad+PwAAAGApocM/AAAAgMXqob8AAABgLVu4vwAAAIDOAsu/AAAAgMPgqz8AAAAgVsGCPwAAACARMLE/AAAAYD6IwD8AAABAt3nKvwAAAOBOMqo/AAAAoOJhwr8AAABgR3S2vwAAAIC0waQ/AAAAQITXyb8AAADgCq+5vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "troops"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " My prognostications, my predictions have become, have been very accurate, if you look",
    "question": " With U.S. troops?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIDqUyT8AAABA9GzIvwAAAICu+ME/AAAAIKpQw78AAABgceKzPwAAACDRXMO/AAAAAAlTlj8AAABA6k/EPwAAAACdpru/AAAAAGNr1b8AAAAABrVKPwAAAGC4qsi/AAAAwNCrez8AAABAYJvAvwAAAEDZh6K/AAAAYFNfi78AAADALo2lPwAAAOCUWGE/AAAA4FjHub8AAABg+Z+YvwAAAIB+1aW/AAAAQOxgrj8AAAAAvAaePwAAAKBwxri/AAAAAJc0sr8AAAAg9CzRvwAAAECxppU/AAAAYKwQrb8AAAAAz/C0PwAAACDjR7Y/AAAAAHks4D8AAABAXhiiPwAAAADJLcm/AAAAQFSkhz8AAAAA3Ad+PwAAAGApocM/AAAAgMXqob8AAABgLVu4vwAAAIDOAsu/AAAAgMPgqz8AAAAgVsGCPwAAACARMLE/AAAAYD6IwD8AAABAt3nKvwAAAOBOMqo/AAAAoOJhwr8AAABgR3S2vwAAAIC0waQ/AAAAQITXyb8AAADgCq+5vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "troops"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You would… You would, well for that– for that, I would circle it",
    "question": " How do you keep it without troops, how do you defend the oil?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgBJ1tz9VVVUF+rS2v6uqqlozRcA/VVVVlf1ktb9VVVU1X2CyP1VVVfVyp7q/VVVVlcuMsb8AAAA4n5KzP6uqqip/KGI/AAAAZmqZsr8AAADgabOWP6uqqiohHJC/q6qq6gpncD9VVVUVd4GLvwAAAID1E5Y/AAAAvAiPsj9VVVUVxHG2P1VVVSEqsJK/q6qqauMror9VVVVdN0m+vwAAABjdILA/AAAAIKF5kb+rqqpa8CGyP1VVVek1C72/q6qq5kg4rb+rqqoq03XSvwAAAKAEf6c/VVVVdeZppz+rqqrKHF3GP6uqqmoI6bI/AAAAQJVb4j+rqqoqEairPwAAAPyREbm/VVVV1bEupT9VVVV9iIyZvwAAAECsu6M/q6qqaicXwL+rqqqqOnNhv1VVVVU9dUs/VVVVVTg8iL9VVVXl9IaWv6uqqkoP5qQ/q6qqqmUbuz9VVVXVTTK3v1VVVWW0gqY/q6qqiiOYlb9VVVU1E+e3vwAAAIBUe6k/q6qqeomxs7+rqqoyqs+0vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "keep",
      "troops",
      "oil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I would defend those areas",
    "question": " How do you keep it without troops, how do you defend the oil?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgBJ1tz9VVVUF+rS2v6uqqlozRcA/VVVVlf1ktb9VVVU1X2CyP1VVVfVyp7q/VVVVlcuMsb8AAAA4n5KzP6uqqip/KGI/AAAAZmqZsr8AAADgabOWP6uqqiohHJC/q6qq6gpncD9VVVUVd4GLvwAAAID1E5Y/AAAAvAiPsj9VVVUVxHG2P1VVVSEqsJK/q6qqauMror9VVVVdN0m+vwAAABjdILA/AAAAIKF5kb+rqqpa8CGyP1VVVek1C72/q6qq5kg4rb+rqqoq03XSvwAAAKAEf6c/VVVVdeZppz+rqqrKHF3GP6uqqmoI6bI/AAAAQJVb4j+rqqoqEairPwAAAPyREbm/VVVV1bEupT9VVVV9iIyZvwAAAECsu6M/q6qqaicXwL+rqqqqOnNhv1VVVVU9dUs/VVVVVTg8iL9VVVXl9IaWv6uqqkoP5qQ/q6qqqmUbuz9VVVXVTTK3v1VVVWW0gqY/q6qqiiOYlb9VVVU1E+e3vwAAAIBUe6k/q6qqeomxs7+rqqoyqs+0vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "keep",
      "troops",
      "oil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well look, we have power over China and people don’t realize it",
    "question": " –and what should we do about it?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We have trade power over China",
    "question": " –and what should we do about it?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I don’t think we are going to start World War III over what they did, it affects other countries certainly a lot more than it affects us",
    "question": " –and what should we do about it?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But—and honestly, you know part of—I always say we have to be unpredictable",
    "question": " –and what should we do about it?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We’re totally predictable",
    "question": " –and what should we do about it?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "  And predictable is bad",
    "question": " –and what should we do about it?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Sitting at a meeting like this and explaining my views and if I do become president, I have these views that are down for the other side to look at, you know",
    "question": " –and what should we do about it?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I hate being so open",
    "question": " –and what should we do about it?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I hate when they say — like I said get rid of the oil, keep the oil, different things over the years, when people are saying what would you do with regard to the Middle East, when we left — We should have never been in Iraq",
    "question": " –and what should we do about it?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " It was a horr- it was one of the worst decisions ever made in the history of our country",
    "question": " –and what should we do about it?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We then got out badly, then after we got out, I said, “Keep the oil",
    "question": " –and what should we do about it?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " If we don’t keep it Iran’s going to get it",
    "question": " –and what should we do about it?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” And it turns out Iran and ISIS basically—",
    "question": " –and what should we do about it?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIOecqT8AAABA//KXvwAAAIAJTH4/AAAAgIDCsL8AAACgkDeVPwAAAMAEMry/AAAAQJVuqL8AAACg50CPPwAAAABJ37e/AAAAgKK8qz8AAAAAdLhEPwAAAGAUKsQ/AAAAoBQQo78AAABgRveivwAAAGBx78M/AAAAYNRgwD8AAADgdVzCPwAAAIBLXUe/AAAAIIgytz8AAABAtGXLvwAAACA6Zrq/AAAAwGrlnD8AAABgBubBPwAAAEDNcrw/AAAAgLUttT8AAACgHVrVvwAAACAA2si/AAAAQCyRor8AAACAb2vBPwAAAEBK5M+/AAAAAItF5D8AAACAD+/FPwAAAADsbMi/AAAAAKvHtr8AAAAAW9CUvwAAAEAlKqi/AAAAYJ6Ghj8AAAAAHjR+vwAAAACQI7o/AAAAoCYTor8AAACAIMmzvwAAAMDl51w/AAAAwAzvsT8AAACg+M29PwAAAIC7CJk/AAAAwBchdr8AAAAA4KKAvwAAACAL/PO+AAAAgMH4lz8AAAAgVfjEPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "do"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think it’s a terrible situation, I think it’s terrible they have no respect for–",
    "question": " What about China and the South China Sea. What do you think they’re up to and—",
    "question_vector": "AAAAcE/fnL8AAABe1M6UPwAAAHB3HYE/AAAAsOrysz8AAAB2ApizPwAAAPBPwrK/AAAAANo3b78AAAAw8qGivwAAAACR/IK/AAAAgB4Amj8AAACAo1uJPwAAAJARHJw/AAAAoK5Zor8AAADgq8FjvwAAABihvLg/AAAAWL71tj8AAABganixPwAAAIAeYqU/AAAAKPFGnD8AAACgoNulvwAAAADwIJA/AAAAAPD+Ur8AAABoi22bPwAAAFAv56u/AAAA4Cucxz8AAABAbgfZvwAAAOB/l7W/AAAAgOBcfL8AAACAaAqRPwAAALipUra/AAAA4CKx4j8AAAAgjV/APwAAAEAtmpS/AAAAYKbdor8AAABQ9fi9vwAAAEgYDMG/AAAA2EG5sL8AAACwJOe2PwAAABDZ8rC/AAAAQEnooL8AAABQ6dDBvwAAAH6/SKW/AAAAeMddvD8AAAAAqJCPvwAAAPh2cbs/AAAAMLCPoj8AAACAO7GyvwAAAEDKF7A/AACATxReoj8AAADAU72oPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "China"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I find it hard to go along with—I mention that as an example because it’s so much",
    "question": " If they said that, would you go along with that and send the troops?",
    "question_vector": "AAAALGZXvT8AAADoQ+uzvwAAAEBSt7w/AAAA2BJOu78AAABwjiGyPwAAALA/3sK/AAAA4D4+sb8AAABYVmbAPwAAAIhyE7O/AAAoBi1txb8AAABUaRaovwAAADiJWLG/AAAAlCBjq78AAACg62ajvwAAAHAGm7c/AAAAlBLqqT8AAACwIfq2PwAAANL5/pu/AAAAnPSLrL8AAABM/MOyvwAAAIDwZXG/AAAAEBgKrj8AAABAROKqPwAAAIA5IYs/AAAAwPzgkz8AAADA3KHTvwAAAOAjaJK/AAAA8Ak7p78AAAAAb2+9PwAAAGDBJq2/AAAAkBO+4j8AAADYz6/APwAAAEDNT8m/AAAAcBfclz8AAAAwYwNpPwAAAF6/BLI/AAAAAKAeVz8AAADU9h6mvwAAADCoT7G/AAAAgJGzjL8AAAAcGjanvwAAAHC43pk/AAAAqH/5tD8AAACgLjiwvwAAALywBaE/AAAAoFftq78AAABwCxegvwAAAADmOla/AAAA5PeMtr8AAACAEOyRvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "go",
      "troops"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " That’s why I brought that up",
    "question": " If they said that, would you go along with that and send the troops?",
    "question_vector": "AAAALGZXvT8AAADoQ+uzvwAAAEBSt7w/AAAA2BJOu78AAABwjiGyPwAAALA/3sK/AAAA4D4+sb8AAABYVmbAPwAAAIhyE7O/AAAoBi1txb8AAABUaRaovwAAADiJWLG/AAAAlCBjq78AAACg62ajvwAAAHAGm7c/AAAAlBLqqT8AAACwIfq2PwAAANL5/pu/AAAAnPSLrL8AAABM/MOyvwAAAIDwZXG/AAAAEBgKrj8AAABAROKqPwAAAIA5IYs/AAAAwPzgkz8AAADA3KHTvwAAAOAjaJK/AAAA8Ak7p78AAAAAb2+9PwAAAGDBJq2/AAAAkBO+4j8AAADYz6/APwAAAEDNT8m/AAAAcBfclz8AAAAwYwNpPwAAAF6/BLI/AAAAAKAeVz8AAADU9h6mvwAAADCoT7G/AAAAgJGzjL8AAAAcGjanvwAAAHC43pk/AAAAqH/5tD8AAACgLjiwvwAAALywBaE/AAAAoFftq78AAABwCxegvwAAAADmOla/AAAA5PeMtr8AAACAEOyRvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "go",
      "troops"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But a couple of people have said the same thing as you, where they said did I say that and I said that that’s a number that I heard would be needed",
    "question": " If they said that, would you go along with that and send the troops?",
    "question_vector": "AAAALGZXvT8AAADoQ+uzvwAAAEBSt7w/AAAA2BJOu78AAABwjiGyPwAAALA/3sK/AAAA4D4+sb8AAABYVmbAPwAAAIhyE7O/AAAoBi1txb8AAABUaRaovwAAADiJWLG/AAAAlCBjq78AAACg62ajvwAAAHAGm7c/AAAAlBLqqT8AAACwIfq2PwAAANL5/pu/AAAAnPSLrL8AAABM/MOyvwAAAIDwZXG/AAAAEBgKrj8AAABAROKqPwAAAIA5IYs/AAAAwPzgkz8AAADA3KHTvwAAAOAjaJK/AAAA8Ak7p78AAAAAb2+9PwAAAGDBJq2/AAAAkBO+4j8AAADYz6/APwAAAEDNT8m/AAAAcBfclz8AAAAwYwNpPwAAAF6/BLI/AAAAAKAeVz8AAADU9h6mvwAAADCoT7G/AAAAgJGzjL8AAAAcGjanvwAAAHC43pk/AAAAqH/5tD8AAACgLjiwvwAAALywBaE/AAAAoFftq78AAABwCxegvwAAAADmOla/AAAA5PeMtr8AAACAEOyRvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "go",
      "troops"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I would find it very, very hard to send that many troops to take care of it",
    "question": " If they said that, would you go along with that and send the troops?",
    "question_vector": "AAAALGZXvT8AAADoQ+uzvwAAAEBSt7w/AAAA2BJOu78AAABwjiGyPwAAALA/3sK/AAAA4D4+sb8AAABYVmbAPwAAAIhyE7O/AAAoBi1txb8AAABUaRaovwAAADiJWLG/AAAAlCBjq78AAACg62ajvwAAAHAGm7c/AAAAlBLqqT8AAACwIfq2PwAAANL5/pu/AAAAnPSLrL8AAABM/MOyvwAAAIDwZXG/AAAAEBgKrj8AAABAROKqPwAAAIA5IYs/AAAAwPzgkz8AAADA3KHTvwAAAOAjaJK/AAAA8Ak7p78AAAAAb2+9PwAAAGDBJq2/AAAAkBO+4j8AAADYz6/APwAAAEDNT8m/AAAAcBfclz8AAAAwYwNpPwAAAF6/BLI/AAAAAKAeVz8AAADU9h6mvwAAADCoT7G/AAAAgJGzjL8AAAAcGjanvwAAAHC43pk/AAAAqH/5tD8AAACgLjiwvwAAALywBaE/AAAAoFftq78AAABwCxegvwAAAADmOla/AAAA5PeMtr8AAACAEOyRvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "go",
      "troops"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I would say this, I would put tremendous pressure on other countries that are over there to use their troops and I’d give them tremendous air supporters and support , because we have to get rid of ISIS, okay, just so — we have to get rid of ISIS",
    "question": " If they said that, would you go along with that and send the troops?",
    "question_vector": "AAAALGZXvT8AAADoQ+uzvwAAAEBSt7w/AAAA2BJOu78AAABwjiGyPwAAALA/3sK/AAAA4D4+sb8AAABYVmbAPwAAAIhyE7O/AAAoBi1txb8AAABUaRaovwAAADiJWLG/AAAAlCBjq78AAACg62ajvwAAAHAGm7c/AAAAlBLqqT8AAACwIfq2PwAAANL5/pu/AAAAnPSLrL8AAABM/MOyvwAAAIDwZXG/AAAAEBgKrj8AAABAROKqPwAAAIA5IYs/AAAAwPzgkz8AAADA3KHTvwAAAOAjaJK/AAAA8Ak7p78AAAAAb2+9PwAAAGDBJq2/AAAAkBO+4j8AAADYz6/APwAAAEDNT8m/AAAAcBfclz8AAAAwYwNpPwAAAF6/BLI/AAAAAKAeVz8AAADU9h6mvwAAADCoT7G/AAAAgJGzjL8AAAAcGjanvwAAAHC43pk/AAAAqH/5tD8AAACgLjiwvwAAALywBaE/AAAAoFftq78AAABwCxegvwAAAADmOla/AAAA5PeMtr8AAACAEOyRvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "go",
      "troops"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I would get other countries to become very much involved",
    "question": " If they said that, would you go along with that and send the troops?",
    "question_vector": "AAAALGZXvT8AAADoQ+uzvwAAAEBSt7w/AAAA2BJOu78AAABwjiGyPwAAALA/3sK/AAAA4D4+sb8AAABYVmbAPwAAAIhyE7O/AAAoBi1txb8AAABUaRaovwAAADiJWLG/AAAAlCBjq78AAACg62ajvwAAAHAGm7c/AAAAlBLqqT8AAACwIfq2PwAAANL5/pu/AAAAnPSLrL8AAABM/MOyvwAAAIDwZXG/AAAAEBgKrj8AAABAROKqPwAAAIA5IYs/AAAAwPzgkz8AAADA3KHTvwAAAOAjaJK/AAAA8Ak7p78AAAAAb2+9PwAAAGDBJq2/AAAAkBO+4j8AAADYz6/APwAAAEDNT8m/AAAAcBfclz8AAAAwYwNpPwAAAF6/BLI/AAAAAKAeVz8AAADU9h6mvwAAADCoT7G/AAAAgJGzjL8AAAAcGjanvwAAAHC43pk/AAAAqH/5tD8AAACgLjiwvwAAALywBaE/AAAAoFftq78AAABwCxegvwAAAADmOla/AAAA5PeMtr8AAACAEOyRvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "go",
      "troops"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No I didn’t, oh no no no, okay, I know what you’re saying",
    "question": " And could I ask you about ISIS, speaking of making commitments, because you talked recently about possibly sending 20 or 30,000 troops and—",
    "question_vector": "AAAAU/owtj8AAADY222zP6uqqgqAP5A/q6qqWqX1tb8AAACwNz+wP6uqqoryDKm/AAAAAIB0jT9VVVX1wwGov1VVVWXhLbA/AAAA8Iwssj8AAADgn/6uPwAAAOBvvMo/AAAAEK4/p79VVVWVJ1t1PwAAAKBpoKE/AAAAIOf8vT9VVVWVvQ+WP6uqqspKgpm/q6qq0lznwz8AAACAhqqJPwAAAMC25LM/AAAA8PPLuT8AAAAwLcyvP1VVVbVLHbO/VVVVFUOzsD+rqqps7yfFv6uqqiq0WaC/q6qqFjy6qL8AAADQupu8vwAAAEDi2sG/VVVVpxa30z9VVVX1e8W6PwAAAIDZJ7u/AAAAMEsqlr+rqqr6SXmQvwAAAICTK6u/VVVVUf5wsz8AAAAgFK2+vwAAAABSbKC/q6qqyj+Cp7+rqqpKDIGkvwAAAIBsd72/AAAAgMbIpj8AAACAhbRGP6uqqmrYgpG/AAAAAN6oaT9VVVUVZUKqvwAAAAD86rU/VVVVbbxzmb9VVVVl1dqtvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "ask",
      "ISIS",
      "commitments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " There was a question asked to me",
    "question": " And could I ask you about ISIS, speaking of making commitments, because you talked recently about possibly sending 20 or 30,000 troops and—",
    "question_vector": "AAAAU/owtj8AAADY222zP6uqqgqAP5A/q6qqWqX1tb8AAACwNz+wP6uqqoryDKm/AAAAAIB0jT9VVVX1wwGov1VVVWXhLbA/AAAA8Iwssj8AAADgn/6uPwAAAOBvvMo/AAAAEK4/p79VVVWVJ1t1PwAAAKBpoKE/AAAAIOf8vT9VVVWVvQ+WP6uqqspKgpm/q6qq0lznwz8AAACAhqqJPwAAAMC25LM/AAAA8PPLuT8AAAAwLcyvP1VVVbVLHbO/VVVVFUOzsD+rqqps7yfFv6uqqiq0WaC/q6qqFjy6qL8AAADQupu8vwAAAEDi2sG/VVVVpxa30z9VVVX1e8W6PwAAAIDZJ7u/AAAAMEsqlr+rqqr6SXmQvwAAAICTK6u/VVVVUf5wsz8AAAAgFK2+vwAAAABSbKC/q6qqyj+Cp7+rqqpKDIGkvwAAAIBsd72/AAAAgMbIpj8AAACAhbRGP6uqqmrYgpG/AAAAAN6oaT9VVVUVZUKqvwAAAAD86rU/VVVVbbxzmb9VVVVl1dqtvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "ask",
      "ISIS",
      "commitments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I said that the military, the generals have said that 20- to 30,000",
    "question": " And could I ask you about ISIS, speaking of making commitments, because you talked recently about possibly sending 20 or 30,000 troops and—",
    "question_vector": "AAAAU/owtj8AAADY222zP6uqqgqAP5A/q6qqWqX1tb8AAACwNz+wP6uqqoryDKm/AAAAAIB0jT9VVVX1wwGov1VVVWXhLbA/AAAA8Iwssj8AAADgn/6uPwAAAOBvvMo/AAAAEK4/p79VVVWVJ1t1PwAAAKBpoKE/AAAAIOf8vT9VVVWVvQ+WP6uqqspKgpm/q6qq0lznwz8AAACAhqqJPwAAAMC25LM/AAAA8PPLuT8AAAAwLcyvP1VVVbVLHbO/VVVVFUOzsD+rqqps7yfFv6uqqiq0WaC/q6qqFjy6qL8AAADQupu8vwAAAEDi2sG/VVVVpxa30z9VVVX1e8W6PwAAAIDZJ7u/AAAAMEsqlr+rqqr6SXmQvwAAAICTK6u/VVVVUf5wsz8AAAAgFK2+vwAAAABSbKC/q6qqyj+Cp7+rqqpKDIGkvwAAAIBsd72/AAAAgMbIpj8AAACAhbRGP6uqqmrYgpG/AAAAAN6oaT9VVVUVZUKqvwAAAAD86rU/VVVVbbxzmb9VVVVl1dqtvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "ask",
      "ISIS",
      "commitments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They said, would you send troops? I didn’t say send 20,000",
    "question": " And could I ask you about ISIS, speaking of making commitments, because you talked recently about possibly sending 20 or 30,000 troops and—",
    "question_vector": "AAAAU/owtj8AAADY222zP6uqqgqAP5A/q6qqWqX1tb8AAACwNz+wP6uqqoryDKm/AAAAAIB0jT9VVVX1wwGov1VVVWXhLbA/AAAA8Iwssj8AAADgn/6uPwAAAOBvvMo/AAAAEK4/p79VVVWVJ1t1PwAAAKBpoKE/AAAAIOf8vT9VVVWVvQ+WP6uqqspKgpm/q6qq0lznwz8AAACAhqqJPwAAAMC25LM/AAAA8PPLuT8AAAAwLcyvP1VVVbVLHbO/VVVVFUOzsD+rqqps7yfFv6uqqiq0WaC/q6qqFjy6qL8AAADQupu8vwAAAEDi2sG/VVVVpxa30z9VVVX1e8W6PwAAAIDZJ7u/AAAAMEsqlr+rqqr6SXmQvwAAAICTK6u/VVVVUf5wsz8AAAAgFK2+vwAAAABSbKC/q6qqyj+Cp7+rqqpKDIGkvwAAAIBsd72/AAAAgMbIpj8AAACAhbRGP6uqqmrYgpG/AAAAAN6oaT9VVVUVZUKqvwAAAAD86rU/VVVVbbxzmb9VVVVl1dqtvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "ask",
      "ISIS",
      "commitments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I said, well the generals are saying you’d need because they , what would it take to wipe out ISIS, I said pretty much exactly this, I said the generals, the military is saying you would need 20- to 30,000 troops, but I didn’t say that I would send them",
    "question": " And could I ask you about ISIS, speaking of making commitments, because you talked recently about possibly sending 20 or 30,000 troops and—",
    "question_vector": "AAAAU/owtj8AAADY222zP6uqqgqAP5A/q6qqWqX1tb8AAACwNz+wP6uqqoryDKm/AAAAAIB0jT9VVVX1wwGov1VVVWXhLbA/AAAA8Iwssj8AAADgn/6uPwAAAOBvvMo/AAAAEK4/p79VVVWVJ1t1PwAAAKBpoKE/AAAAIOf8vT9VVVWVvQ+WP6uqqspKgpm/q6qq0lznwz8AAACAhqqJPwAAAMC25LM/AAAA8PPLuT8AAAAwLcyvP1VVVbVLHbO/VVVVFUOzsD+rqqps7yfFv6uqqiq0WaC/q6qqFjy6qL8AAADQupu8vwAAAEDi2sG/VVVVpxa30z9VVVX1e8W6PwAAAIDZJ7u/AAAAMEsqlr+rqqr6SXmQvwAAAICTK6u/VVVVUf5wsz8AAAAgFK2+vwAAAABSbKC/q6qqyj+Cp7+rqqpKDIGkvwAAAIBsd72/AAAAgMbIpj8AAACAhbRGP6uqqmrYgpG/AAAAAN6oaT9VVVUVZUKqvwAAAAD86rU/VVVVbbxzmb9VVVVl1dqtvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "ask",
      "ISIS",
      "commitments"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think the answer is yes, it was, but I don’t see other people doing much about it",
    "question": " About Ukraine, was it right for the United States to impose sanctions on Russia when they invaded Crimea and would you keep those sanctions on them?",
    "question_vector": "AACARtOQl78AAAB//VGwPwAAABiKiaQ/AAAAIOoqoD8AAACAizCqvwAAAHULUrE/AAAAED42uz8AAEC5Rd69PwAAAIA1coG/AACAfRtwk78AAAA2cFq0PwAAAMT0LbG/AAAAYINjd78AACBVvXmoPwAAABTPdLM/AAAAip9Xqz8AAABYf+iiPwAAACC2Iq+/AAAAwfUbsT8AAAAIEj6qPwAAALjlF7A/AAAAEZd4u78AAABQ0eCWPwAAAK7kjay/AAAAiJOMlr8AAABwF0/YvwAAAFA6DL0/AAAAeLi6gb8AAID4k9GwPwAAAFzQoaU/AAAA8Ne33T8AAABsK/WqPwAAANT+iLi/AAAAYCy/p78AAABERBbAvwAAwOSVYrW/AAAAAPdxpr8AAAD0T7K4PwAAAIzUbcG/AADA616ilb8AAAAQDyCfvwAAALi8VJO/AAAAVH1c0j8AAADkub7JvwAAANA/Yp6/AAAAiO8bwj8AAACoG+/BvwAAAF5e7cI/AAAAhmJeu78AAACQjoqwvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Ukraine",
      "States",
      "sanctions",
      "Russia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I see us doing things about it, but I don’t see other people doing much about it",
    "question": " About Ukraine, was it right for the United States to impose sanctions on Russia when they invaded Crimea and would you keep those sanctions on them?",
    "question_vector": "AACARtOQl78AAAB//VGwPwAAABiKiaQ/AAAAIOoqoD8AAACAizCqvwAAAHULUrE/AAAAED42uz8AAEC5Rd69PwAAAIA1coG/AACAfRtwk78AAAA2cFq0PwAAAMT0LbG/AAAAYINjd78AACBVvXmoPwAAABTPdLM/AAAAip9Xqz8AAABYf+iiPwAAACC2Iq+/AAAAwfUbsT8AAAAIEj6qPwAAALjlF7A/AAAAEZd4u78AAABQ0eCWPwAAAK7kjay/AAAAiJOMlr8AAABwF0/YvwAAAFA6DL0/AAAAeLi6gb8AAID4k9GwPwAAAFzQoaU/AAAA8Ne33T8AAABsK/WqPwAAANT+iLi/AAAAYCy/p78AAABERBbAvwAAwOSVYrW/AAAAAPdxpr8AAAD0T7K4PwAAAIzUbcG/AADA616ilb8AAAAQDyCfvwAAALi8VJO/AAAAVH1c0j8AAADkub7JvwAAANA/Yp6/AAAAiO8bwj8AAACoG+/BvwAAAF5e7cI/AAAAhmJeu78AAACQjoqwvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Ukraine",
      "States",
      "sanctions",
      "Russia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Billions",
    "question": " Hundreds of billions?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA8NlBzz8AAACw+Eu0vwAAAGB9jc8/AAAA0ArbuL8AAADYsVOlvwAAAEAL84m/AAAA5gWltL8AAAAQ/t6UPwAAAGgNO6A/AAAA9+pLsj8AAABAKrrAvwAAAIA9vKC/AAAAgBNvvD8AAACgLYKmvwAAAACLVsQ/AAAAOJqIrr8AAACIr3qrPwAAANNoPZ8/AAAAwIMThb8AAADQER+4vwAAAIhQfsU/AAAAAN4Qkb8AAACwJY+mPwAAALgWbMG/AAAA4AoioL8AAADAzLDNvwAAAHjaA5A/AAAAMNI5p78AAADUMfugPwAAAMi8x7K/AAAA+I9r4D8AAAAQ3ZG+PwAAAFiHNZ0/AAAAoBQklb8AAAA4x4y/vwAAAKgBk8E/AAAAzN0Lvr8AAECMD0WxvwAAABCiBqk/AAAA4Gvzrb8AAAC45lSwvwAAAOx8Dac/AAAAME31wz8AAABgNTixPwAAAABm9HG/AAAAEBcVlr8AAACgLSDFvwAAADC+b6Y/AAAAMEvUvr8AAACw78LKvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Hundreds",
      "billions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well if you look at Germany, if you look at Saudi Arabia, if you look at Japan, if you look at South Korea  — I mean we spend billions of dollars on Saudi Arabia, and they have nothing but money",
    "question": " Hundreds of billions?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA8NlBzz8AAACw+Eu0vwAAAGB9jc8/AAAA0ArbuL8AAADYsVOlvwAAAEAL84m/AAAA5gWltL8AAAAQ/t6UPwAAAGgNO6A/AAAA9+pLsj8AAABAKrrAvwAAAIA9vKC/AAAAgBNvvD8AAACgLYKmvwAAAACLVsQ/AAAAOJqIrr8AAACIr3qrPwAAANNoPZ8/AAAAwIMThb8AAADQER+4vwAAAIhQfsU/AAAAAN4Qkb8AAACwJY+mPwAAALgWbMG/AAAA4AoioL8AAADAzLDNvwAAAHjaA5A/AAAAMNI5p78AAADUMfugPwAAAMi8x7K/AAAA+I9r4D8AAAAQ3ZG+PwAAAFiHNZ0/AAAAoBQklb8AAAA4x4y/vwAAAKgBk8E/AAAAzN0Lvr8AAECMD0WxvwAAABCiBqk/AAAA4Gvzrb8AAAC45lSwvwAAAOx8Dac/AAAAME31wz8AAABgNTixPwAAAABm9HG/AAAAEBcVlr8AAACgLSDFvwAAADC+b6Y/AAAAMEvUvr8AAACw78LKvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Hundreds",
      "billions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I say, why? Now I would go in and I would structure a much different deal with them, and it would be a much better deal",
    "question": " Hundreds of billions?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA8NlBzz8AAACw+Eu0vwAAAGB9jc8/AAAA0ArbuL8AAADYsVOlvwAAAEAL84m/AAAA5gWltL8AAAAQ/t6UPwAAAGgNO6A/AAAA9+pLsj8AAABAKrrAvwAAAIA9vKC/AAAAgBNvvD8AAACgLYKmvwAAAACLVsQ/AAAAOJqIrr8AAACIr3qrPwAAANNoPZ8/AAAAwIMThb8AAADQER+4vwAAAIhQfsU/AAAAAN4Qkb8AAACwJY+mPwAAALgWbMG/AAAA4AoioL8AAADAzLDNvwAAAHjaA5A/AAAAMNI5p78AAADUMfugPwAAAMi8x7K/AAAA+I9r4D8AAAAQ3ZG+PwAAAFiHNZ0/AAAAoBQklb8AAAA4x4y/vwAAAKgBk8E/AAAAzN0Lvr8AAECMD0WxvwAAABCiBqk/AAAA4Gvzrb8AAAC45lSwvwAAAOx8Dac/AAAAME31wz8AAABgNTixPwAAAABm9HG/AAAAEBcVlr8AAACgLSDFvwAAADC+b6Y/AAAAMEvUvr8AAACw78LKvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Hundreds",
      "billions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " When you look at the kind of money that our country is losing, we can’t afford to do this",
    "question": " Hundreds of billions?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA8NlBzz8AAACw+Eu0vwAAAGB9jc8/AAAA0ArbuL8AAADYsVOlvwAAAEAL84m/AAAA5gWltL8AAAAQ/t6UPwAAAGgNO6A/AAAA9+pLsj8AAABAKrrAvwAAAIA9vKC/AAAAgBNvvD8AAACgLYKmvwAAAACLVsQ/AAAAOJqIrr8AAACIr3qrPwAAANNoPZ8/AAAAwIMThb8AAADQER+4vwAAAIhQfsU/AAAAAN4Qkb8AAACwJY+mPwAAALgWbMG/AAAA4AoioL8AAADAzLDNvwAAAHjaA5A/AAAAMNI5p78AAADUMfugPwAAAMi8x7K/AAAA+I9r4D8AAAAQ3ZG+PwAAAFiHNZ0/AAAAoBQklb8AAAA4x4y/vwAAAKgBk8E/AAAAzN0Lvr8AAECMD0WxvwAAABCiBqk/AAAA4Gvzrb8AAAC45lSwvwAAAOx8Dac/AAAAME31wz8AAABgNTixPwAAAABm9HG/AAAAEBcVlr8AAACgLSDFvwAAADC+b6Y/AAAAMEvUvr8AAACw78LKvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Hundreds",
      "billions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Certainly we can’t afford to do it anymore",
    "question": " Hundreds of billions?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA8NlBzz8AAACw+Eu0vwAAAGB9jc8/AAAA0ArbuL8AAADYsVOlvwAAAEAL84m/AAAA5gWltL8AAAAQ/t6UPwAAAGgNO6A/AAAA9+pLsj8AAABAKrrAvwAAAIA9vKC/AAAAgBNvvD8AAACgLYKmvwAAAACLVsQ/AAAAOJqIrr8AAACIr3qrPwAAANNoPZ8/AAAAwIMThb8AAADQER+4vwAAAIhQfsU/AAAAAN4Qkb8AAACwJY+mPwAAALgWbMG/AAAA4AoioL8AAADAzLDNvwAAAHjaA5A/AAAAMNI5p78AAADUMfugPwAAAMi8x7K/AAAA+I9r4D8AAAAQ3ZG+PwAAAFiHNZ0/AAAAoBQklb8AAAA4x4y/vwAAAKgBk8E/AAAAzN0Lvr8AAECMD0WxvwAAABCiBqk/AAAA4Gvzrb8AAAC45lSwvwAAAOx8Dac/AAAAME31wz8AAABgNTixPwAAAABm9HG/AAAAEBcVlr8AAACgLSDFvwAAADC+b6Y/AAAAMEvUvr8AAACw78LKvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Hundreds",
      "billions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Look, I see NATO as a good thing to have – I look at the Ukraine situation and I say, so Ukraine is a country that affects us far less than it affects other countries in NATO, and yet we are doing all of the lifting, they’re not doing anything",
    "question": " Back to foreign policy a little bit, can you talk a little bit about what you see as the future of NATO? Should it expand in any way?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA8F9Upb8AAAA41EaivwAAAExdzq2/AAAArPdEtr8AAAC8hAqoPwAAAG9TsaW/AAAAAucior8AAADAqaCIvwAAADjCB76/AAAAIJBxqj8AAACIwt6zvwAAAEBjt6w/AAAASJTjsr8AAABsz7akPwAAANxiaLQ/AAAAPCnvuj8AAAAAcwuVPwAAAAAo4k4/AAAAgFX+oT8AAAAc1H+9vwAAAODYrpO/AAAAbH76tT8AAADQm+mqPwAAAACxzqA/AAAADBLCwj8AAAAgwEfVvwAAAFTMrq2/AAAAji1Jwj8AAAA+aFTEPwAAAKD5MoE/AAAAyFbc4j8AAICD4COxPwAAAMC/wpA/AAAA9PZisL8AAAAihXazvwAAAAD9MK+/AAAAuA+Zsb8AAABokwmWPwAAAJB0LqO/AAAAiNFiwr8AAIDjb3WfvwAAAGgUUKQ/AAAAoMulqr8AAAAUj3K5PwAAAOJJwKE/AAAAUIW9jb8AAEA5Zju1PwAAAKwIIrc/AAAAACiDLr8AAADwo4jGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "talk",
      "bit",
      "policy",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I say, why is it that Germany is not dealing with NATO on Ukraine? Why is it that other countries that are in the vicinity of the Ukraine not dealing with — why are we always the one that’s leading, potentially the third world war, okay, with Russia? Why are we always the ones that are doing it? And I think the concept of NATO is good, but I do think the United States has to have some help",
    "question": " Back to foreign policy a little bit, can you talk a little bit about what you see as the future of NATO? Should it expand in any way?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA8F9Upb8AAAA41EaivwAAAExdzq2/AAAArPdEtr8AAAC8hAqoPwAAAG9TsaW/AAAAAucior8AAADAqaCIvwAAADjCB76/AAAAIJBxqj8AAACIwt6zvwAAAEBjt6w/AAAASJTjsr8AAABsz7akPwAAANxiaLQ/AAAAPCnvuj8AAAAAcwuVPwAAAAAo4k4/AAAAgFX+oT8AAAAc1H+9vwAAAODYrpO/AAAAbH76tT8AAADQm+mqPwAAAACxzqA/AAAADBLCwj8AAAAgwEfVvwAAAFTMrq2/AAAAji1Jwj8AAAA+aFTEPwAAAKD5MoE/AAAAyFbc4j8AAICD4COxPwAAAMC/wpA/AAAA9PZisL8AAAAihXazvwAAAAD9MK+/AAAAuA+Zsb8AAABokwmWPwAAAJB0LqO/AAAAiNFiwr8AAIDjb3WfvwAAAGgUUKQ/AAAAoMulqr8AAAAUj3K5PwAAAOJJwKE/AAAAUIW9jb8AAEA5Zju1PwAAAKwIIrc/AAAAACiDLr8AAADwo4jGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "talk",
      "bit",
      "policy",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We are not helped",
    "question": " Back to foreign policy a little bit, can you talk a little bit about what you see as the future of NATO? Should it expand in any way?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA8F9Upb8AAAA41EaivwAAAExdzq2/AAAArPdEtr8AAAC8hAqoPwAAAG9TsaW/AAAAAucior8AAADAqaCIvwAAADjCB76/AAAAIJBxqj8AAACIwt6zvwAAAEBjt6w/AAAASJTjsr8AAABsz7akPwAAANxiaLQ/AAAAPCnvuj8AAAAAcwuVPwAAAAAo4k4/AAAAgFX+oT8AAAAc1H+9vwAAAODYrpO/AAAAbH76tT8AAADQm+mqPwAAAACxzqA/AAAADBLCwj8AAAAgwEfVvwAAAFTMrq2/AAAAji1Jwj8AAAA+aFTEPwAAAKD5MoE/AAAAyFbc4j8AAICD4COxPwAAAMC/wpA/AAAA9PZisL8AAAAihXazvwAAAAD9MK+/AAAAuA+Zsb8AAABokwmWPwAAAJB0LqO/AAAAiNFiwr8AAIDjb3WfvwAAAGgUUKQ/AAAAoMulqr8AAAAUj3K5PwAAAOJJwKE/AAAAUIW9jb8AAEA5Zju1PwAAAKwIIrc/AAAAACiDLr8AAADwo4jGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "talk",
      "bit",
      "policy",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’ll give you a better example than that",
    "question": " Back to foreign policy a little bit, can you talk a little bit about what you see as the future of NATO? Should it expand in any way?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA8F9Upb8AAAA41EaivwAAAExdzq2/AAAArPdEtr8AAAC8hAqoPwAAAG9TsaW/AAAAAucior8AAADAqaCIvwAAADjCB76/AAAAIJBxqj8AAACIwt6zvwAAAEBjt6w/AAAASJTjsr8AAABsz7akPwAAANxiaLQ/AAAAPCnvuj8AAAAAcwuVPwAAAAAo4k4/AAAAgFX+oT8AAAAc1H+9vwAAAODYrpO/AAAAbH76tT8AAADQm+mqPwAAAACxzqA/AAAADBLCwj8AAAAgwEfVvwAAAFTMrq2/AAAAji1Jwj8AAAA+aFTEPwAAAKD5MoE/AAAAyFbc4j8AAICD4COxPwAAAMC/wpA/AAAA9PZisL8AAAAihXazvwAAAAD9MK+/AAAAuA+Zsb8AAABokwmWPwAAAJB0LqO/AAAAiNFiwr8AAIDjb3WfvwAAAGgUUKQ/AAAAoMulqr8AAAAUj3K5PwAAAOJJwKE/AAAAUIW9jb8AAEA5Zju1PwAAAKwIIrc/AAAAACiDLr8AAADwo4jGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "talk",
      "bit",
      "policy",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean, we pay billions– hundreds of billions of dollars to supporting other countries that are in theory wealthier than we are",
    "question": " Back to foreign policy a little bit, can you talk a little bit about what you see as the future of NATO? Should it expand in any way?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA8F9Upb8AAAA41EaivwAAAExdzq2/AAAArPdEtr8AAAC8hAqoPwAAAG9TsaW/AAAAAucior8AAADAqaCIvwAAADjCB76/AAAAIJBxqj8AAACIwt6zvwAAAEBjt6w/AAAASJTjsr8AAABsz7akPwAAANxiaLQ/AAAAPCnvuj8AAAAAcwuVPwAAAAAo4k4/AAAAgFX+oT8AAAAc1H+9vwAAAODYrpO/AAAAbH76tT8AAADQm+mqPwAAAACxzqA/AAAADBLCwj8AAAAgwEfVvwAAAFTMrq2/AAAAji1Jwj8AAAA+aFTEPwAAAKD5MoE/AAAAyFbc4j8AAICD4COxPwAAAMC/wpA/AAAA9PZisL8AAAAihXazvwAAAAD9MK+/AAAAuA+Zsb8AAABokwmWPwAAAJB0LqO/AAAAiNFiwr8AAIDjb3WfvwAAAGgUUKQ/AAAAoMulqr8AAAAUj3K5PwAAAOJJwKE/AAAAUIW9jb8AAEA5Zju1PwAAAKwIIrc/AAAAACiDLr8AAADwo4jGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "talk",
      "bit",
      "policy",
      "bit"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I want to make it more fair from the side where I am, because things are said that are libelous, things are said about me that are so egregious and so wrong, and right now according to the libel laws I can do almost nothing about it because I’m a well-known person you know, etc",
    "question": " The reason I keep asking this is because you’ve  said three times you’ve said we are going to open up the libel laws and when we ask you what you mean you say hatred, or bad–",
    "question_vector": "AAAA8Jmmnr8AAADAQQ6PPwAAAAcfZ7a/AAAAEH+Iqb8AAACY+TayPwAAABEZZL8/AABwSeSnrT8AAADcHCywvwAAAABl13y/AAAAOCrjsD8AAAB8vlCSPwAAADCBTqs/AAAAZ8Rtp78AAAC0CbO/vwAAAPy5MLU/AAAAHC8vrz8AAADEUEasPwAAANBllJO/AAAAHg9alD8AAAAyTMOmvwAAAICr3pK/AAAASKIyc78AAACulPiVPwAAABCyL6I/AAAAeHKJoT8AAACwXxfYvwAAAKBLyKq/AAAA4OJPeb8AAIDGKjfDPwAAALCfqXw/AAAADCsW4D8AAACAtHNlPwAAAGS3K7m/AAAAPO3CyL8AAAAUWiS2vwAAAGAO77W/AAAAbOOUor8AAAAwPsa2vwAAAPhzCKG/AAAAYAQimj8AAABf3YKhvwAAAACWzB6/AAAAsPsznD8AAAB03Xe/PwAAAAAA4/S+AAAACHVWmj8AAADmEOCxvwAAADMYOqE/AAAAPLqJpD8AAACAR0hnvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "reason",
      "laws",
      "hatred"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": ", etc",
    "question": " The reason I keep asking this is because you’ve  said three times you’ve said we are going to open up the libel laws and when we ask you what you mean you say hatred, or bad–",
    "question_vector": "AAAA8Jmmnr8AAADAQQ6PPwAAAAcfZ7a/AAAAEH+Iqb8AAACY+TayPwAAABEZZL8/AABwSeSnrT8AAADcHCywvwAAAABl13y/AAAAOCrjsD8AAAB8vlCSPwAAADCBTqs/AAAAZ8Rtp78AAAC0CbO/vwAAAPy5MLU/AAAAHC8vrz8AAADEUEasPwAAANBllJO/AAAAHg9alD8AAAAyTMOmvwAAAICr3pK/AAAASKIyc78AAACulPiVPwAAABCyL6I/AAAAeHKJoT8AAACwXxfYvwAAAKBLyKq/AAAA4OJPeb8AAIDGKjfDPwAAALCfqXw/AAAADCsW4D8AAACAtHNlPwAAAGS3K7m/AAAAPO3CyL8AAAAUWiS2vwAAAGAO77W/AAAAbOOUor8AAAAwPsa2vwAAAPhzCKG/AAAAYAQimj8AAABf3YKhvwAAAACWzB6/AAAAsPsznD8AAAB03Xe/PwAAAAAA4/S+AAAACHVWmj8AAADmEOCxvwAAADMYOqE/AAAAPLqJpD8AAACAR0hnvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "reason",
      "laws",
      "hatred"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean, The Washington Post never calls me",
    "question": " Wrong whether there’s malice or not?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgOpnhj8AAACArci2PwAAAOD2Fr6/AAAAgDFpuL8AAAAAR1GyPwAAAEC/d80/AAAAgIbD1z8AAACAkTyBPwAAAMBfi6e/AAAA4KHZxT8AAAAAwbiNvwAAAKA49sU/AAAAIJaAy78AAADg+p7SvwAAAMA6DHq/AAAAAPdzgr8AAAAAXaW8PwAAAIC+cpc/AAAAQCd1lL8AAAAgPC65vwAAAICrn6Q/AAAAoHkgyD8AAABgQnvDPwAAAADF9bm/AAAAgADuor8AAACgrqKuvwAAAIBth8O/AAAAgMqqxT8AAABA93DRPwAAAMCgq6e/AAAAYMZop78AAACA9RWdvwAAAEBVWKi/AAAAAJHHyr8AAADglteoPwAAAEDxEbK/AAAAQJwzwT8AAADAHpDRvwAAAGDQn7u/AAAAgFaItb8AAACgadm1PwAAACBgj8W/AAAAwEXWjL8AAADAbwmpPwAAAMBYocG/AAAAoKiD0b8AAAAgLrm0vwAAAMD8Eri/AAAAYOaryD8AAABgt0Whvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "malice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I never had a call, “Why – why did you do this?” or “Why did you do that?” It’s just, you know, like I’m this horrible human being",
    "question": " Wrong whether there’s malice or not?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgOpnhj8AAACArci2PwAAAOD2Fr6/AAAAgDFpuL8AAAAAR1GyPwAAAEC/d80/AAAAgIbD1z8AAACAkTyBPwAAAMBfi6e/AAAA4KHZxT8AAAAAwbiNvwAAAKA49sU/AAAAIJaAy78AAADg+p7SvwAAAMA6DHq/AAAAAPdzgr8AAAAAXaW8PwAAAIC+cpc/AAAAQCd1lL8AAAAgPC65vwAAAICrn6Q/AAAAoHkgyD8AAABgQnvDPwAAAADF9bm/AAAAgADuor8AAACgrqKuvwAAAIBth8O/AAAAgMqqxT8AAABA93DRPwAAAMCgq6e/AAAAYMZop78AAACA9RWdvwAAAEBVWKi/AAAAAJHHyr8AAADglteoPwAAAEDxEbK/AAAAQJwzwT8AAADAHpDRvwAAAGDQn7u/AAAAgFaItb8AAACgadm1PwAAACBgj8W/AAAAwEXWjL8AAADAbwmpPwAAAMBYocG/AAAAoKiD0b8AAAAgLrm0vwAAAMD8Eri/AAAAYOaryD8AAABgt0Whvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "malice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I’m not",
    "question": " Wrong whether there’s malice or not?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgOpnhj8AAACArci2PwAAAOD2Fr6/AAAAgDFpuL8AAAAAR1GyPwAAAEC/d80/AAAAgIbD1z8AAACAkTyBPwAAAMBfi6e/AAAA4KHZxT8AAAAAwbiNvwAAAKA49sU/AAAAIJaAy78AAADg+p7SvwAAAMA6DHq/AAAAAPdzgr8AAAAAXaW8PwAAAIC+cpc/AAAAQCd1lL8AAAAgPC65vwAAAICrn6Q/AAAAoHkgyD8AAABgQnvDPwAAAADF9bm/AAAAgADuor8AAACgrqKuvwAAAIBth8O/AAAAgMqqxT8AAABA93DRPwAAAMCgq6e/AAAAYMZop78AAACA9RWdvwAAAEBVWKi/AAAAAJHHyr8AAADglteoPwAAAEDxEbK/AAAAQJwzwT8AAADAHpDRvwAAAGDQn7u/AAAAgFaItb8AAACgadm1PwAAACBgj8W/AAAAwEXWjL8AAADAbwmpPwAAAMBYocG/AAAAoKiD0b8AAAAgLrm0vwAAAMD8Eri/AAAAYOaryD8AAABgt0Whvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "malice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You know, the one thing we have in common I think we all love the country",
    "question": " Wrong whether there’s malice or not?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgOpnhj8AAACArci2PwAAAOD2Fr6/AAAAgDFpuL8AAAAAR1GyPwAAAEC/d80/AAAAgIbD1z8AAACAkTyBPwAAAMBfi6e/AAAA4KHZxT8AAAAAwbiNvwAAAKA49sU/AAAAIJaAy78AAADg+p7SvwAAAMA6DHq/AAAAAPdzgr8AAAAAXaW8PwAAAIC+cpc/AAAAQCd1lL8AAAAgPC65vwAAAICrn6Q/AAAAoHkgyD8AAABgQnvDPwAAAADF9bm/AAAAgADuor8AAACgrqKuvwAAAIBth8O/AAAAgMqqxT8AAABA93DRPwAAAMCgq6e/AAAAYMZop78AAACA9RWdvwAAAEBVWKi/AAAAAJHHyr8AAADglteoPwAAAEDxEbK/AAAAQJwzwT8AAADAHpDRvwAAAGDQn7u/AAAAgFaItb8AAACgadm1PwAAACBgj8W/AAAAwEXWjL8AAADAbwmpPwAAAMBYocG/AAAAoKiD0b8AAAAgLrm0vwAAAMD8Eri/AAAAYOaryD8AAABgt0Whvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "malice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Now, maybe we come at it from different sides, but nobody ever calls me",
    "question": " Wrong whether there’s malice or not?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgOpnhj8AAACArci2PwAAAOD2Fr6/AAAAgDFpuL8AAAAAR1GyPwAAAEC/d80/AAAAgIbD1z8AAACAkTyBPwAAAMBfi6e/AAAA4KHZxT8AAAAAwbiNvwAAAKA49sU/AAAAIJaAy78AAADg+p7SvwAAAMA6DHq/AAAAAPdzgr8AAAAAXaW8PwAAAIC+cpc/AAAAQCd1lL8AAAAgPC65vwAAAICrn6Q/AAAAoHkgyD8AAABgQnvDPwAAAADF9bm/AAAAgADuor8AAACgrqKuvwAAAIBth8O/AAAAgMqqxT8AAABA93DRPwAAAMCgq6e/AAAAYMZop78AAACA9RWdvwAAAEBVWKi/AAAAAJHHyr8AAADglteoPwAAAEDxEbK/AAAAQJwzwT8AAADAHpDRvwAAAGDQn7u/AAAAgFaItb8AAACgadm1PwAAACBgj8W/AAAAwEXWjL8AAADAbwmpPwAAAMBYocG/AAAAoKiD0b8AAAAgLrm0vwAAAMD8Eri/AAAAYOaryD8AAABgt0Whvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "malice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean, Bob Costa calls about a political story – he called because we’re meeting senators in a little while and congressmen, supporters – but nobody ever calls",
    "question": " Wrong whether there’s malice or not?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgOpnhj8AAACArci2PwAAAOD2Fr6/AAAAgDFpuL8AAAAAR1GyPwAAAEC/d80/AAAAgIbD1z8AAACAkTyBPwAAAMBfi6e/AAAA4KHZxT8AAAAAwbiNvwAAAKA49sU/AAAAIJaAy78AAADg+p7SvwAAAMA6DHq/AAAAAPdzgr8AAAAAXaW8PwAAAIC+cpc/AAAAQCd1lL8AAAAgPC65vwAAAICrn6Q/AAAAoHkgyD8AAABgQnvDPwAAAADF9bm/AAAAgADuor8AAACgrqKuvwAAAIBth8O/AAAAgMqqxT8AAABA93DRPwAAAMCgq6e/AAAAYMZop78AAACA9RWdvwAAAEBVWKi/AAAAAJHHyr8AAADglteoPwAAAEDxEbK/AAAAQJwzwT8AAADAHpDRvwAAAGDQn7u/AAAAgFaItb8AAACgadm1PwAAACBgj8W/AAAAwEXWjL8AAADAbwmpPwAAAMBYocG/AAAAoKiD0b8AAAAgLrm0vwAAAMD8Eri/AAAAYOaryD8AAABgt0Whvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "malice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No, if it’s wrong",
    "question": " Would that be the standard then? If there is an article that you feel has hatred, or is bad, would that be the basis for libel?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAzMlvwb8AAAAYVAOgPwAAcAvnkLC/AAAA4BX/bT8AAACAJyZdvwAAAJQ2uMM/AAAARLGBuz8AAAAWPi/AvwAAAOi9YXi/AAAAMjEksD8AAAAA5QqtvwAAANAQfps/AAAA2Iidkb8AANDKHV28vwAAAJwznr0/AAAAEIEqqL8AAADpgX6zvwAAADCzxLG/AAAAr4ZKoL8AAADAx1+CvwAAALjMiLc/AAAARPwtmj8AAACastezPwAAACDLY5A/AAAAMPHPmb8AAACoG0LRvwAAALgEibO/AAAAQN0Kpb8AAID1vuiwPwAAADa/mKM/AAAAbhAN1j8AAADAnl+3vwAAAIVCVqe/AAAADFrctb8AAADAJve9vwAAAD4vZLK/AAAAkAeHpz8AAACEuca9vwAAAKh8WrS/AAAAwLQUjL8AAACQxTfEPwAAAPAUVZG/AAAAUMtXtD8AAABcoSXDPwAAANCbp4G/AAAAmJg5oz8AAAAAbtuyvwAAgLUNMLc/AAAA5NgcsD8AAACQy5WYvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "standard",
      "article",
      "hatred",
      "libel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " If it’s wrong",
    "question": " Would that be the standard then? If there is an article that you feel has hatred, or is bad, would that be the basis for libel?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAzMlvwb8AAAAYVAOgPwAAcAvnkLC/AAAA4BX/bT8AAACAJyZdvwAAAJQ2uMM/AAAARLGBuz8AAAAWPi/AvwAAAOi9YXi/AAAAMjEksD8AAAAA5QqtvwAAANAQfps/AAAA2Iidkb8AANDKHV28vwAAAJwznr0/AAAAEIEqqL8AAADpgX6zvwAAADCzxLG/AAAAr4ZKoL8AAADAx1+CvwAAALjMiLc/AAAARPwtmj8AAACastezPwAAACDLY5A/AAAAMPHPmb8AAACoG0LRvwAAALgEibO/AAAAQN0Kpb8AAID1vuiwPwAAADa/mKM/AAAAbhAN1j8AAADAnl+3vwAAAIVCVqe/AAAADFrctb8AAADAJve9vwAAAD4vZLK/AAAAkAeHpz8AAACEuca9vwAAAKh8WrS/AAAAwLQUjL8AAACQxTfEPwAAAPAUVZG/AAAAUMtXtD8AAABcoSXDPwAAANCbp4G/AAAAmJg5oz8AAAAAbtuyvwAAgLUNMLc/AAAA5NgcsD8AAACQy5WYvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "standard",
      "article",
      "hatred",
      "libel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’d have to get my lawyers in to tell you, but I would loosen them up",
    "question": " What does that mean?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIDKqj78AAACAskqxPwAAAGAQuqc/AAAAwLWKwb8AAACAlo25PwAAAMByLki/AAAAoI2nuT8AAACg9VuavwAAAEAMn6e/AAAAABPLuD8AAAAgeBmXvwAAAOB6gqA/AAAA4Jp2i78AAACAs1GwvwAAAABV2cg/AAAAAOwavz8AAABg3T7APwAAAEBj34+/AAAAgOWclr8AAABgp3/FvwAAAMArG7i/AAAAoEk3ub8AAACAkGixPwAAAID7MKM/AAAAQBxdvD8AAABAnN/TvwAAAIA1M8S/AAAAIFtYtD8AAACgEkzQPwAAAADbFIA/AAAAQE8I5j8AAACAdd7BPwAAAEBoray/AAAAgEMOm78AAABg+MKrvwAAAODnA8K/AAAAgL+epz8AAADAc1CovwAAAICr15C/AAAAQOVFp78AAAAge9a7vwAAAOCLlEm/AAAAQPUFpz8AAADgKRHDPwAAAIDRwLq/AAAA4NsEr78AAACAl5WkPwAAAAATzbM/AAAAAPlgfT8AAADAEe/DPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I would loosen them up",
    "question": " What does that mean?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIDKqj78AAACAskqxPwAAAGAQuqc/AAAAwLWKwb8AAACAlo25PwAAAMByLki/AAAAoI2nuT8AAACg9VuavwAAAEAMn6e/AAAAABPLuD8AAAAgeBmXvwAAAOB6gqA/AAAA4Jp2i78AAACAs1GwvwAAAABV2cg/AAAAAOwavz8AAABg3T7APwAAAEBj34+/AAAAgOWclr8AAABgp3/FvwAAAMArG7i/AAAAoEk3ub8AAACAkGixPwAAAID7MKM/AAAAQBxdvD8AAABAnN/TvwAAAIA1M8S/AAAAIFtYtD8AAACgEkzQPwAAAADbFIA/AAAAQE8I5j8AAACAdd7BPwAAAEBoray/AAAAgEMOm78AAABg+MKrvwAAAODnA8K/AAAAgL+epz8AAADAc1CovwAAAICr15C/AAAAQOVFp78AAAAge9a7vwAAAOCLlEm/AAAAQPUFpz8AAADgKRHDPwAAAIDRwLq/AAAA4NsEr78AAACAl5WkPwAAAAATzbM/AAAAAPlgfT8AAADAEe/DPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " If The Washington Post writes badly about me – and they do, they don’t write good – I mean, I don’t think I get – I read some of the stories coming up here, and I said to my staff, I said, “Why are we even wasting our time? The hatred is so enormous",
    "question": " What does that mean?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIDKqj78AAACAskqxPwAAAGAQuqc/AAAAwLWKwb8AAACAlo25PwAAAMByLki/AAAAoI2nuT8AAACg9VuavwAAAEAMn6e/AAAAABPLuD8AAAAgeBmXvwAAAOB6gqA/AAAA4Jp2i78AAACAs1GwvwAAAABV2cg/AAAAAOwavz8AAABg3T7APwAAAEBj34+/AAAAgOWclr8AAABgp3/FvwAAAMArG7i/AAAAoEk3ub8AAACAkGixPwAAAID7MKM/AAAAQBxdvD8AAABAnN/TvwAAAIA1M8S/AAAAIFtYtD8AAACgEkzQPwAAAADbFIA/AAAAQE8I5j8AAACAdd7BPwAAAEBoray/AAAAgEMOm78AAABg+MKrvwAAAODnA8K/AAAAgL+epz8AAADAc1CovwAAAICr15C/AAAAQOVFp78AAAAge9a7vwAAAOCLlEm/AAAAQPUFpz8AAADgKRHDPwAAAIDRwLq/AAAA4NsEr78AAACAl5WkPwAAAAATzbM/AAAAAPlgfT8AAADAEe/DPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” I don’t know why",
    "question": " What does that mean?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIDKqj78AAACAskqxPwAAAGAQuqc/AAAAwLWKwb8AAACAlo25PwAAAMByLki/AAAAoI2nuT8AAACg9VuavwAAAEAMn6e/AAAAABPLuD8AAAAgeBmXvwAAAOB6gqA/AAAA4Jp2i78AAACAs1GwvwAAAABV2cg/AAAAAOwavz8AAABg3T7APwAAAEBj34+/AAAAgOWclr8AAABgp3/FvwAAAMArG7i/AAAAoEk3ub8AAACAkGixPwAAAID7MKM/AAAAQBxdvD8AAABAnN/TvwAAAIA1M8S/AAAAIFtYtD8AAACgEkzQPwAAAADbFIA/AAAAQE8I5j8AAACAdd7BPwAAAEBoray/AAAAgEMOm78AAABg+MKrvwAAAODnA8K/AAAAgL+epz8AAADAc1CovwAAAICr15C/AAAAQOVFp78AAAAge9a7vwAAAOCLlEm/AAAAQPUFpz8AAADgKRHDPwAAAIDRwLq/AAAA4NsEr78AAACAl5WkPwAAAAATzbM/AAAAAPlgfT8AAADAEe/DPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean, I do a good job",
    "question": " What does that mean?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIDKqj78AAACAskqxPwAAAGAQuqc/AAAAwLWKwb8AAACAlo25PwAAAMByLki/AAAAoI2nuT8AAACg9VuavwAAAEAMn6e/AAAAABPLuD8AAAAgeBmXvwAAAOB6gqA/AAAA4Jp2i78AAACAs1GwvwAAAABV2cg/AAAAAOwavz8AAABg3T7APwAAAEBj34+/AAAAgOWclr8AAABgp3/FvwAAAMArG7i/AAAAoEk3ub8AAACAkGixPwAAAID7MKM/AAAAQBxdvD8AAABAnN/TvwAAAIA1M8S/AAAAIFtYtD8AAACgEkzQPwAAAADbFIA/AAAAQE8I5j8AAACAdd7BPwAAAEBoray/AAAAgEMOm78AAABg+MKrvwAAAODnA8K/AAAAgL+epz8AAADAc1CovwAAAICr15C/AAAAQOVFp78AAAAge9a7vwAAAOCLlEm/AAAAQPUFpz8AAADgKRHDPwAAAIDRwLq/AAAA4NsEr78AAACAl5WkPwAAAAATzbM/AAAAAPlgfT8AAADAEe/DPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I have thousands of employees",
    "question": " What does that mean?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIDKqj78AAACAskqxPwAAAGAQuqc/AAAAwLWKwb8AAACAlo25PwAAAMByLki/AAAAoI2nuT8AAACg9VuavwAAAEAMn6e/AAAAABPLuD8AAAAgeBmXvwAAAOB6gqA/AAAA4Jp2i78AAACAs1GwvwAAAABV2cg/AAAAAOwavz8AAABg3T7APwAAAEBj34+/AAAAgOWclr8AAABgp3/FvwAAAMArG7i/AAAAoEk3ub8AAACAkGixPwAAAID7MKM/AAAAQBxdvD8AAABAnN/TvwAAAIA1M8S/AAAAIFtYtD8AAACgEkzQPwAAAADbFIA/AAAAQE8I5j8AAACAdd7BPwAAAEBoray/AAAAgEMOm78AAABg+MKrvwAAAODnA8K/AAAAgL+epz8AAADAc1CovwAAAICr15C/AAAAQOVFp78AAAAge9a7vwAAAOCLlEm/AAAAQPUFpz8AAADgKRHDPwAAAIDRwLq/AAAA4NsEr78AAACAl5WkPwAAAAATzbM/AAAAAPlgfT8AAADAEe/DPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I work hard",
    "question": " What does that mean?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIDKqj78AAACAskqxPwAAAGAQuqc/AAAAwLWKwb8AAACAlo25PwAAAMByLki/AAAAoI2nuT8AAACg9VuavwAAAEAMn6e/AAAAABPLuD8AAAAgeBmXvwAAAOB6gqA/AAAA4Jp2i78AAACAs1GwvwAAAABV2cg/AAAAAOwavz8AAABg3T7APwAAAEBj34+/AAAAgOWclr8AAABgp3/FvwAAAMArG7i/AAAAoEk3ub8AAACAkGixPwAAAID7MKM/AAAAQBxdvD8AAABAnN/TvwAAAIA1M8S/AAAAIFtYtD8AAACgEkzQPwAAAADbFIA/AAAAQE8I5j8AAACAdd7BPwAAAEBoray/AAAAgEMOm78AAABg+MKrvwAAAODnA8K/AAAAgL+epz8AAADAc1CovwAAAICr15C/AAAAQOVFp78AAAAge9a7vwAAAOCLlEm/AAAAQPUFpz8AAADgKRHDPwAAAIDRwLq/AAAA4NsEr78AAACAl5WkPwAAAAATzbM/AAAAAPlgfT8AAADAEe/DPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "mean"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I would just loosen them up",
    "question": " But just – given the Supreme Court rulings on libel — Sullivan v. New York Times — how would you change the law?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAIDTgk78AANRIrf2xPwAAANBUIZy/AAAAEB5Tg78AAABwDNSpPwAAADAjhos/AABAwHS/uL8AAAAgh46JvwAAIAitwqK/AAAANhido78AAAA4yBWmvwAAAOYEDrg/AAAAovD9t78AAABCkKa1vwAAAOzZIMM/AAAAgJkgeD8AAAD4DmdmvwAAANAHg7q/AAAAlLgit78AAICQNwPAvwAAALiYCZk/AAAAgLXnnD8AAIByD/WxPwAAAKBJboi/AACAb39Ysj8AAABEI5fSvwAAACikJLW/AAAACd6ior8AAAAAgTNuvwAAAPCAuZ4/AAAANDyZ4z8AAACAOzZ0vwAAAIBNcp0/AAAAHJ0Yxb8AAAAAtmQ2PwAAAFeUiLS/AAAAIMV2qT8AAECn02OdPwAAAODdAli/AAAAZK66oL8AAABWyOeLvwAAADc3v7c/AAAA4FHFpL8AAAA05r6nPwAAAFhvsbS/AAAAUH5TlD8AAADAWciSvwAAAEDF2XM/AAAAQE51gr8AAMD4KCvCPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "change",
      "Sullivan",
      "Times",
      "given"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Very loud, and it’s repeated over and over",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Actually, I guess it’s on tape, but they repeat it over and over",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " One thing that was interesting this weekend",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We had in Phoenix, Arizona, we had an interesting incident",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We had people, we had a major highway coming into the arena",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " It’s not an arena, it’s a huge open space, 60 acres, and it was packed",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And we had a major highway coming in, and people — protesters — stopped their car in the middle of the highway, chained themselves to their cars, and the cars — blocked",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They were there for a while",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " A car was not able to move",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They were backed up for 20 — I mean, like, just forever",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And, it was terrible",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And they were very abusive, screaming, you know, “screw you, screw you, pigs, pigs” — meaning to the cops",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Sheriff Joe Arpaio — now that was his territory",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Okay, he’s a tough cookie",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Sheriff Joe saw this, he gave them a couple of minutes to move their car — they didn’t move them — cut the chains, arrested the people and just moved the cars over",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I don’t know how they did it — just, they were gone in minutes after he came there",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Minutes",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " It was amazing how quick",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They actually had chains around their necks",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They didn’t even know why they were there",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " People – somebody was interviewed, “Why are you here?” “Well, I don’t know, I’m not sure",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” They didn’t even know",
    "question": " — please do not engage these protesters. You know, they may cause a disturbance. Please do your best, let local law enforcement handle this or security at that venue. The problem becomes, with a massive crowd of twenty or thirty or forty thousand people, the resources that are there don’t have the ability to get to all these people in a manner before the crowd reacts, because the agitators are inciting those people. So we are very clear at the onset, that there is a loud public notice that says, “please do not engage these people, please let them do their job, and let the local law enforcement deal with that.” That’s said at the very front end at every event.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAA3QnD8AAABYLre5vwAAAKAeH5C/AABkBrJPkr8AAECRReOwvwAAAKRk5bO/AACApxvPtD8AAADgWPGuPwAAAIDTE50/AAAAiLZ4oL8AAAD8vhGXvwAAAJy7f7C/AAAATqr8nz8AAAAKefmDvwAAAEJEmLO/AAAAgdxgpr8AAABQxpeIvwAAANAhF5C/AAAAwF5ZgD8AAAB8EWjAvwAAAAjvMpU/AACAUZiFrz8AAAAAQraNPwAAAMqHEI0/AAAAAGu4Yz8AAADg4u/NvwAAAMDneMM/AAAAsJkmmb8AAADMcHi4PwAAANC/r4Q/AAAAoJpT2z8AAAAYtUujPwAAABTtEL+/AAAA8lIt0b8AAAAhZaq3vwAAAECGI5c/AAAAMHv6qr8AAADMopHGvwAAAFC5jbm/AAAA8Az+sz8AAABIfk+3vwAAAIBqSnQ/AAAAthYNsj8AAAC48+muPwAAAEPiEsA/AAAAUa3KuL8AAAAALQVQvwAAAAC602q/AAAAqA5xjr8AAAByKO2Avw==",
    "important_question": [
      "engage",
      "protesters.",
      "disturbance.",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Strong",
    "question": " — any potential protesters. That is made to everybody that says —",
    "question_vector": "AAAAsFBTr78AAABUCOypvwAAAFjL77M/AAAAQGDnt78AAAA40Ma0PwAAAEjfCMC/AAAAJHbJnr8AAABg2qerPwAAADApG76/AAAAwOgHjD8AAADYG3mwvwAAAHzFscG/AAAAEEylr78AAACYf4OKvwAAAAYHKMA/AAAAwF9rmT8AAABMpV+zPwAAAJCi4qE/AAAAALYxYb8AAADwBbTHvwAAAICjqIO/AAAA0JCvwT8AAABANH2MPwAAAMCQWKo/AAAA4KwJvD8AAABomgTSvwAAAAAhypI/AAAAyGVItz8AAAC4Mdy4PwAAAIiuHcW/AAAAUJbN2z8AAABgBCzEPwAAABQZk7q/AAAAjNDirL8AAABAYxHGvwAAAABCSIu/AAAAKKA5tT8AAABoaye/vwAAAICGS4q/AAAAoEEkpT8AAADwmeWxvwAAYOTeIaA/AAAAoIyYir8AAAAgpEWVPwAAgHj0u8A/AAAAAIS2ib8AAAC8yvbAvwAAAMwt8rW/AAAAoE5WkL8AAACA4Pqqvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "protesters.",
      "everybody"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " It’s true",
    "question": " To be fair, before every event, there is a public service announcement made about —",
    "question_vector": "AAAASklBtz9VVVUJXMi/P1VVBZrj9bG/AAAAwC8FxD+rqqqq3FCqP6uqqioguXe/AADA+MHmpr+rqqqq4U6MPwAAAECLwJY/q6qqqiFZgD9VVVVV3p2Dv6uqquolXLm/VVVVtcsPsr+rqqpqFtegv1VVVR1ofsY/q6qqak52rT+rqqqqu0SCv6uqqqpsZHg/q6qqTu8Zwb8AAAB80r+xvwAAAID92qo/VVVVdbhRm78AAADEBKWjvwAAAAD8E5m/AAAA8Kw9qT9VVVWVx0/Sv6uqqvqur7O/q6qqKsZRrz+rqqpuqr6xv6uqqhpWj60/q6qqGgCe4j8AAAAA6lNnP1VVVRWgFLK/q6qqlh6gsb9VVVU1ekqov6uqqiLdrb6/AAAAKFVmtj+rqqpqxcibPwAAAPDdabW/VVVVFR/1tL9VVVXJ1YOmvwAAAIAfvX2/AAAA4Lf0ur9VVVW12wWgv6uqqioCT5w/VVVVVXK+bz9VVVWFkeOcv1VVVeXforE/VVVV1ZFmZT+rqqqqJj+wPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "event",
      "announcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Don’t think so",
    "question": " Doesn’t that convey a message of approval?",
    "question_vector": "q6qq6lfmnj+rqqrqA3Svv1VVVbXIRa4/VVVVRbJts78AAADlTHWxP6uqqmqs05q/q6qqWh73qD9VVVVVszG0PwAAALqYm4A/q6qqyg3rtj+rqqq6iW2APwAAAACk6KM/q6qq0hPcuT+rqqraYEGwPwAAAOBRv5Q/q6qquqLpuj9VVVUFWeK8vwAAAHwXOL6/q6qq6vPsvT9VVVUVRhq4vwAAAMBZHI8/AAAAgGwLg78AAAAAqBdkPwAAAMAyW7a/AAAAUMMHwj+rqqpKIlzQv6uqqip+j5e/VVVV4VJ7tD8AAAAAikhtP1VVVYUMYrK/q6qqilnP0D9VVVUlombAPwAAAI4gJsC/VVVVtaiVsr+rqqoKEYSnv6uqqro1z8O/VVVVrceqtz8AAAAAlpyFP6uqqqqkcbC/AAAAbEV7tL9VVVVVLUtkPwAAAABBBXg/AAAAKDDLqL9VVVV1viymP1VVVQULVcC/q6qqQn2Ppj9VVVVV3zVgv1VVVfVXFMw/q6qqiswQhr9VVVWVd1S2Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Doesnt",
      "message",
      "approval"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No, I don’t think so",
    "question": " Isn’t that condoning?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAiIq+oj8AAAAQJF3IvwAAAMDPUrO/AAAAwH8W0b8AAAB0tauivwAAAHAvNqY/AAAAAA8Zzj8AAABAzqOgvwAAAAB6ZXs/AAAAkJkVyD8AAAD4hXmzvwAAAMBk3Ye/AAAA6L9mqr8AAACkpn+4vwAAAIA69MM/AAAAwL30gL8AAADkfgLBPwAAAAD5mLA/AAAAiFM9xT8AAACQIYy6PwAAAHjaKrS/AAAA8Obxmj8AAAAgLiOuPwAAAJjE2Kw/AAAACAwhtT8AAACAL4+cvwAAAACK+Gs/AAAAWN4txT8AAABo+RPQPwAAACCtSqG/AAAAOClTyb8AAADQYn+5PwAAAIB0lZG/AAAAJPjGtb8AAADQAi7FvwAAAIC0OZ8/AAAAoMaXoj8AAAB8vo2zvwAAABBXPMq/AAAAABI3uD8AAACA3GKLvwAAADSznqy/AAAAdkfvkr8AAAAAwOjBPwAAAABcwK6/AAAAAHo2wb8AAAAA+CqtvwAAAEDEwco/AAAAABTXjT8AAABYfWujPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Isnt",
      "condoning"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I said I want to look into it",
    "question": " You said you would consider it —",
    "question_vector": "AAAA4PevsD8AAABAzimivwAAAEAJMrY/AAAAoP4nwT8AAADA0yDGPwAAACABy6e/AAAAoIoYwr8AAADArbGlvwAAAEBijpU/AAAAQFpXw78AAAAgMmOlPwAAAIDR26I/AAAA4NvNyb8AAACABwa3vwAAAGAdXcY/AAAAgFHhuj8AAACAGACxPwAAACDWFJu/AAAAoH5QsD8AAACAAmm3vwAAAGD717K/AAAAIJd/xz8AAAAgIOhhPwAAAAAFQ8O/AAAAYO2msT8AAACga+HXvwAAAGDt1Kg/AAAAQKGNqz8AAACAESW/vwAAAMDzmI+/AAAAQN804D8AAACgW3GFvwAAAAA0Qno/AAAAQGT7Uz8AAADAAU6uvwAAAKBAwMO/AAAAgN7FkD8AAAAgWz6RPwAAACBj8Mk/AAAA4MPjwj8AAAAAx9KzvwAAAADSOsw/AAAAINIBrD8AAADArHK/vwAAAIBMHsM/AAAAoB9os78AAADAXC/LvwAAAGDnb8I/AAAAICA8mD8AAABArbrJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "said"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I said I want to look into it",
    "question": " You said you would consider it —",
    "question_vector": "AAAA4PevsD8AAABAzimivwAAAEAJMrY/AAAAoP4nwT8AAADA0yDGPwAAACABy6e/AAAAoIoYwr8AAADArbGlvwAAAEBijpU/AAAAQFpXw78AAAAgMmOlPwAAAIDR26I/AAAA4NvNyb8AAACABwa3vwAAAGAdXcY/AAAAgFHhuj8AAACAGACxPwAAACDWFJu/AAAAoH5QsD8AAACAAmm3vwAAAGD717K/AAAAIJd/xz8AAAAgIOhhPwAAAAAFQ8O/AAAAYO2msT8AAACga+HXvwAAAGDt1Kg/AAAAQKGNqz8AAACAESW/vwAAAMDzmI+/AAAAQN804D8AAACgW3GFvwAAAAA0Qno/AAAAQGT7Uz8AAADAAU6uvwAAAKBAwMO/AAAAgN7FkD8AAAAgWz6RPwAAACBj8Mk/AAAA4MPjwj8AAAAAx9KzvwAAAADSOsw/AAAAINIBrD8AAADArHK/vwAAAIBMHsM/AAAAoB9os78AAADAXC/LvwAAAGDnb8I/AAAAICA8mD8AAABArbrJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "said"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I didn’t say that",
    "question": " You said you would consider it —",
    "question_vector": "AAAA4PevsD8AAABAzimivwAAAEAJMrY/AAAAoP4nwT8AAADA0yDGPwAAACABy6e/AAAAoIoYwr8AAADArbGlvwAAAEBijpU/AAAAQFpXw78AAAAgMmOlPwAAAIDR26I/AAAA4NvNyb8AAACABwa3vwAAAGAdXcY/AAAAgFHhuj8AAACAGACxPwAAACDWFJu/AAAAoH5QsD8AAACAAmm3vwAAAGD717K/AAAAIJd/xz8AAAAgIOhhPwAAAAAFQ8O/AAAAYO2msT8AAACga+HXvwAAAGDt1Kg/AAAAQKGNqz8AAACAESW/vwAAAMDzmI+/AAAAQN804D8AAACgW3GFvwAAAAA0Qno/AAAAQGT7Uz8AAADAAU6uvwAAAKBAwMO/AAAAgN7FkD8AAAAgWz6RPwAAACBj8Mk/AAAA4MPjwj8AAAAAx9KzvwAAAADSOsw/AAAAINIBrD8AAADArHK/vwAAAIBMHsM/AAAAoB9os78AAADAXC/LvwAAAGDnb8I/AAAAICA8mD8AAABArbrJPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "said"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No, I didn’t offer, Fred —",
    "question": " Isn’t that condoning?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAiIq+oj8AAAAQJF3IvwAAAMDPUrO/AAAAwH8W0b8AAAB0tauivwAAAHAvNqY/AAAAAA8Zzj8AAABAzqOgvwAAAAB6ZXs/AAAAkJkVyD8AAAD4hXmzvwAAAMBk3Ye/AAAA6L9mqr8AAACkpn+4vwAAAIA69MM/AAAAwL30gL8AAADkfgLBPwAAAAD5mLA/AAAAiFM9xT8AAACQIYy6PwAAAHjaKrS/AAAA8Obxmj8AAAAgLiOuPwAAAJjE2Kw/AAAACAwhtT8AAACAL4+cvwAAAACK+Gs/AAAAWN4txT8AAABo+RPQPwAAACCtSqG/AAAAOClTyb8AAADQYn+5PwAAAIB0lZG/AAAAJPjGtb8AAADQAi7FvwAAAIC0OZ8/AAAAoMaXoj8AAAB8vo2zvwAAABBXPMq/AAAAABI3uD8AAACA3GKLvwAAADSznqy/AAAAdkfvkr8AAAAAwOjBPwAAAABcwK6/AAAAAHo2wb8AAAAA+CqtvwAAAEDEwco/AAAAABTXjT8AAABYfWujPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Isnt",
      "condoning"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I didn’t offer —",
    "question": " I guess the question is, when you then offer to pay the guy’s legal fees, isn’t that —",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYE+3n78AAADAynaMPwAAAMizg54/AAAA1xCprb8AAAAIjPi8PwAAAACIFGm/AAAALGMTsb8AAAAyn+qbPwAAACiBXKW/AAAAEGHUjj8AAACwK0u2vwAAAPznzbE/AAAAICnztL8AAAAEVvOSvwAAAIDeV8g/AAAAbRzwrT8AAAAif2yzPwAAAPg2spI/AAAAiMd0kD8AAABwX8vFvwAAAADKN3a/AAAAUMOUoj8AAACYSlGhPwAAACjFH7I/AAAAIE14tD8AAAAQCmTUvwAAAFR20MC/AAAAcAMwnT8AAAAVs1TBPwAAAL+tbsK/AAAAMOLE3T8AAAD89Iq/PwAAAKBWDZG/AAAAHMz2o78AAIACg1qTPwAAAByzRaW/AAAAgIosTT8AAADsf+eWPwAAAChZEqI/AAAAVK6dtL8AAADESkekvwAAAMXS75k/AAAAeH1okT8AAAAomSnNPwAAAGTpIa+/AAAAz7HBtr8AAACQNjufPwAAABxb+rs/AAAAg/7Xdz8AAABGcarCPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "guess",
      "question",
      "fees",
      "guys"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Again I don’t condone it",
    "question": " — to punch him in the face?",
    "question_vector": "AAAATKQntL8AAACYrP++vwAAAGA6f4K/AAAAwuO1sD8AAADgZyGpPwAAAJAARrE/AAAAIKSXtD8AAABYZyjAPwAAAAAhZp0/AAAAwEXXlj8AAAAgR7+3vwAAADQXg46/AAAAkP0lqr8AAAAAVh6YPwAAAHaT8rA/AAAAIh9Prr8AAADAKImEvwAAAHBpA7q/AAAAyHPEvL8AAADgIzDJvwAAAOB2572/AAAA4F8Pl78AAAC9jZq3PwAAAOz/yqG/AAAAAIKFaz8AAADQfmPXvwAAACAR0bK/AAAAkKr2uD8AAAD4v9LDPwAAAMyenba/AAAAoCRO4D8AAAA0clS2PwAAANhyzJO/AAAAgGqLmD8AAAAwArqxvwAAAABjGsE/AAAgdSkakr8AAACAWV6XPwAAAODeXY4/AAAAALorxb8AAADg78SiPwAAANiApsg/AAAAIABlt78AAAD4+k+xPwAAAPCgA6k/AAAAZLu7rD8AAADopFGRPwAAAMCwCrm/AAAAc1lurj8AAAB4jlOpvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "punch",
      "face"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " So do you let him walk out, he’s holding up his finger, telling everybody",
    "question": " — to punch him in the face?",
    "question_vector": "AAAATKQntL8AAACYrP++vwAAAGA6f4K/AAAAwuO1sD8AAADgZyGpPwAAAJAARrE/AAAAIKSXtD8AAABYZyjAPwAAAAAhZp0/AAAAwEXXlj8AAAAgR7+3vwAAADQXg46/AAAAkP0lqr8AAAAAVh6YPwAAAHaT8rA/AAAAIh9Prr8AAADAKImEvwAAAHBpA7q/AAAAyHPEvL8AAADgIzDJvwAAAOB2572/AAAA4F8Pl78AAAC9jZq3PwAAAOz/yqG/AAAAAIKFaz8AAADQfmPXvwAAACAR0bK/AAAAkKr2uD8AAAD4v9LDPwAAAMyenba/AAAAoCRO4D8AAAA0clS2PwAAANhyzJO/AAAAgGqLmD8AAAAwArqxvwAAAABjGsE/AAAgdSkakr8AAACAWV6XPwAAAODeXY4/AAAAALorxb8AAADg78SiPwAAANiApsg/AAAAIABlt78AAAD4+k+xPwAAAPCgA6k/AAAAZLu7rD8AAADopFGRPwAAAMCwCrm/AAAAc1lurj8AAAB4jlOpvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "punch",
      "face"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Same thing happened, you know, the last one in —",
    "question": " — to punch him in the face?",
    "question_vector": "AAAATKQntL8AAACYrP++vwAAAGA6f4K/AAAAwuO1sD8AAADgZyGpPwAAAJAARrE/AAAAIKSXtD8AAABYZyjAPwAAAAAhZp0/AAAAwEXXlj8AAAAgR7+3vwAAADQXg46/AAAAkP0lqr8AAAAAVh6YPwAAAHaT8rA/AAAAIh9Prr8AAADAKImEvwAAAHBpA7q/AAAAyHPEvL8AAADgIzDJvwAAAOB2572/AAAA4F8Pl78AAAC9jZq3PwAAAOz/yqG/AAAAAIKFaz8AAADQfmPXvwAAACAR0bK/AAAAkKr2uD8AAAD4v9LDPwAAAMyenba/AAAAoCRO4D8AAAA0clS2PwAAANhyzJO/AAAAgGqLmD8AAAAwArqxvwAAAABjGsE/AAAgdSkakr8AAACAWV6XPwAAAODeXY4/AAAAALorxb8AAADg78SiPwAAANiApsg/AAAAIABlt78AAAD4+k+xPwAAAPCgA6k/AAAAZLu7rD8AAADopFGRPwAAAMCwCrm/AAAAc1lurj8AAAB4jlOpvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "punch",
      "face"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " So do you let him —",
    "question": " But does it — is it — does it qualify to —",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYLg9vz8AAADgSTrAPwAAAMCPg7e/AAAAIB36sj8AAACglubCPwAAAIDmJLs/AAAA4MLBPD8AAABgHJm+vwAAAGCMrao/AAAAgC6llz8AAACAnhW2PwAAAEAgTKQ/AAAAAFJhh78AAABApXixvwAAAOCr4qU/AAAAIPqVvT8AAAAALTy7PwAAAGDRjME/AAAAYCaOn78AAABgbY+GPwAAAOAXkb6/AAAAgBtLrb8AAABgOq90vwAAAGCjFLw/AAAAAHydqT8AAADA/MPYvwAAAMD987m/AAAAIFhzwT8AAACg7cSKPwAAAMBK6YW/AAAAgEvp5z8AAABAbYzDvwAAAIAso5m/AAAAYNr+ub8AAAAAafSKPwAAAOCCorC/AAAAYNs9mz8AAACgYz6jPwAAAMAG6Js/AAAAwAi5pb8AAADAr8lqvwAAAADXhK8/AAAAIJ3DsL8AAAAAbwN1vwAAAGD3S7O/AAAAYPCZoz8AAACg1C+ZvwAAAACz1qu/AAAAAP82rz8AAADgEH+4Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well, a lot of people don’t — you know, the finger means, “F you",
    "question": " So that’s okay?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwBkasT8AAAAAtMm9vwAAAEBR16C/AAAAYJyCwr8AAADA/oWrPwAAAMCMXcO/AAAAIBXcwT8AAADA/ZOqPwAAAMBxPKy/AAAAYJMUvj8AAADgdVm3vwAAAMDxibg/AAAAQHPhwr8AAAAAw9KrvwAAAOBlVrA/AAAAQFytxD8AAAAAyhDOPwAAAEBAMcE/AAAAoLu3wD8AAABgoIaAPwAAACBXzsq/AAAA4JfLgb8AAACAiVXAPwAAAGCDV7g/AAAAAKx70z8AAAAAox+qvwAAAACQp9O/AAAAIMBVxD8AAAAA2NzGPwAAAEBZ+cy/AAAAQDuvxr8AAABgLEa0PwAAAODkEJc/AAAAALZbwj8AAABA4ZuYPwAAAABTisG/AAAAwHOmjb8AAACgmGrKPwAAAGDBNrk/AAAAQKTitz8AAACAzzOzvwAAAEBlps+/AAAAAOvVjz8AAADgIafTPwAAAMBQajA/AAAAINP2sz8AAADg4F6/PwAAACDXqMg/AAAAANAufD8AAACA5HG0Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” A lot of people think — and you have children there, you have a lot of children that go, you know, they go with their parents — a lot of people think that’s very inappropriate",
    "question": " So that’s okay?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwBkasT8AAAAAtMm9vwAAAEBR16C/AAAAYJyCwr8AAADA/oWrPwAAAMCMXcO/AAAAIBXcwT8AAADA/ZOqPwAAAMBxPKy/AAAAYJMUvj8AAADgdVm3vwAAAMDxibg/AAAAQHPhwr8AAAAAw9KrvwAAAOBlVrA/AAAAQFytxD8AAAAAyhDOPwAAAEBAMcE/AAAAoLu3wD8AAABgoIaAPwAAACBXzsq/AAAA4JfLgb8AAACAiVXAPwAAAGCDV7g/AAAAAKx70z8AAAAAox+qvwAAAACQp9O/AAAAIMBVxD8AAAAA2NzGPwAAAEBZ+cy/AAAAQDuvxr8AAABgLEa0PwAAAODkEJc/AAAAALZbwj8AAABA4ZuYPwAAAABTisG/AAAAwHOmjb8AAACgmGrKPwAAAGDBNrk/AAAAQKTitz8AAACAzzOzvwAAAEBlps+/AAAAAOvVjz8AAADgIafTPwAAAMBQajA/AAAAINP2sz8AAADg4F6/PwAAACDXqMg/AAAAANAufD8AAACA5HG0Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean, you know —",
    "question": " So that’s okay?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwBkasT8AAAAAtMm9vwAAAEBR16C/AAAAYJyCwr8AAADA/oWrPwAAAMCMXcO/AAAAIBXcwT8AAADA/ZOqPwAAAMBxPKy/AAAAYJMUvj8AAADgdVm3vwAAAMDxibg/AAAAQHPhwr8AAAAAw9KrvwAAAOBlVrA/AAAAQFytxD8AAAAAyhDOPwAAAEBAMcE/AAAAoLu3wD8AAABgoIaAPwAAACBXzsq/AAAA4JfLgb8AAACAiVXAPwAAAGCDV7g/AAAAAKx70z8AAAAAox+qvwAAAACQp9O/AAAAIMBVxD8AAAAA2NzGPwAAAEBZ+cy/AAAAQDuvxr8AAABgLEa0PwAAAODkEJc/AAAAALZbwj8AAABA4ZuYPwAAAABTisG/AAAAwHOmjb8AAACgmGrKPwAAAGDBNrk/AAAAQKTitz8AAACAzzOzvwAAAEBlps+/AAAAAOvVjz8AAADgIafTPwAAAMBQajA/AAAAINP2sz8AAADg4F6/PwAAACDXqMg/AAAAANAufD8AAACA5HG0Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " He did give the finger, and —",
    "question": " But, yet, you explained it that he was giving the finger and so he provoked it, so he got sucker punched. And you are going to possibly pay for his legal expenses.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwLC3lT+rqqqqCvlcv1VVVVXLUZe/AAAAGJhjsL8AAADgkI65P1VVVbX5nb0/VVVVFUcMjr8AAADkBK6WP1VVVdVGAq0/AAAA8GJnsL+rqqqqDEWNv6uqqrb71Lc/VVVVBcr5s78AAADALguyvwAAAEDWibc/q6qqitpvoT8AAADMT2qxv6uqqnr7krm/VVVVMYjysj8AAAAQony+v1VVVZUpyq8/AAAAwDIEkD+rqqoqdU22P6uqqqr8hri/AAAAwFV0tD+rqqq67RHRvwAAAKDy/a2/VVVVFd6Wsj8AAACADOWZPwAAAMDDJ7G/VVVV1fAg3z9VVVUFK5awP6uqquganbI/q6qqKirgiL9VVdWypPGuv1VVVVXC7KI/q6qqSoajhj9VVVUJNlKzPwAAAGAUa7o/AAAAgLBPmz+rqqqq2AB1P1VVVfXgULM/VVVVNf5Ft78AAAAQEoy9P1VVVVUZEXk/q6qqWnp2xL+rqqoq5pGdP1VVVf0gwrU/VVVVlbYKmD8AAACA+eSlPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "explained",
      "finger",
      "expenses.."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " By the way, that’s different —",
    "question": " Where the protester is being walked out —",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOPKEub8AAADA8PyZvwAAAGDlHK0/AAAAqFTUwL8AAACwScrNPwAAAABLpo4/AAAAlF2Twb8AAABASv62PwAAABg1i6i/AAAAgG0vtb8AAAC4r5K4vwAAAHDjac2/AAAAepbQt78AAAAYV1rBPwAAAHAFG7M/AAAAEOocx78AAADIxZqavwAAAHziD6G/AAAAIGweqb8AAADWZn+0vwAAABAA3rO/AAAAMAvbyD8AAAAs1z+4vwAAAFilQYG/AAAAANg5vT8AAACYA17QvwAAAEAko8Y/AAAAsMehuz8AAABA5tCCvwAAgIrdksG/AAAArhrXyT8AAAAwDLKbPwAAADCN0q6/AAAAkOKPuz8AAAAIw1C9vwAAAADPnli/AAAAYJT9vj8AAACAd26rvwAAAJDiH7I/AAAA8Ol2wj8AAADYNa61vwAAAOCJWbs/AAAAyCIxtr8AAACAnTeIPwAAABJyl8o/AAAA8PHKyb8AAAAAh3m4vwAAAHjFqMe/AAAAAHYZpT8AAAC4DGW5vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "walked",
      "protester"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No I don’t, no I don’t, that’s different —",
    "question": " Well, okay, Fayetteville, do you condone violence in that case —",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgE84oD8AAAAMTtSxvwAAAJ8rY7S/AAAARKHedT8AAACgstR8vwAAADC9TaU/AAAAYPJ/sz8AAADQ042XPwAAADyXA6U/AAAAlEFiiD8AAADMovG1vwAAALw5N7a/AAAA6CEktb8AAACuV6fGvwAAAGBRNrQ/AAAALAsIrj8AAADAgeJ/PwAAAADAdlA/AAAAwA3PV78AAADAYXGlPwAAAJAAxKO/AAAAkMwntz8AAACGx7ixPwAAiHvmbrY/AAAAEDphsr8AAAB2eYPSvwAAAGBQdFu/AAAA0Jomlj8AAEDIC3HAPwAAAJCDF6a/AABIVj7ezj8AAADwZOOmvwAAAAQftsG/AAAAzB4vyb8AAACgtqKBvwAAAORpeLW/AAAAQGSneD8AAAAAY27EvwAAACC/faS/AAAApPr6oz8AAACgBVyzvwAAAIB542m/AAAAgDjUUj8AAABkyxK0PwAAAMRHibE/AAAA8Ccfiz8AAADYmfaOvwAAACBRBac/AAAAtkFopr8AAAACa52xPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "condone",
      "Fayetteville",
      "violence",
      "case"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Oh well that’s a different — that’s different from the one I’m talking about",
    "question": " That’s the gentleman you said you were going to look into to see whether or not to pay his legal fees.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgPfXkr9VVVVVTwmOP1VVVZ3nvLu/q6qqyoUqwb9VVVUV1wi3PwAAAIB2zqu/VVVVVdpAib+rqqqKB/mqPwAAAIAqp5O/AAAAgJR1oz+rqqoKmc6vv6uqqoo/fsA/AAAAgNR/oj+rqqpKhtKpvwAAAOCre7U/AAAAAIXgdD+rqqoCx3e1PwAAABh61Lo/VVVVNQE2qD+rqqombmy2v1VVVVVNkWW/q6qqCtI+iT8AAACAoaWWvwAAAEiLuLc/q6qqap6YtT8AAAAA9TDHv6uqqnoFjsS/VVVVhZE7pT+rqqpyOiC4P1VVVfWF4bC/AAAAAPlXxD8AAACAdBORPwAAAABpUmg/q6qqQtxMuz+rqqp6pb60PwAAAGja0KO/VVVV5Ua8hD+rqqq6E2enP6uqqupzBZ0/AAAAIC3Dqb+rqqqKlgaSP6uqqpJTTLG/VVVVVVnWfj+rqqpak83QP1VVFakus7O/VVVVhfHDwb8AAAAAczlgvwAAAACUebM/AAAAoKqUrT+rqqoqW1O3Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Thats",
      "gentleman",
      "fees.."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " This one was about a month ago",
    "question": " That’s the gentleman you said you were going to look into to see whether or not to pay his legal fees.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgPfXkr9VVVVVTwmOP1VVVZ3nvLu/q6qqyoUqwb9VVVUV1wi3PwAAAIB2zqu/VVVVVdpAib+rqqqKB/mqPwAAAIAqp5O/AAAAgJR1oz+rqqoKmc6vv6uqqoo/fsA/AAAAgNR/oj+rqqpKhtKpvwAAAOCre7U/AAAAAIXgdD+rqqoCx3e1PwAAABh61Lo/VVVVNQE2qD+rqqombmy2v1VVVVVNkWW/q6qqCtI+iT8AAACAoaWWvwAAAEiLuLc/q6qqap6YtT8AAAAA9TDHv6uqqnoFjsS/VVVVhZE7pT+rqqpyOiC4P1VVVfWF4bC/AAAAAPlXxD8AAACAdBORPwAAAABpUmg/q6qqQtxMuz+rqqp6pb60PwAAAGja0KO/VVVV5Ua8hD+rqqq6E2enP6uqqupzBZ0/AAAAIC3Dqb+rqqqKlgaSP6uqqpJTTLG/VVVVVVnWfj+rqqpak83QP1VVFakus7O/VVVVhfHDwb8AAAAAczlgvwAAAACUebM/AAAAoKqUrT+rqqoqW1O3Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Thats",
      "gentleman",
      "fees.."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " This one was before Fayetteville",
    "question": " That’s the gentleman you said you were going to look into to see whether or not to pay his legal fees.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAgPfXkr9VVVVVTwmOP1VVVZ3nvLu/q6qqyoUqwb9VVVUV1wi3PwAAAIB2zqu/VVVVVdpAib+rqqqKB/mqPwAAAIAqp5O/AAAAgJR1oz+rqqoKmc6vv6uqqoo/fsA/AAAAgNR/oj+rqqpKhtKpvwAAAOCre7U/AAAAAIXgdD+rqqoCx3e1PwAAABh61Lo/VVVVNQE2qD+rqqombmy2v1VVVVVNkWW/q6qqCtI+iT8AAACAoaWWvwAAAEiLuLc/q6qqap6YtT8AAAAA9TDHv6uqqnoFjsS/VVVVhZE7pT+rqqpyOiC4P1VVVfWF4bC/AAAAAPlXxD8AAACAdBORPwAAAABpUmg/q6qqQtxMuz+rqqp6pb60PwAAAGja0KO/VVVV5Ua8hD+rqqq6E2enP6uqqupzBZ0/AAAAIC3Dqb+rqqqKlgaSP6uqqpJTTLG/VVVVVVnWfj+rqqpak83QP1VVFakus7O/VVVVhfHDwb8AAAAAczlgvwAAAACUebM/AAAAoKqUrT+rqqoqW1O3Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Thats",
      "gentleman",
      "fees.."
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I don’t know",
    "question": " North Carolina.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoNtdqz8AAACAHk+5PwAAAOARkH2/AAAAwASObT8AAAAgODu6vwAAAKD0aaa/AAAAgLVuw78AAAAgZj+xPwAAACDQALU/AAAAAOWayr8AAADgkq23vwAAAODN8sG/AAAAIIrJgT8AAABgpqLGvwAAAAC1qMi/AAAAgIH3vT8AAADg0UfAPwAAAABuGbY/AAAAYPGcxL8AAADArYW+PwAAAKCLcqk/AAAAgN8Sjz8AAAAg4zSRPwAAAGAP17c/AAAAgDlGiz8AAAAgSl/YvwAAAMARdro/AAAAgHJOuj8AAABgJ/eHvwAAAOBbk7O/AAAAYPZy4z8AAACAJ8O8vwAAAMCPbpQ/AAAAQFHkpr8AAACgJXG5PwAAAKBXvcK/AAAAAE3Rsb8AAAAg07u0vwAAAKB6ScG/AAAAoAtCpD8AAABA/8S3vwAAAMASKae/AAAAYG6+vj8AAABgzyXHvwAAACBIZpi/AAAAYOYtvT8AAADgk8GuvwAAAIBmm5O/AAAAIDgivL8AAAAgPLOxvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "North"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I don’t know which one",
    "question": " North Carolina.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoNtdqz8AAACAHk+5PwAAAOARkH2/AAAAwASObT8AAAAgODu6vwAAAKD0aaa/AAAAgLVuw78AAAAgZj+xPwAAACDQALU/AAAAAOWayr8AAADgkq23vwAAAODN8sG/AAAAIIrJgT8AAABgpqLGvwAAAAC1qMi/AAAAgIH3vT8AAADg0UfAPwAAAABuGbY/AAAAYPGcxL8AAADArYW+PwAAAKCLcqk/AAAAgN8Sjz8AAAAg4zSRPwAAAGAP17c/AAAAgDlGiz8AAAAgSl/YvwAAAMARdro/AAAAgHJOuj8AAABgJ/eHvwAAAOBbk7O/AAAAYPZy4z8AAACAJ8O8vwAAAMCPbpQ/AAAAQFHkpr8AAACgJXG5PwAAAKBXvcK/AAAAAE3Rsb8AAAAg07u0vwAAAKB6ScG/AAAAoAtCpD8AAABA/8S3vwAAAMASKae/AAAAYG6+vj8AAABgzyXHvwAAACBIZpi/AAAAYOYtvT8AAADgk8GuvwAAAIBmm5O/AAAAIDgivL8AAAAgPLOxvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "North"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No",
    "question": " He was being escorted from police, and he was sucker punched.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAWAbywD8AAAAwshDDvwAAADCYxqY/AAAAQF/Oub8AAACAaou6PwAAAJh/FcK/AAAAzDUswL8AAABIb2jDPwAAAFB5J4i/AAAA4G4c0r8AAADwuy+KPwAAQPDAzLS/AAAAhgtorb8AAABgF/+lPwAAAABJTHi/AAAAgBX7uL8AAABYHH/AvwAAAHjqZ7M/AAAA8Bbvv78AAADwWsu+vwAAACjNtbg/AAAAMP1oyj8AAAAwP/SIvwAAwAVT/qk/AAAACFo8uL8AAAAYup/TvwAAANwPdbw/AAAA2LWDrz8AAABgEVqQvwAAAABCs72/AAAA/N5D0j8AAABA47OePwAAABAjJre/AAAA4Lnuub8AAABAlGC+PwAAALB5M8E/AAAAOEIlwD8AAACwqTLBvwAAAJh3MrS/AAAAkFo7xj8AAAAASFFJPwAAADBVSME/AAAAEABrvj8AAACo7JmzvwAAAHCHqbU/AAAAQFc1yL8AAABgW5bBvwAAADhoR72/AAAAIFSwqD8AAACgysC7vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "escorted",
      "police"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " When are you talking about? When?",
    "question": " He was being escorted from police, and he was sucker punched.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAWAbywD8AAAAwshDDvwAAADCYxqY/AAAAQF/Oub8AAACAaou6PwAAAJh/FcK/AAAAzDUswL8AAABIb2jDPwAAAFB5J4i/AAAA4G4c0r8AAADwuy+KPwAAQPDAzLS/AAAAhgtorb8AAABgF/+lPwAAAABJTHi/AAAAgBX7uL8AAABYHH/AvwAAAHjqZ7M/AAAA8Bbvv78AAADwWsu+vwAAACjNtbg/AAAAMP1oyj8AAAAwP/SIvwAAwAVT/qk/AAAACFo8uL8AAAAYup/TvwAAANwPdbw/AAAA2LWDrz8AAABgEVqQvwAAAABCs72/AAAA/N5D0j8AAABA47OePwAAABAjJre/AAAA4Lnuub8AAABAlGC+PwAAALB5M8E/AAAAOEIlwD8AAACwqTLBvwAAAJh3MrS/AAAAkFo7xj8AAAAASFFJPwAAADBVSME/AAAAEABrvj8AAACo7JmzvwAAAHCHqbU/AAAAQFc1yL8AAABgW5bBvwAAADhoR72/AAAAIFSwqD8AAACgysC7vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "escorted",
      "police"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No",
    "question": " The Fayetteville protester who was sucker punched — he didn’t punch anyone —",
    "question_vector": "VVVV8xOuub8AAAAggb/Cv6uqqsrrq8I/AAAA4BmdvL9VVVXFZCrCPwAAAOyPAqc/VVVVlRkinL9VVVWVAqK1P6uqqqqmSzO/q6qqqmhhlL9VVVUTgd2iv1VVVbVfXr+/AAAAGNypqb9VVVW1g5arPwAAADc3GL4/VVVV1QrDsL9VVVVVMjqSv1VVVcJf+py/AAAAwJYvn78AAADk2Lm6v6uqqjKGjLS/AAAAoC/PwD+rqqqqDlVjv6uqqlKtOpA/AAAAEPKtwT9VVVV1WxLXv6uqqio446U/AAAAiCGbtz8AAABAfautPwAAAGe0PsW/AAAAFHV3zD+rqqrqS1WEP1VVVRVNkLK/AAAAAPzRir9VVVVFZt/Bv6uqqpqlK7E/AAAAgONWvz+rqqr6dgOlv6uqquoLq6Q/q6qqKoJ8jz9VVVXZI0WmP6uqqkLcurs/VVVV9burpb+rqqpK7Ne6P1VVVbGY08A/AAAAiGq5xr+rqqpCpLewvwAAAKAU2rW/VVVVFYIquz+rqqqqFJW4vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "punched",
      "protester",
      "anyone"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Fred, he punched other people",
    "question": " No, I understand that.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYL9IsD8AAABAFgV+PwAAAOD1aVO/AAAAYHt7pr8AAAAgdjvDPwAAAMCAlZG/AAAAANMEmD8AAACgoJ2pPwAAAAAb27+/AAAAoBxppT8AAADAZF6mPwAAAOA3XMM/AAAAwMY7pb8AAADAV+GdvwAAAGBZPbo/AAAAoAm5wD8AAAAAfW28PwAAAEDH/KA/AAAA4NmNwj8AAACAvTfBvwAAAICPrby/AAAAIAxZwj8AAABAGX+ePwAAAIC32bw/AAAAgJZS0z8AAADAp9vWvwAAAAD+9cu/AAAAoA/Tvb8AAADgTZm+PwAAAGCygLq/AAAA4DQw4T8AAADAmmfAPwAAAMDC27q/AAAAwPl/0L8AAABgCqypvwAAAMC3s7K/AAAAICNKuL8AAACAsG+WvwAAAIDHTaI/AAAAQPu5mz8AAABg2sujvwAAAECHqKW/AAAAYCaYtT8AAADAs4jDPwAAAIA467A/AAAAIDNUsj8AAACAb76xPwAAACBO18U/AAAAYM2for8AAADA7Gm7Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "understand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " He was punching people",
    "question": " No, I understand that.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYL9IsD8AAABAFgV+PwAAAOD1aVO/AAAAYHt7pr8AAAAgdjvDPwAAAMCAlZG/AAAAANMEmD8AAACgoJ2pPwAAAAAb27+/AAAAoBxppT8AAADAZF6mPwAAAOA3XMM/AAAAwMY7pb8AAADAV+GdvwAAAGBZPbo/AAAAoAm5wD8AAAAAfW28PwAAAEDH/KA/AAAA4NmNwj8AAACAvTfBvwAAAICPrby/AAAAIAxZwj8AAABAGX+ePwAAAIC32bw/AAAAgJZS0z8AAADAp9vWvwAAAAD+9cu/AAAAoA/Tvb8AAADgTZm+PwAAAGCygLq/AAAA4DQw4T8AAADAmmfAPwAAAMDC27q/AAAAwPl/0L8AAABgCqypvwAAAMC3s7K/AAAAICNKuL8AAACAsG+WvwAAAIDHTaI/AAAAQPu5mz8AAABg2sujvwAAAECHqKW/AAAAYCaYtT8AAADAs4jDPwAAAIA467A/AAAAIDNUsj8AAACAb76xPwAAACBO18U/AAAAYM2for8AAADA7Gm7Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "understand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " He was — one guy was, you know, I’d like to say —",
    "question": " No, I understand that.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYL9IsD8AAABAFgV+PwAAAOD1aVO/AAAAYHt7pr8AAAAgdjvDPwAAAMCAlZG/AAAAANMEmD8AAACgoJ2pPwAAAAAb27+/AAAAoBxppT8AAADAZF6mPwAAAOA3XMM/AAAAwMY7pb8AAADAV+GdvwAAAGBZPbo/AAAAoAm5wD8AAAAAfW28PwAAAEDH/KA/AAAA4NmNwj8AAACAvTfBvwAAAICPrby/AAAAIAxZwj8AAABAGX+ePwAAAIC32bw/AAAAgJZS0z8AAADAp9vWvwAAAAD+9cu/AAAAoA/Tvb8AAADgTZm+PwAAAGCygLq/AAAA4DQw4T8AAADAmmfAPwAAAMDC27q/AAAAwPl/0L8AAABgCqypvwAAAMC3s7K/AAAAICNKuL8AAACAsG+WvwAAAIDHTaI/AAAAQPu5mz8AAABg2sujvwAAAECHqKW/AAAAYCaYtT8AAADAs4jDPwAAAIA467A/AAAAIDNUsj8AAACAb76xPwAAACBO18U/AAAAYM2for8AAADA7Gm7Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "understand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well he punched other people",
    "question": " Rip him out of his seat, punch him in the face, isn’t that violent?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAkCATrr+rqqoqrUZ+vwAAAARuq8A/AAAACDeSqr9VVVUVYuytv6uqqor5fLY/q6qq6oVcpT+rqqq60uq0P1VVVdW1XJy/AAAAkH4du78AAACwqymvv1VVVVXispO/VVVV+Z4xur9VVVXdEnSwP1VVVZXP0pU/VVVV/98LtT9VVVUVYmqYP1VVVZU+RnS/AAAA4OWior8AAABgh+HFv1VVVb2Wg7W/AAAA8E0vkL+rqqrKYil3v6uqqmrYvaQ/q6qqqr/pkr+rqqpK5rDUv6uqqhp/9q2/q6qqyrjauz9VVVVVFOu4P1VVVT1/ULK/VVVV5UEC2z9VVVVl6w24P6uqqlrzsKa/q6qqqrumaL8AAAAAVWmsvwAAADBak7U/AAAgWNFgoD+rqqrqDHqov1VVVZXW56E/q6qqzkd5wr8AAADwhuycvwAAAKDiYbw/AAAAAKEqcT+rqqqqFP1xPwAAAHBYcLK/VVVV4S6ysT+rqqoKHQKEPwAAAEAZpMi/VVVVXWa5hz8AAABQt82xvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Rip",
      "seat",
      "face"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No, I condone strong law and order",
    "question": " But your answer is you condone violence when the guy is really egregious and terrible?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAcJCanj8AAADo79uQPwAAALwI2pS/AAAA2PW5m78AAAB+tMLCPwAAAJiW9ag/AADAhdcRiz8AAAAIXT+QvwAAAPQJEa6/AAAA8OHLjz8AAACop1SyvwAAAABIpUK/AAAAIFxlvL8AAAAoBtCjvwAAAGZhR8E/AAAAAHrJnz8AAACk1PmxPwAAACAIFJg/AAAAMKr3hr8AAAA1bZ6wvwAAQJ4iE7S/AAAAeLlZtz8AAAD9j7KhPwAAAJi74Ls/AAAAwJXusT8AAAA0R/XVvwAAAISvTba/AACA+RcQsD8AAAAtbd29PwAAAKC7c32/AAAARK0i4T8AAACoFseAPwAAADBSLbK/AAAACKNhu78AAADeL7yRvwAAACD4VZy/AAAAgAceZT8AAAC5ZIatvwAAAABO9E4/AAAA8Mn6p78AAAC84hiMvwAAAGsJorg/AAAAoInHrb8AAADgGUWhPwAAABDnSJM/AAAAnvGFoz8AAABgvh6DvwAAAKALNZ0/AAAAwhGIqz8AAACg7He/Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "answer",
      "violence",
      "guy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’ll tell you what they —",
    "question": " But your answer is you condone violence when the guy is really egregious and terrible?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAcJCanj8AAADo79uQPwAAALwI2pS/AAAA2PW5m78AAAB+tMLCPwAAAJiW9ag/AADAhdcRiz8AAAAIXT+QvwAAAPQJEa6/AAAA8OHLjz8AAACop1SyvwAAAABIpUK/AAAAIFxlvL8AAAAoBtCjvwAAAGZhR8E/AAAAAHrJnz8AAACk1PmxPwAAACAIFJg/AAAAMKr3hr8AAAA1bZ6wvwAAQJ4iE7S/AAAAeLlZtz8AAAD9j7KhPwAAAJi74Ls/AAAAwJXusT8AAAA0R/XVvwAAAISvTba/AACA+RcQsD8AAAAtbd29PwAAAKC7c32/AAAARK0i4T8AAACoFseAPwAAADBSLbK/AAAACKNhu78AAADeL7yRvwAAACD4VZy/AAAAgAceZT8AAAC5ZIatvwAAAABO9E4/AAAA8Mn6p78AAAC84hiMvwAAAGsJorg/AAAAoInHrb8AAADgGUWhPwAAABDnSJM/AAAAnvGFoz8AAABgvh6DvwAAAKALNZ0/AAAAwhGIqz8AAACg7He/Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "answer",
      "violence",
      "guy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No, because what I am referring to is, we’ve had some very bad people come in",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We had one guy — and I said it — he had the voice — and this was what I was referring to — and I said, “Boy, I’d like to smash him",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” You know, I said that",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’d like to punch him",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " This guy was unbelievably loud",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " He had a voice like Pavarotti",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I said if I was his manager I would have made a lot of money for him, because he had the best voice",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean, the guy was unbelievable, how loud he was",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And he was a swinger",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " He was hitting people",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " He was punching and swinging and screaming — you couldn’t make — so you have to stop",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You know, there is also something about the First Amendment, but you had to stop",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And, so, this one man was very violent and very loud",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And when he was being taken out, he walked out like this, with his finger way up, like, “screw everybody",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "” And that’s when I made that statement",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " He was absolutely out — I mean, he hit people and he screamed and then he was walking out and he’s giving everybody the finger",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And they don’t talk about that",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " See, they don’t talk about that",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They say, “Donald, wait a second, Donald, don’t” —",
    "question": " You say that. But you’ve also said, “In the good old days, he would have been ripped out of his seat so fast, you wouldn’t believe it.” Isn’t that condoning violence?",
    "question_vector": "AAAA2GdwtT8AAAAARlmBvwAAwF0BPbI/AAAAdFEGq78AAAD4Md+xPwAAAECHhpY/AAAArG8BvL8AABDDa+2hPwAAAIqoeJi/AAAASNIUsL8AAABwaKepvwAAgDezy6y/AAAAVmIprr8AAABA30mFvwAAAEoiJ8E/AAAAcA8Ltz8AAACgOJuVvwAAAIDiSG+/AAAAVMQrob8AAIA5WYPAvwAAAFis1JS/AAAAwA/vpz8AAABgn/OlPwAAAGBVAXC/AAAAYBVJdz8AAABwjQPZvwAAAD41wre/AAAAGmIcqz8AAACk2fGYPwAAAAC7qVs/AAAAyJdb4z8AAABIz4WlPwAAABiqkLy/AADcn5WErb8AAADUZ8ukPwAAABqNBbG/AAAAfP/gpj8AAAAUTvyHPwAAACo0coY/AAAAkjkGmr8AAACwx428vwAAAJzLFbQ/AAAACNSWiL8AAAAee72xPwAAADsQk7C/AAAAbFBCkT8AAABEjEi6vwAAAADcTZW/AAAAYBHtm78AAACgjQ9uvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "say",
      "that.",
      "days",
      "seat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I say that",
    "question": " Sorry, when you say we don’t condone violence —",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEN7vj8AAADgvc2SvwAAAHAgYo4/AAAAiO4Iwr8AAADYrTOxvwAAAPAhYbm/AAAAReVytD8AAACA+siKvwAAAHDs05G/AAAA0LoRqD8AAACQ1Ki4vwAAAADyUqW/AAAAcKL8wb8AAAAADSS+vwAAAEipLsE/AAAAEOwAkT8AAABMKwbBPwAAAKhrI6m/AAAAAD0zqj8AAAAAdbu0vwAAAHTZ1sa/AAAAMO8GuD8AAABwhqq5PwAAAGA4grs/AAAAmPeZtz8AAABIQ1S5vwAAAHjAJLm/AAAA+CFSsT8AAABAZzHBPwAAAKDUELG/AAAAvUZY0D8AAABonIHJPwAAABgwrsG/AAAAYPG1qL8AAACwJdu7vwAAAIg0B7O/AAAAAGSeXT8AAABkcYPKvwAAAICjhZe/AAAAoCKivT8AAAAMUGu5vwAAAADCdaM/AAAAAHddgj8AAAAAJP6dPwAAAECnq5I/AAAA+OqnoL8AAADgcA+NPwAAACAsTrE/AAAA4GPVUT8AAAAgmVqnPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "dont",
      "violence"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Fairness, fairness is, you know, part of the word",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But you know, I’ve had stories that are written that are absolutely incorrect",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’ll tell you now and the word “intent”, as you know, is an important word, as you know, in libel",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’ll give you an example",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Some of the media, not all of it, but some of it, is very, very strong on – you know I get these massive crowds of people, and we’ll get protesters",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And these protesters are honestly, they’re very bad people",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " In many cases, they’re professionals",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Highly trained professionals",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I will rent an arena for 20,000 seats and they will come in – because there’s really no way – how you going to be able to tell – somebody said “oh you shouldn’t let ‘em in” – how you gonna know, you know? They walk in",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " [Inaudible] So we had an incident this weekend, which was amazing in Tucson, Arizona where a man, a protestor, wearing a Ku Klux Klan outfit, another one dragging an American flag, was walking out of the arena, and an African American man who was a supporter was sitting there listening to the speech and we had to stop because they were so loud – they’re so loud, these people, I don’t know what they do, they’re trained voices or something",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And they’re walking up and you saw it, because it was all over television, and the African American man became incensed I think the guy said something to him like you know what, like “screw you,” okay? Or worse",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think, because he looked over to him and said something to him and the guy just had it",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Now, they were together, these two",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " The one wearing a Ku Klux Klan, the other dragging a flag or something, but the African American man, who I think was an Air Force person, I just read he had a pretty stellar life so far",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And he just became incensed",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " So when I saw the television yesterday early in the morning I saw the Ku Klux Klan, I saw exactly what happened",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " By the time it got on to the national shows that was for the most part taken out",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They just had this African American smacking, you know, fighting",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And it didn’t make sense, you know, why, why",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But if you saw it in the morning it made a lot more sense",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We don’t condone violence at all but it’s very, very unfair reporting and we, you know…",
    "question": " How are you defining “incorrect?” It seems like you’re defining it as fairness or your view of fairness rather than accuracy.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHyVtr+rqqqiT1+Yv1VVVXVieLy/AAAAcN3dpr8AAADA3wq+P1VVVdVXD6I/AAAAbC60xj+rqqoKtEiTv1VVVVUMerI/q6qqauK2tT+rqqraAyiwv1VVVVWRX4M/q6qqygPtwL+rqqpal7u1v1VVVVVxkHM/AAAAgD7GnD8AAAAApvOsP1VVVW0VW7W/AAAA6NVKxT9VVVU1bXnKv1VVVRV17py/VVVV1b2Qxj8AAADgi96qv6uqqvp8f7C/VVVVtdm3uz9VVVWVihnNv6uqqkre2Me/AAAAAMjLhz8AAADAtk67P6uqqgrPirQ/AAAAgPid1j+rqqqyo1W4PwAAADAewby/q6qqSjQVyr9VVVUFAhCzv1VVVXWZAcq/q6qqytWZo79VVVVVNaqCv6uqqqpx6IO/q6qqytD/t7+rqqp6zaKlv1VVVQ1habe/AAAAQHKLkj9VVVXl5BTLPwAAAJA9+Mi/VVVVteIUpD9VVVVD/G+rvwAAADIESsA/AAAAICJ5sz+rqqqq6sW6Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "seems",
      "fairness",
      "fairness"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I would make it so that when someone writes incorrectly, yeah, I think I would get a little bit away from malice without having to get too totally away",
    "question": " But there’s standards like malice is required. Would you weaken that? Would you require less than malice for news organizations?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAKr/pr8AAIAdBRSkPwAAALjhy6y/AAAAyEUsu78AAACmXAV+vwAAAGgoa8A/AAAAYoZPyj8AAABcTMepvwAAAMA7Yqw/AAAAWlMLtj8AAADAGRKlPwAAAFpzmbo/AAAAOPH9tb8AAACy9lLDvwAAAEAam2O/AAAAEEo0oT8AABBvuACnPwAAAIDOzX8/AAAAIFsGrD8AAAD4knbEvwAAAKTHbLA/AAAAMN1jtj8AAAAM/8+vPwAAAHw/ObW/AAAAPJaJor8AAACkWKrBvwAAAMm2m7q/AAAALiVMpz8AAIDouoXCPwAAACAORoC/AAAAynCI0z8AAABwgNCIPwAAAIQPrra/AAAAhM2Bx78AAACMHW+0PwAAAPDnZ5+/AAAAKH8/xT8AAADJmGi+vwAAACffZrC/AAAAxoZKp78AAIDOHDiSPwAAAOwzi8G/AAAAJD5Qsz8AAADA4hq6PwAAAORN/cK/AAAA/Gxqwb8AAADAWBukvwAAAOAzwKA/AAAANho+uz8AAABgwiaAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "required.",
      "malice",
      "standards",
      "malice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Look, I think many of the stories about me are written badly",
    "question": " But there’s standards like malice is required. Would you weaken that? Would you require less than malice for news organizations?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAKr/pr8AAIAdBRSkPwAAALjhy6y/AAAAyEUsu78AAACmXAV+vwAAAGgoa8A/AAAAYoZPyj8AAABcTMepvwAAAMA7Yqw/AAAAWlMLtj8AAADAGRKlPwAAAFpzmbo/AAAAOPH9tb8AAACy9lLDvwAAAEAam2O/AAAAEEo0oT8AABBvuACnPwAAAIDOzX8/AAAAIFsGrD8AAAD4knbEvwAAAKTHbLA/AAAAMN1jtj8AAAAM/8+vPwAAAHw/ObW/AAAAPJaJor8AAACkWKrBvwAAAMm2m7q/AAAALiVMpz8AAIDouoXCPwAAACAORoC/AAAAynCI0z8AAABwgNCIPwAAAIQPrra/AAAAhM2Bx78AAACMHW+0PwAAAPDnZ5+/AAAAKH8/xT8AAADJmGi+vwAAACffZrC/AAAAxoZKp78AAIDOHDiSPwAAAOwzi8G/AAAAJD5Qsz8AAADA4hq6PwAAAORN/cK/AAAA/Gxqwb8AAADAWBukvwAAAOAzwKA/AAAANho+uz8AAABgwiaAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "required.",
      "malice",
      "standards",
      "malice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I don’t know if it’s malice because the people don’t know me",
    "question": " But there’s standards like malice is required. Would you weaken that? Would you require less than malice for news organizations?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAKr/pr8AAIAdBRSkPwAAALjhy6y/AAAAyEUsu78AAACmXAV+vwAAAGgoa8A/AAAAYoZPyj8AAABcTMepvwAAAMA7Yqw/AAAAWlMLtj8AAADAGRKlPwAAAFpzmbo/AAAAOPH9tb8AAACy9lLDvwAAAEAam2O/AAAAEEo0oT8AABBvuACnPwAAAIDOzX8/AAAAIFsGrD8AAAD4knbEvwAAAKTHbLA/AAAAMN1jtj8AAAAM/8+vPwAAAHw/ObW/AAAAPJaJor8AAACkWKrBvwAAAMm2m7q/AAAALiVMpz8AAIDouoXCPwAAACAORoC/AAAAynCI0z8AAABwgNCIPwAAAIQPrra/AAAAhM2Bx78AAACMHW+0PwAAAPDnZ5+/AAAAKH8/xT8AAADJmGi+vwAAACffZrC/AAAAxoZKp78AAIDOHDiSPwAAAOwzi8G/AAAAJD5Qsz8AAADA4hq6PwAAAORN/cK/AAAA/Gxqwb8AAADAWBukvwAAAOAzwKA/AAAANho+uz8AAABgwiaAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "required.",
      "malice",
      "standards",
      "malice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " When Charles writes about me or when Ruth writes about me, you know, we’ve never really met",
    "question": " But there’s standards like malice is required. Would you weaken that? Would you require less than malice for news organizations?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAKr/pr8AAIAdBRSkPwAAALjhy6y/AAAAyEUsu78AAACmXAV+vwAAAGgoa8A/AAAAYoZPyj8AAABcTMepvwAAAMA7Yqw/AAAAWlMLtj8AAADAGRKlPwAAAFpzmbo/AAAAOPH9tb8AAACy9lLDvwAAAEAam2O/AAAAEEo0oT8AABBvuACnPwAAAIDOzX8/AAAAIFsGrD8AAAD4knbEvwAAAKTHbLA/AAAAMN1jtj8AAAAM/8+vPwAAAHw/ObW/AAAAPJaJor8AAACkWKrBvwAAAMm2m7q/AAAALiVMpz8AAIDouoXCPwAAACAORoC/AAAAynCI0z8AAABwgNCIPwAAAIQPrra/AAAAhM2Bx78AAACMHW+0PwAAAPDnZ5+/AAAAKH8/xT8AAADJmGi+vwAAACffZrC/AAAAxoZKp78AAIDOHDiSPwAAAOwzi8G/AAAAJD5Qsz8AAADA4hq6PwAAAORN/cK/AAAA/Gxqwb8AAADAWBukvwAAAOAzwKA/AAAANho+uz8AAABgwiaAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "required.",
      "malice",
      "standards",
      "malice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I get these stories and they’re so angry and I actually say, I actually say, “How could they write?” – and many stories I must tell you, many stories are written that with a brief phone call could be corrected before they’re written",
    "question": " But there’s standards like malice is required. Would you weaken that? Would you require less than malice for news organizations?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAKr/pr8AAIAdBRSkPwAAALjhy6y/AAAAyEUsu78AAACmXAV+vwAAAGgoa8A/AAAAYoZPyj8AAABcTMepvwAAAMA7Yqw/AAAAWlMLtj8AAADAGRKlPwAAAFpzmbo/AAAAOPH9tb8AAACy9lLDvwAAAEAam2O/AAAAEEo0oT8AABBvuACnPwAAAIDOzX8/AAAAIFsGrD8AAAD4knbEvwAAAKTHbLA/AAAAMN1jtj8AAAAM/8+vPwAAAHw/ObW/AAAAPJaJor8AAACkWKrBvwAAAMm2m7q/AAAALiVMpz8AAIDouoXCPwAAACAORoC/AAAAynCI0z8AAABwgNCIPwAAAIQPrra/AAAAhM2Bx78AAACMHW+0PwAAAPDnZ5+/AAAAKH8/xT8AAADJmGi+vwAAACffZrC/AAAAxoZKp78AAIDOHDiSPwAAAOwzi8G/AAAAJD5Qsz8AAADA4hq6PwAAAORN/cK/AAAA/Gxqwb8AAADAWBukvwAAAOAzwKA/AAAANho+uz8AAABgwiaAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "required.",
      "malice",
      "standards",
      "malice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Nobody calls me",
    "question": " But there’s standards like malice is required. Would you weaken that? Would you require less than malice for news organizations?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAKr/pr8AAIAdBRSkPwAAALjhy6y/AAAAyEUsu78AAACmXAV+vwAAAGgoa8A/AAAAYoZPyj8AAABcTMepvwAAAMA7Yqw/AAAAWlMLtj8AAADAGRKlPwAAAFpzmbo/AAAAOPH9tb8AAACy9lLDvwAAAEAam2O/AAAAEEo0oT8AABBvuACnPwAAAIDOzX8/AAAAIFsGrD8AAAD4knbEvwAAAKTHbLA/AAAAMN1jtj8AAAAM/8+vPwAAAHw/ObW/AAAAPJaJor8AAACkWKrBvwAAAMm2m7q/AAAALiVMpz8AAIDouoXCPwAAACAORoC/AAAAynCI0z8AAABwgNCIPwAAAIQPrra/AAAAhM2Bx78AAACMHW+0PwAAAPDnZ5+/AAAAKH8/xT8AAADJmGi+vwAAACffZrC/AAAAxoZKp78AAIDOHDiSPwAAAOwzi8G/AAAAJD5Qsz8AAADA4hq6PwAAAORN/cK/AAAA/Gxqwb8AAADAWBukvwAAAOAzwKA/AAAANho+uz8AAABgwiaAPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "required.",
      "malice",
      "standards",
      "malice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I had one basic big libel suit, it was a very bad system, it was New Jersey",
    "question": " Well, now, you’ve been a plaintiff in libel suits so you know a little bit of the elements …",
    "question_vector": "AAAAsEa2hz8AAAAUg++yvwAAAGBzsra/AAAAWLy4oj8AAABwpz62PwAAAPY8FMI/AAAAg5vYuz8AAABA8FGHPwAAAKi6lK2/AAAAED3TsD8AAABwjdWDvwAAADGBXZg/AAAAHLfOk78AAACA641FPwAAAHAsp5c/AAAAwC+bVr8AAACAJvk5PwAAAOhtyKC/AAAAghmPhD8AAACoXyPOvwAAADz3JaG/AAAAaBrXsj8AAABA/VucvwAAACjXNaO/AAAAIJYUrb8AAADk9XvLvwAAABT3qMS/AAAA+BpIoj8AAADwJEm4PwAAAKA4zKm/AAAAOGi22j8AAACAoSazvwAAAMBTXnI/AAAAd/DWt78AAAA8NQ6dPwAAAID7TGQ/AAAAJLvvij8AAADYL16XvwAAAKCG7KC/AAAAvDYiwr8AACBZRtesPwAAAICVjGy/AAAAVDfztD8AAABEywvDPwAAAAqQVJk/AAAAOdbUsb8AAADg32WIPwAAAKCL/Ju/AAAAIAOYjL8AAACQZKKvPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "plaintiff",
      "suits",
      "bit",
      "elements"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I had a great judge, the first one, and I was going to win it",
    "question": " Well, now, you’ve been a plaintiff in libel suits so you know a little bit of the elements …",
    "question_vector": "AAAAsEa2hz8AAAAUg++yvwAAAGBzsra/AAAAWLy4oj8AAABwpz62PwAAAPY8FMI/AAAAg5vYuz8AAABA8FGHPwAAAKi6lK2/AAAAED3TsD8AAABwjdWDvwAAADGBXZg/AAAAHLfOk78AAACA641FPwAAAHAsp5c/AAAAwC+bVr8AAACAJvk5PwAAAOhtyKC/AAAAghmPhD8AAACoXyPOvwAAADz3JaG/AAAAaBrXsj8AAABA/VucvwAAACjXNaO/AAAAIJYUrb8AAADk9XvLvwAAABT3qMS/AAAA+BpIoj8AAADwJEm4PwAAAKA4zKm/AAAAOGi22j8AAACAoSazvwAAAMBTXnI/AAAAd/DWt78AAAA8NQ6dPwAAAID7TGQ/AAAAJLvvij8AAADYL16XvwAAAKCG7KC/AAAAvDYiwr8AACBZRtesPwAAAICVjGy/AAAAVDfztD8AAABEywvDPwAAAAqQVJk/AAAAOdbUsb8AAADg32WIPwAAAKCL/Ju/AAAAIAOYjL8AAACQZKKvPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "plaintiff",
      "suits",
      "bit",
      "elements"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And then I had another good judge, the second one, and then they kept switching judges",
    "question": " Well, now, you’ve been a plaintiff in libel suits so you know a little bit of the elements …",
    "question_vector": "AAAAsEa2hz8AAAAUg++yvwAAAGBzsra/AAAAWLy4oj8AAABwpz62PwAAAPY8FMI/AAAAg5vYuz8AAABA8FGHPwAAAKi6lK2/AAAAED3TsD8AAABwjdWDvwAAADGBXZg/AAAAHLfOk78AAACA641FPwAAAHAsp5c/AAAAwC+bVr8AAACAJvk5PwAAAOhtyKC/AAAAghmPhD8AAACoXyPOvwAAADz3JaG/AAAAaBrXsj8AAABA/VucvwAAACjXNaO/AAAAIJYUrb8AAADk9XvLvwAAABT3qMS/AAAA+BpIoj8AAADwJEm4PwAAAKA4zKm/AAAAOGi22j8AAACAoSazvwAAAMBTXnI/AAAAd/DWt78AAAA8NQ6dPwAAAID7TGQ/AAAAJLvvij8AAADYL16XvwAAAKCG7KC/AAAAvDYiwr8AACBZRtesPwAAAICVjGy/AAAAVDfztD8AAABEywvDPwAAAAqQVJk/AAAAOdbUsb8AAADg32WIPwAAAKCL/Ju/AAAAIAOYjL8AAACQZKKvPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "plaintiff",
      "suits",
      "bit",
      "elements"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And the third one was a bad judge",
    "question": " Well, now, you’ve been a plaintiff in libel suits so you know a little bit of the elements …",
    "question_vector": "AAAAsEa2hz8AAAAUg++yvwAAAGBzsra/AAAAWLy4oj8AAABwpz62PwAAAPY8FMI/AAAAg5vYuz8AAABA8FGHPwAAAKi6lK2/AAAAED3TsD8AAABwjdWDvwAAADGBXZg/AAAAHLfOk78AAACA641FPwAAAHAsp5c/AAAAwC+bVr8AAACAJvk5PwAAAOhtyKC/AAAAghmPhD8AAACoXyPOvwAAADz3JaG/AAAAaBrXsj8AAABA/VucvwAAACjXNaO/AAAAIJYUrb8AAADk9XvLvwAAABT3qMS/AAAA+BpIoj8AAADwJEm4PwAAAKA4zKm/AAAAOGi22j8AAACAoSazvwAAAMBTXnI/AAAAd/DWt78AAAA8NQ6dPwAAAID7TGQ/AAAAJLvvij8AAADYL16XvwAAAKCG7KC/AAAAvDYiwr8AACBZRtesPwAAAICVjGy/AAAAVDfztD8AAABEywvDPwAAAAqQVJk/AAAAOdbUsb8AAADg32WIPwAAAKCL/Ju/AAAAIAOYjL8AAACQZKKvPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "plaintiff",
      "suits",
      "bit",
      "elements"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " That’s what happened",
    "question": " Well, now, you’ve been a plaintiff in libel suits so you know a little bit of the elements …",
    "question_vector": "AAAAsEa2hz8AAAAUg++yvwAAAGBzsra/AAAAWLy4oj8AAABwpz62PwAAAPY8FMI/AAAAg5vYuz8AAABA8FGHPwAAAKi6lK2/AAAAED3TsD8AAABwjdWDvwAAADGBXZg/AAAAHLfOk78AAACA641FPwAAAHAsp5c/AAAAwC+bVr8AAACAJvk5PwAAAOhtyKC/AAAAghmPhD8AAACoXyPOvwAAADz3JaG/AAAAaBrXsj8AAABA/VucvwAAACjXNaO/AAAAIJYUrb8AAADk9XvLvwAAABT3qMS/AAAA+BpIoj8AAADwJEm4PwAAAKA4zKm/AAAAOGi22j8AAACAoSazvwAAAMBTXnI/AAAAd/DWt78AAAA8NQ6dPwAAAID7TGQ/AAAAJLvvij8AAADYL16XvwAAAKCG7KC/AAAAvDYiwr8AACBZRtesPwAAAICVjGy/AAAAVDfztD8AAABEywvDPwAAAAqQVJk/AAAAOdbUsb8AAADg32WIPwAAAKCL/Ju/AAAAIAOYjL8AAACQZKKvPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "plaintiff",
      "suits",
      "bit",
      "elements"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But, uh…",
    "question": " Well, now, you’ve been a plaintiff in libel suits so you know a little bit of the elements …",
    "question_vector": "AAAAsEa2hz8AAAAUg++yvwAAAGBzsra/AAAAWLy4oj8AAABwpz62PwAAAPY8FMI/AAAAg5vYuz8AAABA8FGHPwAAAKi6lK2/AAAAED3TsD8AAABwjdWDvwAAADGBXZg/AAAAHLfOk78AAACA641FPwAAAHAsp5c/AAAAwC+bVr8AAACAJvk5PwAAAOhtyKC/AAAAghmPhD8AAACoXyPOvwAAADz3JaG/AAAAaBrXsj8AAABA/VucvwAAACjXNaO/AAAAIJYUrb8AAADk9XvLvwAAABT3qMS/AAAA+BpIoj8AAADwJEm4PwAAAKA4zKm/AAAAOGi22j8AAACAoSazvwAAAMBTXnI/AAAAd/DWt78AAAA8NQ6dPwAAAID7TGQ/AAAAJLvvij8AAADYL16XvwAAAKCG7KC/AAAAvDYiwr8AACBZRtesPwAAAICVjGy/AAAAVDfztD8AAABEywvDPwAAAAqQVJk/AAAAOdbUsb8AAADg32WIPwAAAKCL/Ju/AAAAIAOYjL8AAACQZKKvPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "plaintiff",
      "suits",
      "bit",
      "elements"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " In a better world — no — in a better world I would be able to get a retraction or a correction",
    "question": " So in a better world would you be able to sue me?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHCwsr8AAADA/S7APwAAACBjb6u/AAAAgF2ywz8AAAAgFjikPwAAAACRcrm/AAAAgFvssL8AAACgvi60vwAAACDwors/AAAAQPp3lL8AAACgJMvAPwAAAGDsGJO/AAAA4IzDyr8AAADgp/a2PwAAAKDibs4/AAAAYIosiT8AAACAhoPAPwAAAIBGH6g/AAAAIMWMyr8AAAAAVauavwAAAEDGuXw/AAAAgPzcdz8AAACAR7GovwAAAMAoo6Y/AAAAANyysj8AAAAARDvSvwAAAGCWa8K/AAAAwNqkwL8AAACAPyCqvwAAACCPzbk/AAAAQAeN4z8AAADAh6DAPwAAAAAqCYC/AAAAAH0+m78AAABgsA/FvwAAAIAZs5e/AAAAAOq7qb8AAADgQzHBPwAAAEAyxcK/AAAAACKavr8AAAAgJ52xvwAAAECkCr2/AAAAILOfxj8AAAAAsnqivwAAAOAqFbU/AAAAQMVexj8AAAAg2TqdvwAAAACPu7S/AAAAwMb0sL8AAADAYm2+vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "world"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Not even a retraction, a correction",
    "question": " So in a better world would you be able to sue me?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAAHCwsr8AAADA/S7APwAAACBjb6u/AAAAgF2ywz8AAAAgFjikPwAAAACRcrm/AAAAgFvssL8AAACgvi60vwAAACDwors/AAAAQPp3lL8AAACgJMvAPwAAAGDsGJO/AAAA4IzDyr8AAADgp/a2PwAAAKDibs4/AAAAYIosiT8AAACAhoPAPwAAAIBGH6g/AAAAIMWMyr8AAAAAVauavwAAAEDGuXw/AAAAgPzcdz8AAACAR7GovwAAAMAoo6Y/AAAAANyysj8AAAAARDvSvwAAAGCWa8K/AAAAwNqkwL8AAACAPyCqvwAAACCPzbk/AAAAQAeN4z8AAADAh6DAPwAAAAAqCYC/AAAAAH0+m78AAABgsA/FvwAAAIAZs5e/AAAAAOq7qb8AAADgQzHBPwAAAEAyxcK/AAAAACKavr8AAAAgJ52xvwAAAECkCr2/AAAAILOfxj8AAAAAsnqivwAAAOAqFbU/AAAAQMVexj8AAAAg2TqdvwAAAACPu7S/AAAAwMb0sL8AAADAYm2+vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "world"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No, I would just say this",
    "question": " Would you expand, for example, prior restraints against publications?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoHrmk78AAABm2n6gPwAAAID4RVk/AACAafiWr78AAAAWPcOcvwAAAPz/oK4/AAAA8GgAnb8AAAC4kmzJvwAAAJil0rU/AAAAAQ3lhL8AAAC0dhKhPwAAAAIy6Kw/AAAAILXbfz8AAADgIRF3PwAAAFSODYE/AAAAlNo5tT8AAACYgbuTvwAAgLaFTJ6/AAAAlsoutj8AAAA0yA65vwAAgPJWLMA/AAAA3IIYsb8AAADg4TyhvwAAAACQ34m/AAAAfCg3sL8AAAAkWnXGvwAAAMDbeK6/AAAAeIpBsL8AAACAQTqUPwAAADQ+RZw/AAAAZJBI4D8AAADgKA2rPwAAAIprDoU/AAAA1BnXvb8AAADMX1uzvwAAAHgDnZE/AAAA9JAJoL8AAACK47+cPwAAAGTqdLy/AAAAIH65iT8AAABA64mMPwAAAPCI7JG/AAAA+IWVsD8AAADwGL++PwAAAFIvNKa/AAAAu6EPor8AAAAc/dmIvwAAAAwwQ6o/AAAAbcgvtL8AAABcoXGjPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "expand",
      "example",
      "restraints",
      "publications"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " All I want is fairness",
    "question": " Would you expand, for example, prior restraints against publications?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoHrmk78AAABm2n6gPwAAAID4RVk/AACAafiWr78AAAAWPcOcvwAAAPz/oK4/AAAA8GgAnb8AAAC4kmzJvwAAAJil0rU/AAAAAQ3lhL8AAAC0dhKhPwAAAAIy6Kw/AAAAILXbfz8AAADgIRF3PwAAAFSODYE/AAAAlNo5tT8AAACYgbuTvwAAgLaFTJ6/AAAAlsoutj8AAAA0yA65vwAAgPJWLMA/AAAA3IIYsb8AAADg4TyhvwAAAACQ34m/AAAAfCg3sL8AAAAkWnXGvwAAAMDbeK6/AAAAeIpBsL8AAACAQTqUPwAAADQ+RZw/AAAAZJBI4D8AAADgKA2rPwAAAIprDoU/AAAA1BnXvb8AAADMX1uzvwAAAHgDnZE/AAAA9JAJoL8AAACK47+cPwAAAGTqdLy/AAAAIH65iT8AAABA64mMPwAAAPCI7JG/AAAA+IWVsD8AAADwGL++PwAAAFIvNKa/AAAAu6EPor8AAAAc/dmIvwAAAAwwQ6o/AAAAbcgvtL8AAABcoXGjPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "expand",
      "example",
      "restraints",
      "publications"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " So unfair",
    "question": " Would you expand, for example, prior restraints against publications?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoHrmk78AAABm2n6gPwAAAID4RVk/AACAafiWr78AAAAWPcOcvwAAAPz/oK4/AAAA8GgAnb8AAAC4kmzJvwAAAJil0rU/AAAAAQ3lhL8AAAC0dhKhPwAAAAIy6Kw/AAAAILXbfz8AAADgIRF3PwAAAFSODYE/AAAAlNo5tT8AAACYgbuTvwAAgLaFTJ6/AAAAlsoutj8AAAA0yA65vwAAgPJWLMA/AAAA3IIYsb8AAADg4TyhvwAAAACQ34m/AAAAfCg3sL8AAAAkWnXGvwAAAMDbeK6/AAAAeIpBsL8AAACAQTqUPwAAADQ+RZw/AAAAZJBI4D8AAADgKA2rPwAAAIprDoU/AAAA1BnXvb8AAADMX1uzvwAAAHgDnZE/AAAA9JAJoL8AAACK47+cPwAAAGTqdLy/AAAAIH65iT8AAABA64mMPwAAAPCI7JG/AAAA+IWVsD8AAADwGL++PwAAAFIvNKa/AAAAu6EPor8AAAAc/dmIvwAAAAwwQ6o/AAAAbcgvtL8AAABcoXGjPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "expand",
      "example",
      "restraints",
      "publications"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I have stories and you have no recourse, you have no recourse whatsoever because the laws are really impotent",
    "question": " Would you expand, for example, prior restraints against publications?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoHrmk78AAABm2n6gPwAAAID4RVk/AACAafiWr78AAAAWPcOcvwAAAPz/oK4/AAAA8GgAnb8AAAC4kmzJvwAAAJil0rU/AAAAAQ3lhL8AAAC0dhKhPwAAAAIy6Kw/AAAAILXbfz8AAADgIRF3PwAAAFSODYE/AAAAlNo5tT8AAACYgbuTvwAAgLaFTJ6/AAAAlsoutj8AAAA0yA65vwAAgPJWLMA/AAAA3IIYsb8AAADg4TyhvwAAAACQ34m/AAAAfCg3sL8AAAAkWnXGvwAAAMDbeK6/AAAAeIpBsL8AAACAQTqUPwAAADQ+RZw/AAAAZJBI4D8AAADgKA2rPwAAAIprDoU/AAAA1BnXvb8AAADMX1uzvwAAAHgDnZE/AAAA9JAJoL8AAACK47+cPwAAAGTqdLy/AAAAIH65iT8AAABA64mMPwAAAPCI7JG/AAAA+IWVsD8AAADwGL++PwAAAFIvNKa/AAAAu6EPor8AAAAc/dmIvwAAAAwwQ6o/AAAAbcgvtL8AAABcoXGjPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "expand",
      "example",
      "restraints",
      "publications"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " What I would do, what I would do is I’d – well right now the libel laws, I mean I must tell you that the Hulk Hogan thing was a tremendous shock to me because – not only the amount and the fact that he had the victory — because for the most part I think libel laws almost don’t exist in this country, you know, based on, based on everything I’ve seen and watched and everything else, and I just think that if a paper writes something wrong — media, when I say paper I’m talking about media",
    "question": " But how would you fix that? You’ve said that you would open up the libel laws.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYC4xo78AAACwk+63vwAAAACp9K2/AAAAwB4XxD8AAACATbyqPwAAADhy57s/AAAAAAgOaj8AAAAA0hSKPwAAAICu354/AAAAAIMhhL8AAABwrYyvvwAAAFAlE6U/AAAAcDrMsr8AAADAmj29vwAAABCXtss/AAAAAGALeT8AAAC4grCdPwAAAOQ1X7q/AAAAADDaWr8AAADg3w6ZvwAAABClArM/AAAAUAGfvz8AAAC4Or1zvwAAANBkZr6/AAAAYOKSpr8AAADQJxrWvwAAAEDt3oy/AAAAAB0hnr8AAAC8iXqxvwAAAEB22pO/AAAA3CYv0j8AAADaZka1vwAAAEDuhmW/AAAAYseEnj8AAABYa3vAvwAAALTFHbe/AAAAwMxUpT8AAAAc14axvwAAANALj7E/AAAAgJWQmL8AAACAXC+uPwAAANh4y8E/AAAASDnxtz8AAADgw622PwAAAHzhEbA/AAAAEEBZs78AAAAgobHNvwAAADDdJb8/AAAApPQlsT8AAAAAepmqPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "said",
      "Youve",
      "libel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think that they can do a retraction if they’re wrong",
    "question": " But how would you fix that? You’ve said that you would open up the libel laws.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYC4xo78AAACwk+63vwAAAACp9K2/AAAAwB4XxD8AAACATbyqPwAAADhy57s/AAAAAAgOaj8AAAAA0hSKPwAAAICu354/AAAAAIMhhL8AAABwrYyvvwAAAFAlE6U/AAAAcDrMsr8AAADAmj29vwAAABCXtss/AAAAAGALeT8AAAC4grCdPwAAAOQ1X7q/AAAAADDaWr8AAADg3w6ZvwAAABClArM/AAAAUAGfvz8AAAC4Or1zvwAAANBkZr6/AAAAYOKSpr8AAADQJxrWvwAAAEDt3oy/AAAAAB0hnr8AAAC8iXqxvwAAAEB22pO/AAAA3CYv0j8AAADaZka1vwAAAEDuhmW/AAAAYseEnj8AAABYa3vAvwAAALTFHbe/AAAAwMxUpT8AAAAc14axvwAAANALj7E/AAAAgJWQmL8AAACAXC+uPwAAANh4y8E/AAAASDnxtz8AAADgw622PwAAAHzhEbA/AAAAEEBZs78AAAAgobHNvwAAADDdJb8/AAAApPQlsT8AAAAAepmqPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "said",
      "Youve",
      "libel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They should at least try to get it right",
    "question": " But how would you fix that? You’ve said that you would open up the libel laws.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYC4xo78AAACwk+63vwAAAACp9K2/AAAAwB4XxD8AAACATbyqPwAAADhy57s/AAAAAAgOaj8AAAAA0hSKPwAAAICu354/AAAAAIMhhL8AAABwrYyvvwAAAFAlE6U/AAAAcDrMsr8AAADAmj29vwAAABCXtss/AAAAAGALeT8AAAC4grCdPwAAAOQ1X7q/AAAAADDaWr8AAADg3w6ZvwAAABClArM/AAAAUAGfvz8AAAC4Or1zvwAAANBkZr6/AAAAYOKSpr8AAADQJxrWvwAAAEDt3oy/AAAAAB0hnr8AAAC8iXqxvwAAAEB22pO/AAAA3CYv0j8AAADaZka1vwAAAEDuhmW/AAAAYseEnj8AAABYa3vAvwAAALTFHbe/AAAAwMxUpT8AAAAc14axvwAAANALj7E/AAAAgJWQmL8AAACAXC+uPwAAANh4y8E/AAAASDnxtz8AAADgw622PwAAAHzhEbA/AAAAEEBZs78AAAAgobHNvwAAADDdJb8/AAAApPQlsT8AAAAAepmqPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "said",
      "Youve",
      "libel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And if they don’t do a retraction, they should, they should you know have a form of a trial",
    "question": " But how would you fix that? You’ve said that you would open up the libel laws.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYC4xo78AAACwk+63vwAAAACp9K2/AAAAwB4XxD8AAACATbyqPwAAADhy57s/AAAAAAgOaj8AAAAA0hSKPwAAAICu354/AAAAAIMhhL8AAABwrYyvvwAAAFAlE6U/AAAAcDrMsr8AAADAmj29vwAAABCXtss/AAAAAGALeT8AAAC4grCdPwAAAOQ1X7q/AAAAADDaWr8AAADg3w6ZvwAAABClArM/AAAAUAGfvz8AAAC4Or1zvwAAANBkZr6/AAAAYOKSpr8AAADQJxrWvwAAAEDt3oy/AAAAAB0hnr8AAAC8iXqxvwAAAEB22pO/AAAA3CYv0j8AAADaZka1vwAAAEDuhmW/AAAAYseEnj8AAABYa3vAvwAAALTFHbe/AAAAwMxUpT8AAAAc14axvwAAANALj7E/AAAAgJWQmL8AAACAXC+uPwAAANh4y8E/AAAASDnxtz8AAADgw622PwAAAHzhEbA/AAAAEEBZs78AAAAgobHNvwAAADDdJb8/AAAApPQlsT8AAAAAepmqPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "said",
      "Youve",
      "libel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I don’t want to impede free press, by the way",
    "question": " But how would you fix that? You’ve said that you would open up the libel laws.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYC4xo78AAACwk+63vwAAAACp9K2/AAAAwB4XxD8AAACATbyqPwAAADhy57s/AAAAAAgOaj8AAAAA0hSKPwAAAICu354/AAAAAIMhhL8AAABwrYyvvwAAAFAlE6U/AAAAcDrMsr8AAADAmj29vwAAABCXtss/AAAAAGALeT8AAAC4grCdPwAAAOQ1X7q/AAAAADDaWr8AAADg3w6ZvwAAABClArM/AAAAUAGfvz8AAAC4Or1zvwAAANBkZr6/AAAAYOKSpr8AAADQJxrWvwAAAEDt3oy/AAAAAB0hnr8AAAC8iXqxvwAAAEB22pO/AAAA3CYv0j8AAADaZka1vwAAAEDuhmW/AAAAYseEnj8AAABYa3vAvwAAALTFHbe/AAAAwMxUpT8AAAAc14axvwAAANALj7E/AAAAgJWQmL8AAACAXC+uPwAAANh4y8E/AAAASDnxtz8AAADgw622PwAAAHzhEbA/AAAAEEBZs78AAAAgobHNvwAAADDdJb8/AAAApPQlsT8AAAAAepmqPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "said",
      "Youve",
      "libel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " The last thing I would want to do is that",
    "question": " But how would you fix that? You’ve said that you would open up the libel laws.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYC4xo78AAACwk+63vwAAAACp9K2/AAAAwB4XxD8AAACATbyqPwAAADhy57s/AAAAAAgOaj8AAAAA0hSKPwAAAICu354/AAAAAIMhhL8AAABwrYyvvwAAAFAlE6U/AAAAcDrMsr8AAADAmj29vwAAABCXtss/AAAAAGALeT8AAAC4grCdPwAAAOQ1X7q/AAAAADDaWr8AAADg3w6ZvwAAABClArM/AAAAUAGfvz8AAAC4Or1zvwAAANBkZr6/AAAAYOKSpr8AAADQJxrWvwAAAEDt3oy/AAAAAB0hnr8AAAC8iXqxvwAAAEB22pO/AAAA3CYv0j8AAADaZka1vwAAAEDuhmW/AAAAYseEnj8AAABYa3vAvwAAALTFHbe/AAAAwMxUpT8AAAAc14axvwAAANALj7E/AAAAgJWQmL8AAACAXC+uPwAAANh4y8E/AAAASDnxtz8AAADgw622PwAAAHzhEbA/AAAAEEBZs78AAAAgobHNvwAAADDdJb8/AAAApPQlsT8AAAAAepmqPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "said",
      "Youve",
      "libel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But I mean I can only speak for – I probably get more – do I, I mean, you would know, do I get more publicity than any human being on the earth? Okay? I mean, [Editor’s note: Trump points at Ruth Marcus] she kills me, this one – that’s okay, nice woman",
    "question": " But how would you fix that? You’ve said that you would open up the libel laws.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYC4xo78AAACwk+63vwAAAACp9K2/AAAAwB4XxD8AAACATbyqPwAAADhy57s/AAAAAAgOaj8AAAAA0hSKPwAAAICu354/AAAAAIMhhL8AAABwrYyvvwAAAFAlE6U/AAAAcDrMsr8AAADAmj29vwAAABCXtss/AAAAAGALeT8AAAC4grCdPwAAAOQ1X7q/AAAAADDaWr8AAADg3w6ZvwAAABClArM/AAAAUAGfvz8AAAC4Or1zvwAAANBkZr6/AAAAYOKSpr8AAADQJxrWvwAAAEDt3oy/AAAAAB0hnr8AAAC8iXqxvwAAAEB22pO/AAAA3CYv0j8AAADaZka1vwAAAEDuhmW/AAAAYseEnj8AAABYa3vAvwAAALTFHbe/AAAAwMxUpT8AAAAc14axvwAAANALj7E/AAAAgJWQmL8AAACAXC+uPwAAANh4y8E/AAAASDnxtz8AAADgw622PwAAAHzhEbA/AAAAEEBZs78AAAAgobHNvwAAADDdJb8/AAAApPQlsT8AAAAAepmqPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "said",
      "Youve",
      "libel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Okay, look, I’ve had stories written about me – by your newspaper and by others – that are so false, that are written with such hatred – I’m not a bad person",
    "question": " My question is not so much why you feel they should be open but how. What presidential powers and executive actions would you take to open up the libel laws?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqKkOWpb+rqqqa6cyfv1VVVWW4OLm/q6qqbrWfpL+rqqqKLk2xP1VVVVXQUrw/VVVVpdDluD8AAAAQfSWqvwAAAEAKLm0/q6qqQtrpmL8AAAB4+iqhv6uqqnIP+8I/VVVVaX+Gqb+rqqq67LGePwAAAGDSl7E/AAAAaHPutD+rqqr6shmkPwAAAKCUbb2/AAAA+PTktD+rqqqqQU+yvwAAAMBdwK0/VVVViQFskT+rqqrqwcSAv6uqqiqRQ6a/q6qqqnZPdT+rqqpqfUbbv1VVVRVYGpe/q6qqSoddtL8AAACAuUOqP6uqqupX+Ys/AAAAYNGc3z9VVVVVbRhoP1VVVUV+ssa/AAAAIJc3zL9VVVUJkTicvwAAAODbx6G/VVVVdbfpob8AAABUSxOxv6uqqorWdr2/AAAAgAdthL+rqqrKYRq2vwAAADyfT6o/AAAAUEG+vj9VVVW1cN7EP6uqqrq1kcO/VVVV2WIisD+rqqoKCjalvwAAsHnifbk/q6qqsnxyYT9VVVXVvh+fvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "question",
      "powers",
      "laws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’m just doing my thing – I’m, you know, running, I want to do something that’s good",
    "question": " My question is not so much why you feel they should be open but how. What presidential powers and executive actions would you take to open up the libel laws?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqKkOWpb+rqqqa6cyfv1VVVWW4OLm/q6qqbrWfpL+rqqqKLk2xP1VVVVXQUrw/VVVVpdDluD8AAAAQfSWqvwAAAEAKLm0/q6qqQtrpmL8AAAB4+iqhv6uqqnIP+8I/VVVVaX+Gqb+rqqq67LGePwAAAGDSl7E/AAAAaHPutD+rqqr6shmkPwAAAKCUbb2/AAAA+PTktD+rqqqqQU+yvwAAAMBdwK0/VVVViQFskT+rqqrqwcSAv6uqqiqRQ6a/q6qqqnZPdT+rqqpqfUbbv1VVVRVYGpe/q6qqSoddtL8AAACAuUOqP6uqqupX+Ys/AAAAYNGc3z9VVVVVbRhoP1VVVUV+ssa/AAAAIJc3zL9VVVUJkTicvwAAAODbx6G/VVVVdbfpob8AAABUSxOxv6uqqorWdr2/AAAAgAdthL+rqqrKYRq2vwAAADyfT6o/AAAAUEG+vj9VVVW1cN7EP6uqqrq1kcO/VVVV2WIisD+rqqoKCjalvwAAsHnifbk/q6qqsnxyYT9VVVXVvh+fvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "question",
      "powers",
      "laws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " It’s not an easy thing to do",
    "question": " My question is not so much why you feel they should be open but how. What presidential powers and executive actions would you take to open up the libel laws?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqKkOWpb+rqqqa6cyfv1VVVWW4OLm/q6qqbrWfpL+rqqqKLk2xP1VVVVXQUrw/VVVVpdDluD8AAAAQfSWqvwAAAEAKLm0/q6qqQtrpmL8AAAB4+iqhv6uqqnIP+8I/VVVVaX+Gqb+rqqq67LGePwAAAGDSl7E/AAAAaHPutD+rqqr6shmkPwAAAKCUbb2/AAAA+PTktD+rqqqqQU+yvwAAAMBdwK0/VVVViQFskT+rqqrqwcSAv6uqqiqRQ6a/q6qqqnZPdT+rqqpqfUbbv1VVVRVYGpe/q6qqSoddtL8AAACAuUOqP6uqqupX+Ys/AAAAYNGc3z9VVVVVbRhoP1VVVUV+ssa/AAAAIJc3zL9VVVUJkTicvwAAAODbx6G/VVVVdbfpob8AAABUSxOxv6uqqorWdr2/AAAAgAdthL+rqqrKYRq2vwAAADyfT6o/AAAAUEG+vj9VVVW1cN7EP6uqqrq1kcO/VVVV2WIisD+rqqoKCjalvwAAsHnifbk/q6qqsnxyYT9VVVXVvh+fvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "question",
      "powers",
      "laws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I had a nice life until I did this, you know",
    "question": " My question is not so much why you feel they should be open but how. What presidential powers and executive actions would you take to open up the libel laws?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqKkOWpb+rqqqa6cyfv1VVVWW4OLm/q6qqbrWfpL+rqqqKLk2xP1VVVVXQUrw/VVVVpdDluD8AAAAQfSWqvwAAAEAKLm0/q6qqQtrpmL8AAAB4+iqhv6uqqnIP+8I/VVVVaX+Gqb+rqqq67LGePwAAAGDSl7E/AAAAaHPutD+rqqr6shmkPwAAAKCUbb2/AAAA+PTktD+rqqqqQU+yvwAAAMBdwK0/VVVViQFskT+rqqrqwcSAv6uqqiqRQ6a/q6qqqnZPdT+rqqpqfUbbv1VVVRVYGpe/q6qqSoddtL8AAACAuUOqP6uqqupX+Ys/AAAAYNGc3z9VVVVVbRhoP1VVVUV+ssa/AAAAIJc3zL9VVVUJkTicvwAAAODbx6G/VVVVdbfpob8AAABUSxOxv6uqqorWdr2/AAAAgAdthL+rqqrKYRq2vwAAADyfT6o/AAAAUEG+vj9VVVW1cN7EP6uqqrq1kcO/VVVV2WIisD+rqqoKCjalvwAAsHnifbk/q6qqsnxyYT9VVVXVvh+fvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "question",
      "powers",
      "laws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " This is a very difficult thing to do",
    "question": " My question is not so much why you feel they should be open but how. What presidential powers and executive actions would you take to open up the libel laws?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqKkOWpb+rqqqa6cyfv1VVVWW4OLm/q6qqbrWfpL+rqqqKLk2xP1VVVVXQUrw/VVVVpdDluD8AAAAQfSWqvwAAAEAKLm0/q6qqQtrpmL8AAAB4+iqhv6uqqnIP+8I/VVVVaX+Gqb+rqqq67LGePwAAAGDSl7E/AAAAaHPutD+rqqr6shmkPwAAAKCUbb2/AAAA+PTktD+rqqqqQU+yvwAAAMBdwK0/VVVViQFskT+rqqrqwcSAv6uqqiqRQ6a/q6qqqnZPdT+rqqpqfUbbv1VVVRVYGpe/q6qqSoddtL8AAACAuUOqP6uqqupX+Ys/AAAAYNGc3z9VVVVVbRhoP1VVVUV+ssa/AAAAIJc3zL9VVVUJkTicvwAAAODbx6G/VVVVdbfpob8AAABUSxOxv6uqqorWdr2/AAAAgAdthL+rqqrKYRq2vwAAADyfT6o/AAAAUEG+vj9VVVW1cN7EP6uqqrq1kcO/VVVV2WIisD+rqqoKCjalvwAAsHnifbk/q6qqsnxyYT9VVVXVvh+fvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "question",
      "powers",
      "laws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " In fact I’ve always heard that if you’re a very successful person you can’t run for office",
    "question": " My question is not so much why you feel they should be open but how. What presidential powers and executive actions would you take to open up the libel laws?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqKkOWpb+rqqqa6cyfv1VVVWW4OLm/q6qqbrWfpL+rqqqKLk2xP1VVVVXQUrw/VVVVpdDluD8AAAAQfSWqvwAAAEAKLm0/q6qqQtrpmL8AAAB4+iqhv6uqqnIP+8I/VVVVaX+Gqb+rqqq67LGePwAAAGDSl7E/AAAAaHPutD+rqqr6shmkPwAAAKCUbb2/AAAA+PTktD+rqqqqQU+yvwAAAMBdwK0/VVVViQFskT+rqqrqwcSAv6uqqiqRQ6a/q6qqqnZPdT+rqqpqfUbbv1VVVRVYGpe/q6qqSoddtL8AAACAuUOqP6uqqupX+Ys/AAAAYNGc3z9VVVVVbRhoP1VVVUV+ssa/AAAAIJc3zL9VVVUJkTicvwAAAODbx6G/VVVVdbfpob8AAABUSxOxv6uqqorWdr2/AAAAgAdthL+rqqrKYRq2vwAAADyfT6o/AAAAUEG+vj9VVVW1cN7EP6uqqrq1kcO/VVVV2WIisD+rqqoKCjalvwAAsHnifbk/q6qqsnxyYT9VVVXVvh+fvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "question",
      "powers",
      "laws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I can understand that",
    "question": " My question is not so much why you feel they should be open but how. What presidential powers and executive actions would you take to open up the libel laws?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqKkOWpb+rqqqa6cyfv1VVVWW4OLm/q6qqbrWfpL+rqqqKLk2xP1VVVVXQUrw/VVVVpdDluD8AAAAQfSWqvwAAAEAKLm0/q6qqQtrpmL8AAAB4+iqhv6uqqnIP+8I/VVVVaX+Gqb+rqqq67LGePwAAAGDSl7E/AAAAaHPutD+rqqr6shmkPwAAAKCUbb2/AAAA+PTktD+rqqqqQU+yvwAAAMBdwK0/VVVViQFskT+rqqrqwcSAv6uqqiqRQ6a/q6qqqnZPdT+rqqpqfUbbv1VVVRVYGpe/q6qqSoddtL8AAACAuUOqP6uqqupX+Ys/AAAAYNGc3z9VVVVVbRhoP1VVVUV+ssa/AAAAIJc3zL9VVVUJkTicvwAAAODbx6G/VVVVdbfpob8AAABUSxOxv6uqqorWdr2/AAAAgAdthL+rqqrKYRq2vwAAADyfT6o/AAAAUEG+vj9VVVW1cN7EP6uqqrq1kcO/VVVV2WIisD+rqqoKCjalvwAAsHnifbk/q6qqsnxyYT9VVVXVvh+fvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "question",
      "powers",
      "laws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You’ll do a hundred deals, and you’ll do one bad one or two bad ones — that’s all they read about are the bad ones",
    "question": " My question is not so much why you feel they should be open but how. What presidential powers and executive actions would you take to open up the libel laws?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqKkOWpb+rqqqa6cyfv1VVVWW4OLm/q6qqbrWfpL+rqqqKLk2xP1VVVVXQUrw/VVVVpdDluD8AAAAQfSWqvwAAAEAKLm0/q6qqQtrpmL8AAAB4+iqhv6uqqnIP+8I/VVVVaX+Gqb+rqqq67LGePwAAAGDSl7E/AAAAaHPutD+rqqr6shmkPwAAAKCUbb2/AAAA+PTktD+rqqqqQU+yvwAAAMBdwK0/VVVViQFskT+rqqrqwcSAv6uqqiqRQ6a/q6qqqnZPdT+rqqpqfUbbv1VVVRVYGpe/q6qqSoddtL8AAACAuUOqP6uqqupX+Ys/AAAAYNGc3z9VVVVVbRhoP1VVVUV+ssa/AAAAIJc3zL9VVVUJkTicvwAAAODbx6G/VVVVdbfpob8AAABUSxOxv6uqqorWdr2/AAAAgAdthL+rqqrKYRq2vwAAADyfT6o/AAAAUEG+vj9VVVW1cN7EP6uqqrq1kcO/VVVV2WIisD+rqqoKCjalvwAAsHnifbk/q6qqsnxyYT9VVVXVvh+fvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "question",
      "powers",
      "laws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They don’t read about the one hundred and fifty great ones that you had",
    "question": " My question is not so much why you feel they should be open but how. What presidential powers and executive actions would you take to open up the libel laws?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqKkOWpb+rqqqa6cyfv1VVVWW4OLm/q6qqbrWfpL+rqqqKLk2xP1VVVVXQUrw/VVVVpdDluD8AAAAQfSWqvwAAAEAKLm0/q6qqQtrpmL8AAAB4+iqhv6uqqnIP+8I/VVVVaX+Gqb+rqqq67LGePwAAAGDSl7E/AAAAaHPutD+rqqr6shmkPwAAAKCUbb2/AAAA+PTktD+rqqqqQU+yvwAAAMBdwK0/VVVViQFskT+rqqrqwcSAv6uqqiqRQ6a/q6qqqnZPdT+rqqpqfUbbv1VVVRVYGpe/q6qqSoddtL8AAACAuUOqP6uqqupX+Ys/AAAAYNGc3z9VVVVVbRhoP1VVVUV+ssa/AAAAIJc3zL9VVVUJkTicvwAAAODbx6G/VVVVdbfpob8AAABUSxOxv6uqqorWdr2/AAAAgAdthL+rqqrKYRq2vwAAADyfT6o/AAAAUEG+vj9VVVW1cN7EP6uqqrq1kcO/VVVV2WIisD+rqqoKCjalvwAAsHnifbk/q6qqsnxyYT9VVVXVvh+fvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "question",
      "powers",
      "laws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And even some of the ones they write that are good, they make them sound bad",
    "question": " My question is not so much why you feel they should be open but how. What presidential powers and executive actions would you take to open up the libel laws?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqKkOWpb+rqqqa6cyfv1VVVWW4OLm/q6qqbrWfpL+rqqqKLk2xP1VVVVXQUrw/VVVVpdDluD8AAAAQfSWqvwAAAEAKLm0/q6qqQtrpmL8AAAB4+iqhv6uqqnIP+8I/VVVVaX+Gqb+rqqq67LGePwAAAGDSl7E/AAAAaHPutD+rqqr6shmkPwAAAKCUbb2/AAAA+PTktD+rqqqqQU+yvwAAAMBdwK0/VVVViQFskT+rqqrqwcSAv6uqqiqRQ6a/q6qqqnZPdT+rqqpqfUbbv1VVVRVYGpe/q6qqSoddtL8AAACAuUOqP6uqqupX+Ys/AAAAYNGc3z9VVVVVbRhoP1VVVUV+ssa/AAAAIJc3zL9VVVUJkTicvwAAAODbx6G/VVVVdbfpob8AAABUSxOxv6uqqorWdr2/AAAAgAdthL+rqqrKYRq2vwAAADyfT6o/AAAAUEG+vj9VVVW1cN7EP6uqqrq1kcO/VVVV2WIisD+rqqoKCjalvwAAsHnifbk/q6qqsnxyYT9VVVXVvh+fvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "question",
      "powers",
      "laws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You know, so I’ve always heard that",
    "question": " My question is not so much why you feel they should be open but how. What presidential powers and executive actions would you take to open up the libel laws?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqKkOWpb+rqqqa6cyfv1VVVWW4OLm/q6qqbrWfpL+rqqqKLk2xP1VVVVXQUrw/VVVVpdDluD8AAAAQfSWqvwAAAEAKLm0/q6qqQtrpmL8AAAB4+iqhv6uqqnIP+8I/VVVVaX+Gqb+rqqq67LGePwAAAGDSl7E/AAAAaHPutD+rqqr6shmkPwAAAKCUbb2/AAAA+PTktD+rqqqqQU+yvwAAAMBdwK0/VVVViQFskT+rqqrqwcSAv6uqqiqRQ6a/q6qqqnZPdT+rqqpqfUbbv1VVVRVYGpe/q6qqSoddtL8AAACAuUOqP6uqqupX+Ys/AAAAYNGc3z9VVVVVbRhoP1VVVUV+ssa/AAAAIJc3zL9VVVUJkTicvwAAAODbx6G/VVVVdbfpob8AAABUSxOxv6uqqorWdr2/AAAAgAdthL+rqqrKYRq2vwAAADyfT6o/AAAAUEG+vj9VVVW1cN7EP6uqqrq1kcO/VVVV2WIisD+rqqoKCjalvwAAsHnifbk/q6qqsnxyYT9VVVXVvh+fvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "question",
      "powers",
      "laws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’ve heard that if you’re successful – very successful – you just can’t run for—",
    "question": " My question is not so much why you feel they should be open but how. What presidential powers and executive actions would you take to open up the libel laws?",
    "question_vector": "q6qqKkOWpb+rqqqa6cyfv1VVVWW4OLm/q6qqbrWfpL+rqqqKLk2xP1VVVVXQUrw/VVVVpdDluD8AAAAQfSWqvwAAAEAKLm0/q6qqQtrpmL8AAAB4+iqhv6uqqnIP+8I/VVVVaX+Gqb+rqqq67LGePwAAAGDSl7E/AAAAaHPutD+rqqr6shmkPwAAAKCUbb2/AAAA+PTktD+rqqqqQU+yvwAAAMBdwK0/VVVViQFskT+rqqrqwcSAv6uqqiqRQ6a/q6qqqnZPdT+rqqpqfUbbv1VVVRVYGpe/q6qqSoddtL8AAACAuUOqP6uqqupX+Ys/AAAAYNGc3z9VVVVVbRhoP1VVVUV+ssa/AAAAIJc3zL9VVVUJkTicvwAAAODbx6G/VVVVdbfpob8AAABUSxOxv6uqqorWdr2/AAAAgAdthL+rqqrKYRq2vwAAADyfT6o/AAAAUEG+vj9VVVW1cN7EP6uqqrq1kcO/VVVV2WIisD+rqqoKCjalvwAAsHnifbk/q6qqsnxyYT9VVVXVvh+fvw==",
    "important_question": [
      "question",
      "powers",
      "laws"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I might not have to, based on Gawker",
    "question": " Mr. Trump, you’ve mentioned many times during the campaign, in fact including this morning, instances you feel where the press has been biased or unfair or outright false in their reporting, and you’ve mentioned that you want to “open up” the libel laws. You’ve said that several times.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAuEkLoD8AAACA/YmqPwAAADBY6bA/AAAAkosGuT8AAACAI4puPwAAAHDYgpe/AAAAMnjHwL8AAAC8+Qy2vwAAAAANnaW/AAAACMrzpb8AAABKgWTCvwAAAMD4oG4/AAAAmHMJwr8AAADQHZCkvwAAANyev8E/AAAAXMcsrj8AAADg8PKAPwAAAEDH76K/AAAA+Ixrnr8AAAAQ0pqAvwAAAKDqsZ8/AAAApK9+sT8AAADicVOPPwAAANYjrKi/AAAAwLhler8AAABw5UrWvwAAAFBTU6y/AAAAUEfplz8AAABs57WMvwAAANAm54S/AAAATdyr2z8AAADu1wCsPwAAAPAd0qO/AACAlz3op78AAAAQ+2iovwAAACLLBLi/AACAz5hHmr8AAAB4wKOiPwAAAO7gRpO/AAAADEJgo78AAICd1yKsvwAAAKSiDbk/AAAA9U4ZiL8AAAAgXq+vPwAAAEDcUJu/AAAAMHfWk78AAAAPdA7BvwAAAHD98Xe/AAAA8saXpz8AAADA+5e5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "said",
      "Trump",
      "times",
      "campaign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Right?",
    "question": " Mr. Trump, you’ve mentioned many times during the campaign, in fact including this morning, instances you feel where the press has been biased or unfair or outright false in their reporting, and you’ve mentioned that you want to “open up” the libel laws. You’ve said that several times.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAuEkLoD8AAACA/YmqPwAAADBY6bA/AAAAkosGuT8AAACAI4puPwAAAHDYgpe/AAAAMnjHwL8AAAC8+Qy2vwAAAAANnaW/AAAACMrzpb8AAABKgWTCvwAAAMD4oG4/AAAAmHMJwr8AAADQHZCkvwAAANyev8E/AAAAXMcsrj8AAADg8PKAPwAAAEDH76K/AAAA+Ixrnr8AAAAQ0pqAvwAAAKDqsZ8/AAAApK9+sT8AAADicVOPPwAAANYjrKi/AAAAwLhler8AAABw5UrWvwAAAFBTU6y/AAAAUEfplz8AAABs57WMvwAAANAm54S/AAAATdyr2z8AAADu1wCsPwAAAPAd0qO/AACAlz3op78AAAAQ+2iovwAAACLLBLi/AACAz5hHmr8AAAB4wKOiPwAAAO7gRpO/AAAADEJgo78AAICd1yKsvwAAAKSiDbk/AAAA9U4ZiL8AAAAgXq+vPwAAAEDcUJu/AAAAMHfWk78AAAAPdA7BvwAAAHD98Xe/AAAA8saXpz8AAADA+5e5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "said",
      "Trump",
      "times",
      "campaign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think what’s different is we have a very divided country",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And whether we like it or not, it’s divided as bad as I’ve ever seen it",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I‘ve been, you know, I’ve been doing things for a long time",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I see it all the time",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean I see it so often",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I see it when we go out and we have 21,000 people in Phoenix, Arizona, the other day, the division – not so much Phoenix, because that was actually very smooth, there wasn’t even a minor, they did block a road, but after that, that was Sheriff Joe Arpaio, when the road was unblocked everyone left and it was fine",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But in Tucson, you can see the division",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You can see the division",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " There’s a racial division that’s incredible actually in the country",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think it’s as bad, I mean you have to say it’s as bad or almost as bad as it’s ever been",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And there’s a lack of spirit",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And one thing I thought that would happen, and it hasn’t happened, unfortunately, I thought that President Obama would be a great cheerleader for the country",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And it just hasn’t happened",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean we can say it has",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But it hasn’t happened",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " When you look at the Ferguson problems and the Baltimore problems and the Detroit problems",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And you know there’s a lack of spirit",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I actually think I’d be a great cheerleader – beyond other things, the other things that I’d do – I actually think I’d be a great cheerleader for the country",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Because a lot of people feel it’s a hopeless situation",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " A lot of people in the inner cities they feel that way",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And you have to start by giving them hope and giving them spirit and that has not taken place",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Just has not taken place",
    "question": " Can I follow up on that? I mean, to take the case of Baltimore, I mean one of the things that’s so remarkable about Baltimore and Detroit is that both of these cities, like many others have been – it’s not as if no one has ever said before we should have economic zones, it’s not as if no one has ever said before we need incentives and taxes etc., etc. And Baltimore received a lot of federal aid over the years. So I guess the question, then, is what’s different specifically about your approach to these issues from what’s been tried in the past, because a lot of effort has been put in just the direction you just described.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwEXaqT8AAACAPq6mPwAAAK7tvqi/AAAA8N1Mqj8AAAA9xa20PwAAAEBSG4E/AACQXuytob8AAAAgpJmQPwAAAABszjG/AAAA6++VoD8AAACgdlmqvwAAAGSZZqc/AAAAqO+Lt78AAACwoV6qvwAAAGRCILE/AAAA6NJdqD8AAACgMYuiPwAAANDuX6A/AAAA6nRBqr8AAAB4my2fPwAAgEzRVbS/AAAAlN3Llr8AAACy0gqZPwAAEFMb36g/AAAAIOBjmz8AAAAoNc7TvwAAAGCw07e/AAAAaOmDsz8AAIB98My2PwAAANNrN8G/AAAAmNqU1T8AAODl/Au0vwAAAAABWEK/AAAAuBAyur8AAADwIPOqPwAAAFzzmba/AAAAcBF2oj8AAAAUn7GwPwAAAPSzkbk/AAAAIOCEnT8AAIBX81uyvwAAACC94ae/AAAAAN8OY78AAAC6EbXCPwAAgP47go2/AAAAiIn4tD8AAABI8JODvwAAAHBbMJo/AAAAgEgfiz8AAABCEHW5Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "case",
      "Baltimore",
      "thats"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " That would concern me, Ruth",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " It would concern me",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But at the same time it can be solved to a large extant with jobs",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You know, if we can rebuild those communities and create incentives for companies to move in and create jobs",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Jobs are so important",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " There are no jobs",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " There are none",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You go to those communities and you can’t – there is nothing there",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " There is no incentive for people",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " It is a very sad situation",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And what makes it even sadder is that we are spending so much money in other countries and our own country has vast pockets of poverty and a lot of this is caused by the fact that there are no jobs",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " So we can create jobs in places like Baltimore and Detroit",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You know, Detroit made a move, but I don’t know but it just seems to be fizzling",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I don’t know what is going on",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I watched Detroit four, five years ago and it looked like they were really putting a full-court press on and it doesn’t seem to be, from what I’ve been told, friends of mine that are very much involved in that whole process that it doesn’t seem to be, doesn’t seem to be something that is being pursued like it should be pursued",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But if we can create jobs, it will solve so many problems",
    "question": " But Mr. Trump, if I could just follow up on Fred’s question. I think that what he was trying to get at was the anger in the African American community that held some of the riots and disturbances this summer about disparate treatment and about … clearly you say you’ve read where there is disparate treatment. But it is pretty undeniable that there is disproportionate incarceration of African Americans vs. whites. What would you – is that something that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfPbjqz8AAAA/hOecPwAAAEqqjqk/AAAA2bm7pz8AAADAPv+4PwAAAKigZGG/AAAAUJdPq78AAACACUp5vwAAAI6Mi7S/AAAAODcpoT8AAAD49aK+vwAAAFAcyrM/AAAAAKoFw78AAADLdamiPwAAAOD+zr4/AAAAfDPBxD8AAACYRmy/PwAAANiIJJq/AAAAOvejqT8AAAAxEoa3vwAAAMB+gW6/AAAAUIU/uj8AAAAeuRCXvwAAAJbYw6I/AAAAePTbsz8AAAD4V7bavwAAAADL476/AAAAoCmRkz8AAIAcyRK3PwAAAM6oS7+/AAAAbZK62z8AAACUyrC5PwAAAJj/Wr6/AAAASMKnt78AAABYLJF5vwAAABBIvLi/AADAozldr78AAACkUPqTPwAAAMBfqXq/AAAAEEy2ub8AAACYSgSzvwAAAMlPvqE/AACAxcHmnT8AAAAgAojFPwAAANA8q5a/AAAAYtv6nD8AAADsFA2rvwAAABCgN6M/AAAgZiZlqD8AAAAQPh20Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "think",
      "question.",
      "Trump",
      "trying"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’ve read where there are and I’ve read where there aren’t",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I mean, I’ve read both",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And, you know, I have no opinion on that",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Because frankly, what I’m saying is you know we have to create incentives for people to go back and to reinvigorate the areas and to put people to work",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": "  And you know we have lost million and millions of jobs to China and other countries",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And they’ve been taken out of this country, and when I say millions, you know it’s, it’s tremendous",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’ve seen 5 million jobs, I’ve seen numbers that range from 6 million to, to smaller numbers",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But it’s many millions of jobs, and it’s to countries all over",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Mexico is really becoming the new China",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I have great issue with that",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Because you know I use in speeches sometimes Ford or sometimes I use Carrier – it’s all the same: Ford, Carrier, Nabisco, so many of the companies — they’re moving to Mexico now",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And you know we shouldn’t be allowing that to happen",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And tremendous unemployment, tremendous",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They’re allowing tremendous people that have worked for the companies for a long time, they’re allowing, if they want to move around and they want to work on incentives within the United States, that’s one thing, but when they take these companies out of the United States",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Other countries are outsmarting us by giving them advantages, you know, like in the case of Mexico",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " In the case of many other countries",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Like Ireland is, you’re losing Pfizer to Ireland, a great pharmaceutical company that with many, many jobs and it’s going to move to Ireland",
    "question": " Well, forget Freddie Gray, but in general, do you believe there are disparities in law enforcement?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAeBrWrb8AAACARP2hPwAAAAJOW6u/AAAAF6JLrb8AAIB9f1KgPwAAAMAl55M/AAAAuBOhkr8AAAC4ZkS5vwAAAFBaYqw/AAAA7B67vL8AAAC77dOyvwAAAAAHZJQ/AAAANH3Fob8AAADwj3GsvwAAAHNTqrY/AAAAEEhQoT8AAAAqyHKlPwAAACSshbu/AAAAyBvjuT8AAAD0e/TDvwAAAM6nfbu/AAAAcJmRlj8AAADAmsB8PwAAAJBcG5i/AAAAUF8arL8AAEB791HMvwAAAKgYU7i/AAAAvOHlrT8AAAAsAoG9PwAAoEZVPqC/AAAA5AMM1j8AAAAE3O6zPwAAAH3bgJG/AAAASTajyr8AAACylG2ivwAAADQb+6U/AAAAGpJtub8AAAB6mLCivwAAAHgflaA/AACAhq3hrL8AAAAbDCO6vwAAABUMurY/AAAASgAJvD8AAACgA5+yPwAAANiY5JU/AAAAYBmEjr8AAAC0pSuZPwAAAABrjYG/AAAAALsaOz8AAAAw+2OrPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "forget",
      "Gray",
      "disparities",
      "enforcement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well, look, I mean, I have to see what happens with the trial",
    "question": " Do you see any racial disparities in law enforcement – I mean, what set it off was the Freddie Gray killing, as you know. Is that an issue that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQAq8ZL8AAAB4w3afPwAAAAB8zU8/AAAATp2Imr8AAAA7A5udPwAAAEpJyZS/AAAAcO3qkj8AAABKDAC5vwAAAKB9erA/AAAAClixsL8AAACW8empvwAAAECYdJm/AAAAiACJtL8AAADcI5WgvwAAANAhr7g/AACA1UhTpD8AAADIorWwPwAAACZFfsG/AAAAla50tz8AAABI0Pm9vwAAAHjOM5a/AAAA5MIWor8AAABQzZeevwAAAKAb5oA/AACAHtJ+qb8AAEDbN7jPvwAAADj6Baq/AAAAyNX1mb8AAADuZTuoPwAAAFCX35S/AAAAooxB4T8AAACZGYGxPwAAANDSeKS/AAAAFeB/yb8AAACkIpuSvwAAAHCX44Y/AAAAsKLNor8AAAAk74SXvwAAAIAYOHS/AAAAeuLuhr8AAMCcdRa+vwAAAHbRMKo/AAAAoIT/vT8AAACM0AG0PwAAALj7w5m/AAAAwBufcr8AAAAo2x6wPwAAAPAXcKk/AAAAFDG7ij8AAAAAOnhMPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "see",
      "enforcement",
      "disparities",
      "set"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I—",
    "question": " Do you see any racial disparities in law enforcement – I mean, what set it off was the Freddie Gray killing, as you know. Is that an issue that concerns you?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQAq8ZL8AAAB4w3afPwAAAAB8zU8/AAAATp2Imr8AAAA7A5udPwAAAEpJyZS/AAAAcO3qkj8AAABKDAC5vwAAAKB9erA/AAAAClixsL8AAACW8empvwAAAECYdJm/AAAAiACJtL8AAADcI5WgvwAAANAhr7g/AACA1UhTpD8AAADIorWwPwAAACZFfsG/AAAAla50tz8AAABI0Pm9vwAAAHjOM5a/AAAA5MIWor8AAABQzZeevwAAAKAb5oA/AACAHtJ+qb8AAEDbN7jPvwAAADj6Baq/AAAAyNX1mb8AAADuZTuoPwAAAFCX35S/AAAAooxB4T8AAACZGYGxPwAAANDSeKS/AAAAFeB/yb8AAACkIpuSvwAAAHCX44Y/AAAAsKLNor8AAAAk74SXvwAAAIAYOHS/AAAAeuLuhr8AAMCcdRa+vwAAAHbRMKo/AAAAoIT/vT8AAACM0AG0PwAAALj7w5m/AAAAwBufcr8AAAAo2x6wPwAAAPAXcKk/AAAAFDG7ij8AAAAAOnhMPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "see",
      "enforcement",
      "disparities",
      "set"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well I’ve never really see anything that – you know, I feel very strongly about law enforcement",
    "question": " The root of many people’s unhappiness in Baltimore was the perception that blacks are treated differently by law enforcement. And the disproportionate – do you think it’s a problem that the percentage of blacks in prison is higher than whites, and what do you think is the root of that situation?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoNKwgL8AAACMtXu7PwAAAMRh0pm/AAAAHgi6mD8AAABix5qgPwAAABASw7I/AAAAAPMDYD8AAABgFleUPwAAfuaIyKK/AAAAnBC7lj8AAAA8XNKFvwAAAPJfM6o/AAAAg4SUpb8AAAAM1lm9vwAAALyz5La/AAAA8Ly3iD8AAAAcYL6zvwAAAELQwqa/AAAA4M85pT8AAADAM5qNvwAAgLQH5LW/AAAA+OAfqL8AAAABcmCpPwAAABi9/p6/AAAAtE1Pqj8AAAAYNd3KvwAAAJQc4q6/AAAAUHI3qT8AAAD4p+XBPwAAAEDLKns/AAAA8tkk1T8AACDSwMS2PwAAAJDiv6s/AAAAvKIMzb8AAADoKje5vwAAAJghj6O/AAAA9LEZw78AAAAc6e60vwAAAMinaKo/AAAAkPjRgL8AAAAwGuSUvwAAAMbSL7C/AAAAmNkbvr8AAAAIMYK6PwAAADkwxLA/AAAAPLiFtD8AAAAANimWPwAAAIycDbk/AAAAAIxULb8AAADwAet5vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "perception",
      "unhappiness",
      "Baltimore",
      "root"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And, you know, if you look at the riot that took place over the summer, if that were stopped – it all, it mostly took place on the first evening, and if that were stopped on the first evening, you know, you’d have a much nicer city right now, because much of that damage and much of the destruction was done on Evening One",
    "question": " The root of many people’s unhappiness in Baltimore was the perception that blacks are treated differently by law enforcement. And the disproportionate – do you think it’s a problem that the percentage of blacks in prison is higher than whites, and what do you think is the root of that situation?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoNKwgL8AAACMtXu7PwAAAMRh0pm/AAAAHgi6mD8AAABix5qgPwAAABASw7I/AAAAAPMDYD8AAABgFleUPwAAfuaIyKK/AAAAnBC7lj8AAAA8XNKFvwAAAPJfM6o/AAAAg4SUpb8AAAAM1lm9vwAAALyz5La/AAAA8Ly3iD8AAAAcYL6zvwAAAELQwqa/AAAA4M85pT8AAADAM5qNvwAAgLQH5LW/AAAA+OAfqL8AAAABcmCpPwAAABi9/p6/AAAAtE1Pqj8AAAAYNd3KvwAAAJQc4q6/AAAAUHI3qT8AAAD4p+XBPwAAAEDLKns/AAAA8tkk1T8AACDSwMS2PwAAAJDiv6s/AAAAvKIMzb8AAADoKje5vwAAAJghj6O/AAAA9LEZw78AAAAc6e60vwAAAMinaKo/AAAAkPjRgL8AAAAwGuSUvwAAAMbSL7C/AAAAmNkbvr8AAAAIMYK6PwAAADkwxLA/AAAAPLiFtD8AAAAANimWPwAAAIycDbk/AAAAAIxULb8AAADwAet5vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "perception",
      "unhappiness",
      "Baltimore",
      "root"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " So I feel that law enforcement, it’s got to play a big role",
    "question": " The root of many people’s unhappiness in Baltimore was the perception that blacks are treated differently by law enforcement. And the disproportionate – do you think it’s a problem that the percentage of blacks in prison is higher than whites, and what do you think is the root of that situation?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoNKwgL8AAACMtXu7PwAAAMRh0pm/AAAAHgi6mD8AAABix5qgPwAAABASw7I/AAAAAPMDYD8AAABgFleUPwAAfuaIyKK/AAAAnBC7lj8AAAA8XNKFvwAAAPJfM6o/AAAAg4SUpb8AAAAM1lm9vwAAALyz5La/AAAA8Ly3iD8AAAAcYL6zvwAAAELQwqa/AAAA4M85pT8AAADAM5qNvwAAgLQH5LW/AAAA+OAfqL8AAAABcmCpPwAAABi9/p6/AAAAtE1Pqj8AAAAYNd3KvwAAAJQc4q6/AAAAUHI3qT8AAAD4p+XBPwAAAEDLKns/AAAA8tkk1T8AACDSwMS2PwAAAJDiv6s/AAAAvKIMzb8AAADoKje5vwAAAJghj6O/AAAA9LEZw78AAAAc6e60vwAAAMinaKo/AAAAkPjRgL8AAAAwGuSUvwAAAMbSL7C/AAAAmNkbvr8AAAAIMYK6PwAAADkwxLA/AAAAPLiFtD8AAAAANimWPwAAAIycDbk/AAAAAIxULb8AAADwAet5vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "perception",
      "unhappiness",
      "Baltimore",
      "root"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " It’s got to play a big role",
    "question": " The root of many people’s unhappiness in Baltimore was the perception that blacks are treated differently by law enforcement. And the disproportionate – do you think it’s a problem that the percentage of blacks in prison is higher than whites, and what do you think is the root of that situation?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoNKwgL8AAACMtXu7PwAAAMRh0pm/AAAAHgi6mD8AAABix5qgPwAAABASw7I/AAAAAPMDYD8AAABgFleUPwAAfuaIyKK/AAAAnBC7lj8AAAA8XNKFvwAAAPJfM6o/AAAAg4SUpb8AAAAM1lm9vwAAALyz5La/AAAA8Ly3iD8AAAAcYL6zvwAAAELQwqa/AAAA4M85pT8AAADAM5qNvwAAgLQH5LW/AAAA+OAfqL8AAAABcmCpPwAAABi9/p6/AAAAtE1Pqj8AAAAYNd3KvwAAAJQc4q6/AAAAUHI3qT8AAAD4p+XBPwAAAEDLKns/AAAA8tkk1T8AACDSwMS2PwAAAJDiv6s/AAAAvKIMzb8AAADoKje5vwAAAJghj6O/AAAA9LEZw78AAAAc6e60vwAAAMinaKo/AAAAkPjRgL8AAAAwGuSUvwAAAMbSL7C/AAAAmNkbvr8AAAAIMYK6PwAAADkwxLA/AAAAPLiFtD8AAAAANimWPwAAAIycDbk/AAAAAIxULb8AAADwAet5vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "perception",
      "unhappiness",
      "Baltimore",
      "root"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But that’s a pretty good example, because tremendous amounts of damage was done that first evening – first two evenings, but the first evening in particular",
    "question": " The root of many people’s unhappiness in Baltimore was the perception that blacks are treated differently by law enforcement. And the disproportionate – do you think it’s a problem that the percentage of blacks in prison is higher than whites, and what do you think is the root of that situation?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoNKwgL8AAACMtXu7PwAAAMRh0pm/AAAAHgi6mD8AAABix5qgPwAAABASw7I/AAAAAPMDYD8AAABgFleUPwAAfuaIyKK/AAAAnBC7lj8AAAA8XNKFvwAAAPJfM6o/AAAAg4SUpb8AAAAM1lm9vwAAALyz5La/AAAA8Ly3iD8AAAAcYL6zvwAAAELQwqa/AAAA4M85pT8AAADAM5qNvwAAgLQH5LW/AAAA+OAfqL8AAAABcmCpPwAAABi9/p6/AAAAtE1Pqj8AAAAYNd3KvwAAAJQc4q6/AAAAUHI3qT8AAAD4p+XBPwAAAEDLKns/AAAA8tkk1T8AACDSwMS2PwAAAJDiv6s/AAAAvKIMzb8AAADoKje5vwAAAJghj6O/AAAA9LEZw78AAAAc6e60vwAAAMinaKo/AAAAkPjRgL8AAAAwGuSUvwAAAMbSL7C/AAAAmNkbvr8AAAAIMYK6PwAAADkwxLA/AAAAPLiFtD8AAAAANimWPwAAAIycDbk/AAAAAIxULb8AAADwAet5vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "perception",
      "unhappiness",
      "Baltimore",
      "root"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And so I’m a very strong believer in law enforcement, but I’m also a very strong believer that the inner cities can come back",
    "question": " The root of many people’s unhappiness in Baltimore was the perception that blacks are treated differently by law enforcement. And the disproportionate – do you think it’s a problem that the percentage of blacks in prison is higher than whites, and what do you think is the root of that situation?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAoNKwgL8AAACMtXu7PwAAAMRh0pm/AAAAHgi6mD8AAABix5qgPwAAABASw7I/AAAAAPMDYD8AAABgFleUPwAAfuaIyKK/AAAAnBC7lj8AAAA8XNKFvwAAAPJfM6o/AAAAg4SUpb8AAAAM1lm9vwAAALyz5La/AAAA8Ly3iD8AAAAcYL6zvwAAAELQwqa/AAAA4M85pT8AAADAM5qNvwAAgLQH5LW/AAAA+OAfqL8AAAABcmCpPwAAABi9/p6/AAAAtE1Pqj8AAAAYNd3KvwAAAJQc4q6/AAAAUHI3qT8AAAD4p+XBPwAAAEDLKns/AAAA8tkk1T8AACDSwMS2PwAAAJDiv6s/AAAAvKIMzb8AAADoKje5vwAAAJghj6O/AAAA9LEZw78AAAAc6e60vwAAAMinaKo/AAAAkPjRgL8AAAAwGuSUvwAAAMbSL7C/AAAAmNkbvr8AAAAIMYK6PwAAADkwxLA/AAAAPLiFtD8AAAAANimWPwAAAIycDbk/AAAAAIxULb8AAADwAet5vw==",
    "important_question": [
      "perception",
      "unhappiness",
      "Baltimore",
      "root"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well, number one, I’d create economic zones",
    "question": " So what would you do for Baltimore, let’s say.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwAypmr8AAADoBhq0PwAAANLD5b0/AAAALNM2sj8AAADENAigPwAAAMCMJ7u/AAAAsJSXzL8AAABAPOuNPwAAAAA9inu/AAAArPzAqD8AAADeLIe0vwAAAKxIebg/AAAAAPc+lD8AAABQ2lOrPwAAAADtNn+/AAAAYC6+oD8AAADstXmwvwAAAKCDwqa/AAAAwBbtrL8AAABA3oqlvwAAAI4Xn6g/AAAAgLBXgD8AAABwiQC0vwAAANbdgcA/AAAAABT4aD8AAAAQoePNvwAAADBZuq0/AAAAgNxHs78AAABQLOrBPwAAAFBTydC/AAAAIGw/1j8AAIBoCCCoPwAAAMB92Ka/AAAA4FCAvr8AAADAfgWcPwAAAABk9Xw/AAAAhNqwoD8AAADgbriavwAAACRlE7k/AAAAAOrfpr8AAABA07CjPwAAAABpWY6/AAAAIBxbkL8AAAAgSwbBPwAAAAC7Y5q/AAAA6vs7uz8AAABAq0utPwAAANCmqbi/AAAAeB4eor8AAAAYiL7CPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Baltimore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’d create incentives for companies to move in",
    "question": " So what would you do for Baltimore, let’s say.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwAypmr8AAADoBhq0PwAAANLD5b0/AAAALNM2sj8AAADENAigPwAAAMCMJ7u/AAAAsJSXzL8AAABAPOuNPwAAAAA9inu/AAAArPzAqD8AAADeLIe0vwAAAKxIebg/AAAAAPc+lD8AAABQ2lOrPwAAAADtNn+/AAAAYC6+oD8AAADstXmwvwAAAKCDwqa/AAAAwBbtrL8AAABA3oqlvwAAAI4Xn6g/AAAAgLBXgD8AAABwiQC0vwAAANbdgcA/AAAAABT4aD8AAAAQoePNvwAAADBZuq0/AAAAgNxHs78AAABQLOrBPwAAAFBTydC/AAAAIGw/1j8AAIBoCCCoPwAAAMB92Ka/AAAA4FCAvr8AAADAfgWcPwAAAABk9Xw/AAAAhNqwoD8AAADgbriavwAAACRlE7k/AAAAAOrfpr8AAABA07CjPwAAAABpWY6/AAAAIBxbkL8AAAAgSwbBPwAAAAC7Y5q/AAAA6vs7uz8AAABAq0utPwAAANCmqbi/AAAAeB4eor8AAAAYiL7CPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Baltimore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’d work on spirit because the spirit is so low, it’s incredible, the unemployment, you look at unemployment for black youth in this country, African American youth, is 58-59 percent",
    "question": " So what would you do for Baltimore, let’s say.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwAypmr8AAADoBhq0PwAAANLD5b0/AAAALNM2sj8AAADENAigPwAAAMCMJ7u/AAAAsJSXzL8AAABAPOuNPwAAAAA9inu/AAAArPzAqD8AAADeLIe0vwAAAKxIebg/AAAAAPc+lD8AAABQ2lOrPwAAAADtNn+/AAAAYC6+oD8AAADstXmwvwAAAKCDwqa/AAAAwBbtrL8AAABA3oqlvwAAAI4Xn6g/AAAAgLBXgD8AAABwiQC0vwAAANbdgcA/AAAAABT4aD8AAAAQoePNvwAAADBZuq0/AAAAgNxHs78AAABQLOrBPwAAAFBTydC/AAAAIGw/1j8AAIBoCCCoPwAAAMB92Ka/AAAA4FCAvr8AAADAfgWcPwAAAABk9Xw/AAAAhNqwoD8AAADgbriavwAAACRlE7k/AAAAAOrfpr8AAABA07CjPwAAAABpWY6/AAAAIBxbkL8AAAAgSwbBPwAAAAC7Y5q/AAAA6vs7uz8AAABAq0utPwAAANCmqbi/AAAAeB4eor8AAAAYiL7CPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Baltimore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " It’s unthinkable",
    "question": " So what would you do for Baltimore, let’s say.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwAypmr8AAADoBhq0PwAAANLD5b0/AAAALNM2sj8AAADENAigPwAAAMCMJ7u/AAAAsJSXzL8AAABAPOuNPwAAAAA9inu/AAAArPzAqD8AAADeLIe0vwAAAKxIebg/AAAAAPc+lD8AAABQ2lOrPwAAAADtNn+/AAAAYC6+oD8AAADstXmwvwAAAKCDwqa/AAAAwBbtrL8AAABA3oqlvwAAAI4Xn6g/AAAAgLBXgD8AAABwiQC0vwAAANbdgcA/AAAAABT4aD8AAAAQoePNvwAAADBZuq0/AAAAgNxHs78AAABQLOrBPwAAAFBTydC/AAAAIGw/1j8AAIBoCCCoPwAAAMB92Ka/AAAA4FCAvr8AAADAfgWcPwAAAABk9Xw/AAAAhNqwoD8AAADgbriavwAAACRlE7k/AAAAAOrfpr8AAABA07CjPwAAAABpWY6/AAAAIBxbkL8AAAAgSwbBPwAAAAC7Y5q/AAAA6vs7uz8AAABAq0utPwAAANCmqbi/AAAAeB4eor8AAAAYiL7CPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Baltimore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Unemployment for African Americans – not youth, but African Americans – is very high",
    "question": " So what would you do for Baltimore, let’s say.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwAypmr8AAADoBhq0PwAAANLD5b0/AAAALNM2sj8AAADENAigPwAAAMCMJ7u/AAAAsJSXzL8AAABAPOuNPwAAAAA9inu/AAAArPzAqD8AAADeLIe0vwAAAKxIebg/AAAAAPc+lD8AAABQ2lOrPwAAAADtNn+/AAAAYC6+oD8AAADstXmwvwAAAKCDwqa/AAAAwBbtrL8AAABA3oqlvwAAAI4Xn6g/AAAAgLBXgD8AAABwiQC0vwAAANbdgcA/AAAAABT4aD8AAAAQoePNvwAAADBZuq0/AAAAgNxHs78AAABQLOrBPwAAAFBTydC/AAAAIGw/1j8AAIBoCCCoPwAAAMB92Ka/AAAA4FCAvr8AAADAfgWcPwAAAABk9Xw/AAAAhNqwoD8AAADgbriavwAAACRlE7k/AAAAAOrfpr8AAABA07CjPwAAAABpWY6/AAAAIBxbkL8AAAAgSwbBPwAAAAC7Y5q/AAAA6vs7uz8AAABAq0utPwAAANCmqbi/AAAAeB4eor8AAAAYiL7CPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Baltimore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I would create in the inner cities, which is what I really do best, that’s why when I open a building and I show you it’s way ahead of schedule, under budget and everything else—I think it was the Rite Aid store, the store in Baltimore it took them 20 years to get it built, one store, and then it burned down in one night—we have to create incentives for people to love what they are doing, and to make money",
    "question": " So what would you do for Baltimore, let’s say.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwAypmr8AAADoBhq0PwAAANLD5b0/AAAALNM2sj8AAADENAigPwAAAMCMJ7u/AAAAsJSXzL8AAABAPOuNPwAAAAA9inu/AAAArPzAqD8AAADeLIe0vwAAAKxIebg/AAAAAPc+lD8AAABQ2lOrPwAAAADtNn+/AAAAYC6+oD8AAADstXmwvwAAAKCDwqa/AAAAwBbtrL8AAABA3oqlvwAAAI4Xn6g/AAAAgLBXgD8AAABwiQC0vwAAANbdgcA/AAAAABT4aD8AAAAQoePNvwAAADBZuq0/AAAAgNxHs78AAABQLOrBPwAAAFBTydC/AAAAIGw/1j8AAIBoCCCoPwAAAMB92Ka/AAAA4FCAvr8AAADAfgWcPwAAAABk9Xw/AAAAhNqwoD8AAADgbriavwAAACRlE7k/AAAAAOrfpr8AAABA07CjPwAAAABpWY6/AAAAIBxbkL8AAAAgSwbBPwAAAAC7Y5q/AAAA6vs7uz8AAABAq0utPwAAANCmqbi/AAAAeB4eor8AAAAYiL7CPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Baltimore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And to create, you know, to really create a better life for themselves",
    "question": " So what would you do for Baltimore, let’s say.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwAypmr8AAADoBhq0PwAAANLD5b0/AAAALNM2sj8AAADENAigPwAAAMCMJ7u/AAAAsJSXzL8AAABAPOuNPwAAAAA9inu/AAAArPzAqD8AAADeLIe0vwAAAKxIebg/AAAAAPc+lD8AAABQ2lOrPwAAAADtNn+/AAAAYC6+oD8AAADstXmwvwAAAKCDwqa/AAAAwBbtrL8AAABA3oqlvwAAAI4Xn6g/AAAAgLBXgD8AAABwiQC0vwAAANbdgcA/AAAAABT4aD8AAAAQoePNvwAAADBZuq0/AAAAgNxHs78AAABQLOrBPwAAAFBTydC/AAAAIGw/1j8AAIBoCCCoPwAAAMB92Ka/AAAA4FCAvr8AAADAfgWcPwAAAABk9Xw/AAAAhNqwoD8AAADgbriavwAAACRlE7k/AAAAAOrfpr8AAABA07CjPwAAAABpWY6/AAAAIBxbkL8AAAAgSwbBPwAAAAC7Y5q/AAAA6vs7uz8AAABAq0utPwAAANCmqbi/AAAAeB4eor8AAAAYiL7CPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Baltimore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And you can’t – it doesn’t seem right that you will have a situation like Baltimore, and many other places, let’s use Baltimore as an example, there are many Baltimores in this country",
    "question": " So what would you do for Baltimore, let’s say.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwAypmr8AAADoBhq0PwAAANLD5b0/AAAALNM2sj8AAADENAigPwAAAMCMJ7u/AAAAsJSXzL8AAABAPOuNPwAAAAA9inu/AAAArPzAqD8AAADeLIe0vwAAAKxIebg/AAAAAPc+lD8AAABQ2lOrPwAAAADtNn+/AAAAYC6+oD8AAADstXmwvwAAAKCDwqa/AAAAwBbtrL8AAABA3oqlvwAAAI4Xn6g/AAAAgLBXgD8AAABwiQC0vwAAANbdgcA/AAAAABT4aD8AAAAQoePNvwAAADBZuq0/AAAAgNxHs78AAABQLOrBPwAAAFBTydC/AAAAIGw/1j8AAIBoCCCoPwAAAMB92Ka/AAAA4FCAvr8AAADAfgWcPwAAAABk9Xw/AAAAhNqwoD8AAADgbriavwAAACRlE7k/AAAAAOrfpr8AAABA07CjPwAAAABpWY6/AAAAIBxbkL8AAAAgSwbBPwAAAAC7Y5q/AAAA6vs7uz8AAABAq0utPwAAANCmqbi/AAAAeB4eor8AAAAYiL7CPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Baltimore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Detroit is maybe even a better example than Baltimore",
    "question": " So what would you do for Baltimore, let’s say.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwAypmr8AAADoBhq0PwAAANLD5b0/AAAALNM2sj8AAADENAigPwAAAMCMJ7u/AAAAsJSXzL8AAABAPOuNPwAAAAA9inu/AAAArPzAqD8AAADeLIe0vwAAAKxIebg/AAAAAPc+lD8AAABQ2lOrPwAAAADtNn+/AAAAYC6+oD8AAADstXmwvwAAAKCDwqa/AAAAwBbtrL8AAABA3oqlvwAAAI4Xn6g/AAAAgLBXgD8AAABwiQC0vwAAANbdgcA/AAAAABT4aD8AAAAQoePNvwAAADBZuq0/AAAAgNxHs78AAABQLOrBPwAAAFBTydC/AAAAIGw/1j8AAIBoCCCoPwAAAMB92Ka/AAAA4FCAvr8AAADAfgWcPwAAAABk9Xw/AAAAhNqwoD8AAADgbriavwAAACRlE7k/AAAAAOrfpr8AAABA07CjPwAAAABpWY6/AAAAIBxbkL8AAAAgSwbBPwAAAAC7Y5q/AAAA6vs7uz8AAABAq0utPwAAANCmqbi/AAAAeB4eor8AAAAYiL7CPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Baltimore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But that you’ll have a situation like that, and then we’re over nation building with other, with countries that in many cases don’t want us there",
    "question": " So what would you do for Baltimore, let’s say.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwAypmr8AAADoBhq0PwAAANLD5b0/AAAALNM2sj8AAADENAigPwAAAMCMJ7u/AAAAsJSXzL8AAABAPOuNPwAAAAA9inu/AAAArPzAqD8AAADeLIe0vwAAAKxIebg/AAAAAPc+lD8AAABQ2lOrPwAAAADtNn+/AAAAYC6+oD8AAADstXmwvwAAAKCDwqa/AAAAwBbtrL8AAABA3oqlvwAAAI4Xn6g/AAAAgLBXgD8AAABwiQC0vwAAANbdgcA/AAAAABT4aD8AAAAQoePNvwAAADBZuq0/AAAAgNxHs78AAABQLOrBPwAAAFBTydC/AAAAIGw/1j8AAIBoCCCoPwAAAMB92Ka/AAAA4FCAvr8AAADAfgWcPwAAAABk9Xw/AAAAhNqwoD8AAADgbriavwAAACRlE7k/AAAAAOrfpr8AAABA07CjPwAAAABpWY6/AAAAIBxbkL8AAAAgSwbBPwAAAAC7Y5q/AAAA6vs7uz8AAABAq0utPwAAANCmqbi/AAAAeB4eor8AAAAYiL7CPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Baltimore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " They want our money, but they don’t want us",
    "question": " So what would you do for Baltimore, let’s say.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAwAypmr8AAADoBhq0PwAAANLD5b0/AAAALNM2sj8AAADENAigPwAAAMCMJ7u/AAAAsJSXzL8AAABAPOuNPwAAAAA9inu/AAAArPzAqD8AAADeLIe0vwAAAKxIebg/AAAAAPc+lD8AAABQ2lOrPwAAAADtNn+/AAAAYC6+oD8AAADstXmwvwAAAKCDwqa/AAAAwBbtrL8AAABA3oqlvwAAAI4Xn6g/AAAAgLBXgD8AAABwiQC0vwAAANbdgcA/AAAAABT4aD8AAAAQoePNvwAAADBZuq0/AAAAgNxHs78AAABQLOrBPwAAAFBTydC/AAAAIGw/1j8AAIBoCCCoPwAAAMB92Ka/AAAA4FCAvr8AAADAfgWcPwAAAABk9Xw/AAAAhNqwoD8AAADgbriavwAAACRlE7k/AAAAAOrfpr8AAABA07CjPwAAAABpWY6/AAAAIBxbkL8AAAAgSwbBPwAAAAC7Y5q/AAAA6vs7uz8AAABAq0utPwAAANCmqbi/AAAAeB4eor8AAAAYiL7CPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "lets",
      "Baltimore"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well, there is, I just think that we have values in our country that we have to promote",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We have a country that is in bad shape, it’s in bad condition",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You look at our inner cities, our inner cities are a horrible mess",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I watched Baltimore, I have many, many friends in Baltimore, we watched what happened",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " St",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Louis, Ferguson, Oakland, it could have been much worse over the summer",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And it will probably be worse this summer",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But you look at some of our inner cities",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And yet you know I watched as we built schools in Iraq and they’d be blown up",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And we’d build another one and it would get blown up",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And we would rebuild it three times",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And yet we can’t build a school in Brooklyn",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We have no money for education, because we can’t build in our own country",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And at what point do you say hey, we have to take care of ourselves",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " So, you know, I know the outer world exists and I’ll be very cognizant of that but at the same time, our country is disintegrating, large sections of it, especially in the inner cities",
    "question": " Short of nation building, is there any role in promoting values or democracy? Or that’s not something…",
    "question_vector": "AAAAOH8ksj8AAAAIWMS7PwAAAGGb0aq/AAAA8ElYnr8AAADsp/7FPwAAAGRKvrE/AACAC+kNcj8AAIBC9T3BvwAAAFD3lIe/AAAAiOOThz8AAACwVm+aPwAAABALm6o/AAAAJwBNtL8AAABY+ziPvwAAQIkbkqW/AAAAILHtqT8AAADarsGwPwAAAMhBwa0/AAAA9M6Znj8AAABEfSiVvwAAAGCcBJ4/AAAAqE/pij8AAICZsWi3vwAAACD5imQ/AAAAwCFucb8AAACYdb3RvwAAAPLKwbi/AAAAABeaeD8AAACSmkKiPwAAAKYCVqk/AAAAiK1H5D8AAABYLmygvwAAAMBaPFU/AAAABMbGxb8AAADYhHmEvwAAAAB4RZG/AAAAyKzolL8AAACecmOEPwAAADiZ/qS/AAAAADDti78AAACDVBOovwAAALDq1aa/AAAA8HpWnb8AAACAfT5vPwAAAPHo9bK/AAAAMCRnqT8AAAAMkiytvwAAALSPAqC/AAAAopkolT8AAACshFamPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "is",
      "building",
      "role",
      "values"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I do think it’s a different world today and I don’t think we should be nation building anymore",
    "question": " George Shultz, it’s interesting, was associated with a foreign policy of Reagan that was very much devoted to promoting democracy and freedom overseas. Is that something you think in today’s world the United States should be doing?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYCSZq78AAEB8dvevPwAAALAN8Fk/AACAmXDIur8AAACgaR6CPwAAAM2RQaA/AAAA3kgho78AAAC2oQa0vwAAAAxT1MC/AAAAGKOJtL8AAAAkkfvFvwAAAOi8YsI/AAAAvBY4sL8AAAD8E4igPwAAgMCFQpU/AAAAADl2VL8AAACA635xvwAAAIB/5qM/AAAA92M8wD8AAKgTBtGcvwAAABirVKm/AABAOlNwnD8AAABA/xpgvwAAAGjlxce/AAAAFKmWuD8AAAByNy3VvwAAACA/vZO/AAAAuk1RqT8AAACxFMakPwAAAPCFc54/AAAAmJfL0D8AAABCLCGVvwAAAGyBDba/AAAA3DtJwr8AAABArwS1vwAAADZ2wqK/AAAAIBqfo78AAADGm0q2PwAAAE4mG5C/AAAAmqHTp78AAACkqAW+vwAAAJwfFqQ/AAAAsKhDlj8AAAAAv2FsPwAAAOCJM4m/AAAA/NJEtD8AAIB0ETq4vwAAAPDdB7E/AAAArMK1rb8AAAAYyHTGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "something",
      "Shultz",
      "policy",
      "Reagan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think it’s proven not to work",
    "question": " George Shultz, it’s interesting, was associated with a foreign policy of Reagan that was very much devoted to promoting democracy and freedom overseas. Is that something you think in today’s world the United States should be doing?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYCSZq78AAEB8dvevPwAAALAN8Fk/AACAmXDIur8AAACgaR6CPwAAAM2RQaA/AAAA3kgho78AAAC2oQa0vwAAAAxT1MC/AAAAGKOJtL8AAAAkkfvFvwAAAOi8YsI/AAAAvBY4sL8AAAD8E4igPwAAgMCFQpU/AAAAADl2VL8AAACA635xvwAAAIB/5qM/AAAA92M8wD8AAKgTBtGcvwAAABirVKm/AABAOlNwnD8AAABA/xpgvwAAAGjlxce/AAAAFKmWuD8AAAByNy3VvwAAACA/vZO/AAAAuk1RqT8AAACxFMakPwAAAPCFc54/AAAAmJfL0D8AAABCLCGVvwAAAGyBDba/AAAA3DtJwr8AAABArwS1vwAAADZ2wqK/AAAAIBqfo78AAADGm0q2PwAAAE4mG5C/AAAAmqHTp78AAACkqAW+vwAAAJwfFqQ/AAAAsKhDlj8AAAAAv2FsPwAAAOCJM4m/AAAA/NJEtD8AAIB0ETq4vwAAAPDdB7E/AAAArMK1rb8AAAAYyHTGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "something",
      "Shultz",
      "policy",
      "Reagan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And we have a different country than we did then",
    "question": " George Shultz, it’s interesting, was associated with a foreign policy of Reagan that was very much devoted to promoting democracy and freedom overseas. Is that something you think in today’s world the United States should be doing?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYCSZq78AAEB8dvevPwAAALAN8Fk/AACAmXDIur8AAACgaR6CPwAAAM2RQaA/AAAA3kgho78AAAC2oQa0vwAAAAxT1MC/AAAAGKOJtL8AAAAkkfvFvwAAAOi8YsI/AAAAvBY4sL8AAAD8E4igPwAAgMCFQpU/AAAAADl2VL8AAACA635xvwAAAIB/5qM/AAAA92M8wD8AAKgTBtGcvwAAABirVKm/AABAOlNwnD8AAABA/xpgvwAAAGjlxce/AAAAFKmWuD8AAAByNy3VvwAAACA/vZO/AAAAuk1RqT8AAACxFMakPwAAAPCFc54/AAAAmJfL0D8AAABCLCGVvwAAAGyBDba/AAAA3DtJwr8AAABArwS1vwAAADZ2wqK/AAAAIBqfo78AAADGm0q2PwAAAE4mG5C/AAAAmqHTp78AAACkqAW+vwAAAJwfFqQ/AAAAsKhDlj8AAAAAv2FsPwAAAOCJM4m/AAAA/NJEtD8AAIB0ETq4vwAAAPDdB7E/AAAArMK1rb8AAAAYyHTGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "something",
      "Shultz",
      "policy",
      "Reagan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You know we have 19 trillion dollars in debt",
    "question": " George Shultz, it’s interesting, was associated with a foreign policy of Reagan that was very much devoted to promoting democracy and freedom overseas. Is that something you think in today’s world the United States should be doing?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYCSZq78AAEB8dvevPwAAALAN8Fk/AACAmXDIur8AAACgaR6CPwAAAM2RQaA/AAAA3kgho78AAAC2oQa0vwAAAAxT1MC/AAAAGKOJtL8AAAAkkfvFvwAAAOi8YsI/AAAAvBY4sL8AAAD8E4igPwAAgMCFQpU/AAAAADl2VL8AAACA635xvwAAAIB/5qM/AAAA92M8wD8AAKgTBtGcvwAAABirVKm/AABAOlNwnD8AAABA/xpgvwAAAGjlxce/AAAAFKmWuD8AAAByNy3VvwAAACA/vZO/AAAAuk1RqT8AAACxFMakPwAAAPCFc54/AAAAmJfL0D8AAABCLCGVvwAAAGyBDba/AAAA3DtJwr8AAABArwS1vwAAADZ2wqK/AAAAIBqfo78AAADGm0q2PwAAAE4mG5C/AAAAmqHTp78AAACkqAW+vwAAAJwfFqQ/AAAAsKhDlj8AAAAAv2FsPwAAAOCJM4m/AAAA/NJEtD8AAIB0ETq4vwAAAPDdB7E/AAAArMK1rb8AAAAYyHTGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "something",
      "Shultz",
      "policy",
      "Reagan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We’re sitting probably on a bubble and, you know, it’s a bubble that if it breaks is going to be very nasty",
    "question": " George Shultz, it’s interesting, was associated with a foreign policy of Reagan that was very much devoted to promoting democracy and freedom overseas. Is that something you think in today’s world the United States should be doing?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYCSZq78AAEB8dvevPwAAALAN8Fk/AACAmXDIur8AAACgaR6CPwAAAM2RQaA/AAAA3kgho78AAAC2oQa0vwAAAAxT1MC/AAAAGKOJtL8AAAAkkfvFvwAAAOi8YsI/AAAAvBY4sL8AAAD8E4igPwAAgMCFQpU/AAAAADl2VL8AAACA635xvwAAAIB/5qM/AAAA92M8wD8AAKgTBtGcvwAAABirVKm/AABAOlNwnD8AAABA/xpgvwAAAGjlxce/AAAAFKmWuD8AAAByNy3VvwAAACA/vZO/AAAAuk1RqT8AAACxFMakPwAAAPCFc54/AAAAmJfL0D8AAABCLCGVvwAAAGyBDba/AAAA3DtJwr8AAABArwS1vwAAADZ2wqK/AAAAIBqfo78AAADGm0q2PwAAAE4mG5C/AAAAmqHTp78AAACkqAW+vwAAAJwfFqQ/AAAAsKhDlj8AAAAAv2FsPwAAAOCJM4m/AAAA/NJEtD8AAIB0ETq4vwAAAPDdB7E/AAAArMK1rb8AAAAYyHTGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "something",
      "Shultz",
      "policy",
      "Reagan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And I just think we have to rebuild our country",
    "question": " George Shultz, it’s interesting, was associated with a foreign policy of Reagan that was very much devoted to promoting democracy and freedom overseas. Is that something you think in today’s world the United States should be doing?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYCSZq78AAEB8dvevPwAAALAN8Fk/AACAmXDIur8AAACgaR6CPwAAAM2RQaA/AAAA3kgho78AAAC2oQa0vwAAAAxT1MC/AAAAGKOJtL8AAAAkkfvFvwAAAOi8YsI/AAAAvBY4sL8AAAD8E4igPwAAgMCFQpU/AAAAADl2VL8AAACA635xvwAAAIB/5qM/AAAA92M8wD8AAKgTBtGcvwAAABirVKm/AABAOlNwnD8AAABA/xpgvwAAAGjlxce/AAAAFKmWuD8AAAByNy3VvwAAACA/vZO/AAAAuk1RqT8AAACxFMakPwAAAPCFc54/AAAAmJfL0D8AAABCLCGVvwAAAGyBDba/AAAA3DtJwr8AAABArwS1vwAAADZ2wqK/AAAAIBqfo78AAADGm0q2PwAAAE4mG5C/AAAAmqHTp78AAACkqAW+vwAAAJwfFqQ/AAAAsKhDlj8AAAAAv2FsPwAAAOCJM4m/AAAA/NJEtD8AAIB0ETq4vwAAAPDdB7E/AAAArMK1rb8AAAAYyHTGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "something",
      "Shultz",
      "policy",
      "Reagan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " If you look at the infrastructure — I just landed at an airport where, not in good shape, not in good shape",
    "question": " George Shultz, it’s interesting, was associated with a foreign policy of Reagan that was very much devoted to promoting democracy and freedom overseas. Is that something you think in today’s world the United States should be doing?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYCSZq78AAEB8dvevPwAAALAN8Fk/AACAmXDIur8AAACgaR6CPwAAAM2RQaA/AAAA3kgho78AAAC2oQa0vwAAAAxT1MC/AAAAGKOJtL8AAAAkkfvFvwAAAOi8YsI/AAAAvBY4sL8AAAD8E4igPwAAgMCFQpU/AAAAADl2VL8AAACA635xvwAAAIB/5qM/AAAA92M8wD8AAKgTBtGcvwAAABirVKm/AABAOlNwnD8AAABA/xpgvwAAAGjlxce/AAAAFKmWuD8AAAByNy3VvwAAACA/vZO/AAAAuk1RqT8AAACxFMakPwAAAPCFc54/AAAAmJfL0D8AAABCLCGVvwAAAGyBDba/AAAA3DtJwr8AAABArwS1vwAAADZ2wqK/AAAAIBqfo78AAADGm0q2PwAAAE4mG5C/AAAAmqHTp78AAACkqAW+vwAAAJwfFqQ/AAAAsKhDlj8AAAAAv2FsPwAAAOCJM4m/AAAA/NJEtD8AAIB0ETq4vwAAAPDdB7E/AAAArMK1rb8AAAAYyHTGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "something",
      "Shultz",
      "policy",
      "Reagan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " If you go to Qatar and if you go to (inaudible) you see airports the likes of which you have never seen before",
    "question": " George Shultz, it’s interesting, was associated with a foreign policy of Reagan that was very much devoted to promoting democracy and freedom overseas. Is that something you think in today’s world the United States should be doing?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYCSZq78AAEB8dvevPwAAALAN8Fk/AACAmXDIur8AAACgaR6CPwAAAM2RQaA/AAAA3kgho78AAAC2oQa0vwAAAAxT1MC/AAAAGKOJtL8AAAAkkfvFvwAAAOi8YsI/AAAAvBY4sL8AAAD8E4igPwAAgMCFQpU/AAAAADl2VL8AAACA635xvwAAAIB/5qM/AAAA92M8wD8AAKgTBtGcvwAAABirVKm/AABAOlNwnD8AAABA/xpgvwAAAGjlxce/AAAAFKmWuD8AAAByNy3VvwAAACA/vZO/AAAAuk1RqT8AAACxFMakPwAAAPCFc54/AAAAmJfL0D8AAABCLCGVvwAAAGyBDba/AAAA3DtJwr8AAABArwS1vwAAADZ2wqK/AAAAIBqfo78AAADGm0q2PwAAAE4mG5C/AAAAmqHTp78AAACkqAW+vwAAAJwfFqQ/AAAAsKhDlj8AAAAAv2FsPwAAAOCJM4m/AAAA/NJEtD8AAIB0ETq4vwAAAPDdB7E/AAAArMK1rb8AAAAYyHTGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "something",
      "Shultz",
      "policy",
      "Reagan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Dubai, different places in China",
    "question": " George Shultz, it’s interesting, was associated with a foreign policy of Reagan that was very much devoted to promoting democracy and freedom overseas. Is that something you think in today’s world the United States should be doing?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYCSZq78AAEB8dvevPwAAALAN8Fk/AACAmXDIur8AAACgaR6CPwAAAM2RQaA/AAAA3kgho78AAAC2oQa0vwAAAAxT1MC/AAAAGKOJtL8AAAAkkfvFvwAAAOi8YsI/AAAAvBY4sL8AAAD8E4igPwAAgMCFQpU/AAAAADl2VL8AAACA635xvwAAAIB/5qM/AAAA92M8wD8AAKgTBtGcvwAAABirVKm/AABAOlNwnD8AAABA/xpgvwAAAGjlxce/AAAAFKmWuD8AAAByNy3VvwAAACA/vZO/AAAAuk1RqT8AAACxFMakPwAAAPCFc54/AAAAmJfL0D8AAABCLCGVvwAAAGyBDba/AAAA3DtJwr8AAABArwS1vwAAADZ2wqK/AAAAIBqfo78AAADGm0q2PwAAAE4mG5C/AAAAmqHTp78AAACkqAW+vwAAAJwfFqQ/AAAAsKhDlj8AAAAAv2FsPwAAAOCJM4m/AAAA/NJEtD8AAIB0ETq4vwAAAPDdB7E/AAAArMK1rb8AAAAYyHTGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "something",
      "Shultz",
      "policy",
      "Reagan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " You see infrastructure, you see airports, other things, the likes of which you have never seen here",
    "question": " George Shultz, it’s interesting, was associated with a foreign policy of Reagan that was very much devoted to promoting democracy and freedom overseas. Is that something you think in today’s world the United States should be doing?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAYCSZq78AAEB8dvevPwAAALAN8Fk/AACAmXDIur8AAACgaR6CPwAAAM2RQaA/AAAA3kgho78AAAC2oQa0vwAAAAxT1MC/AAAAGKOJtL8AAAAkkfvFvwAAAOi8YsI/AAAAvBY4sL8AAAD8E4igPwAAgMCFQpU/AAAAADl2VL8AAACA635xvwAAAIB/5qM/AAAA92M8wD8AAKgTBtGcvwAAABirVKm/AABAOlNwnD8AAABA/xpgvwAAAGjlxce/AAAAFKmWuD8AAAByNy3VvwAAACA/vZO/AAAAuk1RqT8AAACxFMakPwAAAPCFc54/AAAAmJfL0D8AAABCLCGVvwAAAGyBDba/AAAA3DtJwr8AAABArwS1vwAAADZ2wqK/AAAAIBqfo78AAADGm0q2PwAAAE4mG5C/AAAAmqHTp78AAACkqAW+vwAAAJwfFqQ/AAAAsKhDlj8AAAAAv2FsPwAAAOCJM4m/AAAA/NJEtD8AAIB0ETq4vwAAAPDdB7E/AAAArMK1rb8AAAAYyHTGPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "something",
      "Shultz",
      "policy",
      "Reagan"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well, because I know so many of them, and because in many cases I like them, I hate to get totally involved",
    "question": " If I could, I’d start by asking is there a secretary of state and a secretary of defense in the modern era who you think have done a good job? Who do you think were the best?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAUhecs78AAADgbyuGPwAAAHQWBaA/AAAACLtqpj8AAAA4+fajPwAAAJ6CTbS/AAAARG1Mur8AAABAuhmNvwAAAIDWb5A/AAAAc5sswL8AAAAgr16jvwAAAGCWKJY/AAAAYI22lr8AAAAAKGcdPwAAAPDc1as/AAAAq6Vchj8AAIBnxnatvwAAAFCZxay/AAAAAE3urD8AAAD2Qh6UPwAAALChSYY/AAAA6iResL8AAAAsIoCPPwAAAHxr8p6/AAAA4BA8jL8AAAA8JqbUvwAAAEC/c4A/AAAACHR5pr8AAACA83ORvwAAAAjH662/AAAAZDma3z8AAAD4u0OkPwAAALhad8W/AAAAZKZBs78AAABU7JGUPwAAAMCLu2g/AACAAFYhrT8AAAAwnNyPPwAAIAqtbIw/AAAAVA+fmz8AAACgPAO2vwAAAAC8gqU/AAAAmOEwqL8AAEAMcU+gvwAAAKtPTqK/AAAAKI5OoT8AAAAQAlmovwAAABw7krc/AAAAVIwitD8AAADmskCwPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "start",
      "Id",
      "secretary",
      "state"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think George Shultz was very good, I thought he was excellent",
    "question": " If I could, I’d start by asking is there a secretary of state and a secretary of defense in the modern era who you think have done a good job? Who do you think were the best?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAUhecs78AAADgbyuGPwAAAHQWBaA/AAAACLtqpj8AAAA4+fajPwAAAJ6CTbS/AAAARG1Mur8AAABAuhmNvwAAAIDWb5A/AAAAc5sswL8AAAAgr16jvwAAAGCWKJY/AAAAYI22lr8AAAAAKGcdPwAAAPDc1as/AAAAq6Vchj8AAIBnxnatvwAAAFCZxay/AAAAAE3urD8AAAD2Qh6UPwAAALChSYY/AAAA6iResL8AAAAsIoCPPwAAAHxr8p6/AAAA4BA8jL8AAAA8JqbUvwAAAEC/c4A/AAAACHR5pr8AAACA83ORvwAAAAjH662/AAAAZDma3z8AAAD4u0OkPwAAALhad8W/AAAAZKZBs78AAABU7JGUPwAAAMCLu2g/AACAAFYhrT8AAAAwnNyPPwAAIAqtbIw/AAAAVA+fmz8AAACgPAO2vwAAAAC8gqU/AAAAmOEwqL8AAEAMcU+gvwAAAKtPTqK/AAAAKI5OoT8AAAAQAlmovwAAABw7krc/AAAAVIwitD8AAADmskCwPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "start",
      "Id",
      "secretary",
      "state"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I can tell you, I think your last secretary of state and your current secretary of state have not done much",
    "question": " If I could, I’d start by asking is there a secretary of state and a secretary of defense in the modern era who you think have done a good job? Who do you think were the best?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAUhecs78AAADgbyuGPwAAAHQWBaA/AAAACLtqpj8AAAA4+fajPwAAAJ6CTbS/AAAARG1Mur8AAABAuhmNvwAAAIDWb5A/AAAAc5sswL8AAAAgr16jvwAAAGCWKJY/AAAAYI22lr8AAAAAKGcdPwAAAPDc1as/AAAAq6Vchj8AAIBnxnatvwAAAFCZxay/AAAAAE3urD8AAAD2Qh6UPwAAALChSYY/AAAA6iResL8AAAAsIoCPPwAAAHxr8p6/AAAA4BA8jL8AAAA8JqbUvwAAAEC/c4A/AAAACHR5pr8AAACA83ORvwAAAAjH662/AAAAZDma3z8AAAD4u0OkPwAAALhad8W/AAAAZKZBs78AAABU7JGUPwAAAMCLu2g/AACAAFYhrT8AAAAwnNyPPwAAIAqtbIw/AAAAVA+fmz8AAACgPAO2vwAAAAC8gqU/AAAAmOEwqL8AAEAMcU+gvwAAAKtPTqK/AAAAKI5OoT8AAAAQAlmovwAAABw7krc/AAAAVIwitD8AAADmskCwPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "start",
      "Id",
      "secretary",
      "state"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I think John Kerry’s deal with Iran is one of the worst things that I’ve ever seen negotiated of any kind",
    "question": " If I could, I’d start by asking is there a secretary of state and a secretary of defense in the modern era who you think have done a good job? Who do you think were the best?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAUhecs78AAADgbyuGPwAAAHQWBaA/AAAACLtqpj8AAAA4+fajPwAAAJ6CTbS/AAAARG1Mur8AAABAuhmNvwAAAIDWb5A/AAAAc5sswL8AAAAgr16jvwAAAGCWKJY/AAAAYI22lr8AAAAAKGcdPwAAAPDc1as/AAAAq6Vchj8AAIBnxnatvwAAAFCZxay/AAAAAE3urD8AAAD2Qh6UPwAAALChSYY/AAAA6iResL8AAAAsIoCPPwAAAHxr8p6/AAAA4BA8jL8AAAA8JqbUvwAAAEC/c4A/AAAACHR5pr8AAACA83ORvwAAAAjH662/AAAAZDma3z8AAAD4u0OkPwAAALhad8W/AAAAZKZBs78AAABU7JGUPwAAAMCLu2g/AACAAFYhrT8AAAAwnNyPPwAAIAqtbIw/AAAAVA+fmz8AAACgPAO2vwAAAAC8gqU/AAAAmOEwqL8AAEAMcU+gvwAAAKtPTqK/AAAAKI5OoT8AAAAQAlmovwAAABw7krc/AAAAVIwitD8AAADmskCwPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "start",
      "Id",
      "secretary",
      "state"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " It’s just a horrible giveaway",
    "question": " If I could, I’d start by asking is there a secretary of state and a secretary of defense in the modern era who you think have done a good job? Who do you think were the best?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAUhecs78AAADgbyuGPwAAAHQWBaA/AAAACLtqpj8AAAA4+fajPwAAAJ6CTbS/AAAARG1Mur8AAABAuhmNvwAAAIDWb5A/AAAAc5sswL8AAAAgr16jvwAAAGCWKJY/AAAAYI22lr8AAAAAKGcdPwAAAPDc1as/AAAAq6Vchj8AAIBnxnatvwAAAFCZxay/AAAAAE3urD8AAAD2Qh6UPwAAALChSYY/AAAA6iResL8AAAAsIoCPPwAAAHxr8p6/AAAA4BA8jL8AAAA8JqbUvwAAAEC/c4A/AAAACHR5pr8AAACA83ORvwAAAAjH662/AAAAZDma3z8AAAD4u0OkPwAAALhad8W/AAAAZKZBs78AAABU7JGUPwAAAMCLu2g/AACAAFYhrT8AAAAwnNyPPwAAIAqtbIw/AAAAVA+fmz8AAACgPAO2vwAAAAC8gqU/AAAAmOEwqL8AAEAMcU+gvwAAAKtPTqK/AAAAKI5OoT8AAAAQAlmovwAAABw7krc/AAAAVIwitD8AAADmskCwPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "start",
      "Id",
      "secretary",
      "state"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " No, other than to say, we’re working hard, I think we’re all in the same business of trying to make our country better, a better place, so we have something in common",
    "question": " Do you want to start out?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQN4NmT8AAABARQiEvwAAAKBCBbE/AAAAAPIbs78AAABA8Na7PwAAACDao7O/AAAAADANt78AAABgAIOwPwAAAEDfl7a/AAAAILIQpD8AAACA8e6bvwAAAIDTJbg/AAAA4I9Apr8AAACg7o5xPwAAAMAc58I/AAAAIAsHyT8AAAAASrbGPwAAAECzXaC/AAAAQKfhwT8AAACAE3jIvwAAAKAMbKq/AAAAwE8xtz8AAAAgGd6jPwAAAKCTML4/AAAAwN+Grz8AAAAATTrYvwAAAKAs+cK/AAAAgMZirb8AAAAA7x/EPwAAACDnisi/AAAAgMhr4z8AAAAghsXLPwAAAIC1O82/AAAA4JdFnb8AAACgMTOnvwAAAOCtyKi/AAAAAPo9ob8AAAAg71OwvwAAAMCB844/AAAAQNr8ub8AAAAgJSOmvwAAAGDyR50/AAAAAIU3rj8AAACAohe5PwAAACDde6s/AAAAQClroT8AAADgZEC6vwAAAKA//Z8/AAAAQPHGob8AAADAdd23Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I’ve been treated very, very badly by The Washington Post, but, you know, I guess — and I’m your neighbor, I’m your neighbor right down the road, in fact we’re actually giving a press conference there in a little while, I think your people are going to be there",
    "question": " Do you want to start out?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQN4NmT8AAABARQiEvwAAAKBCBbE/AAAAAPIbs78AAABA8Na7PwAAACDao7O/AAAAADANt78AAABgAIOwPwAAAEDfl7a/AAAAILIQpD8AAACA8e6bvwAAAIDTJbg/AAAA4I9Apr8AAACg7o5xPwAAAMAc58I/AAAAIAsHyT8AAAAASrbGPwAAAECzXaC/AAAAQKfhwT8AAACAE3jIvwAAAKAMbKq/AAAAwE8xtz8AAAAgGd6jPwAAAKCTML4/AAAAwN+Grz8AAAAATTrYvwAAAKAs+cK/AAAAgMZirb8AAAAA7x/EPwAAACDnisi/AAAAgMhr4z8AAAAghsXLPwAAAIC1O82/AAAA4JdFnb8AAACgMTOnvwAAAOCtyKi/AAAAAPo9ob8AAAAg71OwvwAAAMCB844/AAAAQNr8ub8AAAAgJSOmvwAAAGDyR50/AAAAAIU3rj8AAACAohe5PwAAACDde6s/AAAAQClroT8AAADgZEC6vwAAAKA//Z8/AAAAQPHGob8AAADAdd23Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " And by the way, Bob Costa is an excellent reporter, I’ve found him to be just an excellent reporter",
    "question": " Do you want to start out?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQN4NmT8AAABARQiEvwAAAKBCBbE/AAAAAPIbs78AAABA8Na7PwAAACDao7O/AAAAADANt78AAABgAIOwPwAAAEDfl7a/AAAAILIQpD8AAACA8e6bvwAAAIDTJbg/AAAA4I9Apr8AAACg7o5xPwAAAMAc58I/AAAAIAsHyT8AAAAASrbGPwAAAECzXaC/AAAAQKfhwT8AAACAE3jIvwAAAKAMbKq/AAAAwE8xtz8AAAAgGd6jPwAAAKCTML4/AAAAwN+Grz8AAAAATTrYvwAAAKAs+cK/AAAAgMZirb8AAAAA7x/EPwAAACDnisi/AAAAgMhr4z8AAAAghsXLPwAAAIC1O82/AAAA4JdFnb8AAACgMTOnvwAAAOCtyKi/AAAAAPo9ob8AAAAg71OwvwAAAMCB844/AAAAQNr8ub8AAAAgJSOmvwAAAGDyR50/AAAAAIU3rj8AAACAohe5PwAAACDde6s/AAAAQClroT8AAADgZEC6vwAAAKA//Z8/AAAAQPHGob8AAADAdd23Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " I should tell you, because I have to give you the good and the bad",
    "question": " Do you want to start out?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQN4NmT8AAABARQiEvwAAAKBCBbE/AAAAAPIbs78AAABA8Na7PwAAACDao7O/AAAAADANt78AAABgAIOwPwAAAEDfl7a/AAAAILIQpD8AAACA8e6bvwAAAIDTJbg/AAAA4I9Apr8AAACg7o5xPwAAAMAc58I/AAAAIAsHyT8AAAAASrbGPwAAAECzXaC/AAAAQKfhwT8AAACAE3jIvwAAAKAMbKq/AAAAwE8xtz8AAAAgGd6jPwAAAKCTML4/AAAAwN+Grz8AAAAATTrYvwAAAKAs+cK/AAAAgMZirb8AAAAA7x/EPwAAACDnisi/AAAAgMhr4z8AAAAghsXLPwAAAIC1O82/AAAA4JdFnb8AAACgMTOnvwAAAOCtyKi/AAAAAPo9ob8AAAAg71OwvwAAAMCB844/AAAAQNr8ub8AAAAgJSOmvwAAAGDyR50/AAAAAIU3rj8AAACAohe5PwAAACDde6s/AAAAQClroT8AAADgZEC6vwAAAKA//Z8/AAAAQPHGob8AAADAdd23Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Not that he does me any favors, because he doesn’t, but he’s a real professional",
    "question": " Do you want to start out?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAQN4NmT8AAABARQiEvwAAAKBCBbE/AAAAAPIbs78AAABA8Na7PwAAACDao7O/AAAAADANt78AAABgAIOwPwAAAEDfl7a/AAAAILIQpD8AAACA8e6bvwAAAIDTJbg/AAAA4I9Apr8AAACg7o5xPwAAAMAc58I/AAAAIAsHyT8AAAAASrbGPwAAAECzXaC/AAAAQKfhwT8AAACAE3jIvwAAAKAMbKq/AAAAwE8xtz8AAAAgGd6jPwAAAKCTML4/AAAAwN+Grz8AAAAATTrYvwAAAKAs+cK/AAAAgMZirb8AAAAA7x/EPwAAACDnisi/AAAAgMhr4z8AAAAghsXLPwAAAIC1O82/AAAA4JdFnb8AAACgMTOnvwAAAOCtyKi/AAAAAPo9ob8AAAAg71OwvwAAAMCB844/AAAAQNr8ub8AAAAgJSOmvwAAAGDyR50/AAAAAIU3rj8AAACAohe5PwAAACDde6s/AAAAQClroT8AAADgZEC6vwAAAKA//Z8/AAAAQPHGob8AAADAdd23Pw==",
    "important_question": [
      "want"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Well, I hadn’t thought of doing it, but if you want I can give you some of the names… Walid Phares, who you probably know, PhD, adviser to the House of Representatives caucus, and counter-terrorism expert; Carter Page, PhD; George Papadopoulos, he’s an energy and oil consultant, excellent guy; the Honorable Joe Schmitz, [former] inspector general at the Department of Defense; [retired] Lt",
    "question": " Thank you… We’ve heard you’re going to be announcing your foreign policy team shortly… Any you can share with us?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAHGLqo78AAADbJnDAvwAAAPD8i4e/AAAAINPzwr8AAAC0y2uzPwAAAPQb78K/AAAAJupru78AAACYriLBPwAAAADAoWK/AAAAoG2qjj8AAABglOWZPwAAAEjV9b4/AAAAZxLnub8AAACAKReaPwAAAFgwBcA/AAAAADcgib8AAAAUS3u7PwAAAHhCW6g/AAAAAF+ZWD8AAADw9MaMvwAAAGiwgsO/AAAAP3U9rD8AAAAEECq/PwAAAGTA76c/AAAATiXdwT8AAAAA9K67vwAAAPMUiLe/AACADU9+sj8AAABRNma5PwAAAAZ01r6/AAAAKD/Fvj8AAACwO3vEPwAAAKCXwZ2/AAAAaA9bpj8AAAAo3OCtvwAAAB7nLbE/AAAA9RGvrj8AAAB0RluxPwAAYO+YYqW/AAAA7k0Zub8AAACg5b2PvwAAgLnghr2/AAAAwGLBuL8AAADICQayPwAAADBjK56/AAAAQI7mo78AAIC/tZKmvwAAAEp5Qbg/AAAA8xAuoD8AAABeUJqnPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Thank",
      "Weve",
      "youre",
      "team"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Gen",
    "question": " Thank you… We’ve heard you’re going to be announcing your foreign policy team shortly… Any you can share with us?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAHGLqo78AAADbJnDAvwAAAPD8i4e/AAAAINPzwr8AAAC0y2uzPwAAAPQb78K/AAAAJupru78AAACYriLBPwAAAADAoWK/AAAAoG2qjj8AAABglOWZPwAAAEjV9b4/AAAAZxLnub8AAACAKReaPwAAAFgwBcA/AAAAADcgib8AAAAUS3u7PwAAAHhCW6g/AAAAAF+ZWD8AAADw9MaMvwAAAGiwgsO/AAAAP3U9rD8AAAAEECq/PwAAAGTA76c/AAAATiXdwT8AAAAA9K67vwAAAPMUiLe/AACADU9+sj8AAABRNma5PwAAAAZ01r6/AAAAKD/Fvj8AAACwO3vEPwAAAKCXwZ2/AAAAaA9bpj8AAAAo3OCtvwAAAB7nLbE/AAAA9RGvrj8AAAB0RluxPwAAYO+YYqW/AAAA7k0Zub8AAACg5b2PvwAAgLnghr2/AAAAwGLBuL8AAADICQayPwAAADBjK56/AAAAQI7mo78AAIC/tZKmvwAAAEp5Qbg/AAAA8xAuoD8AAABeUJqnPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Thank",
      "Weve",
      "youre",
      "team"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Keith Kellogg; and I have quite a few more",
    "question": " Thank you… We’ve heard you’re going to be announcing your foreign policy team shortly… Any you can share with us?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAHGLqo78AAADbJnDAvwAAAPD8i4e/AAAAINPzwr8AAAC0y2uzPwAAAPQb78K/AAAAJupru78AAACYriLBPwAAAADAoWK/AAAAoG2qjj8AAABglOWZPwAAAEjV9b4/AAAAZxLnub8AAACAKReaPwAAAFgwBcA/AAAAADcgib8AAAAUS3u7PwAAAHhCW6g/AAAAAF+ZWD8AAADw9MaMvwAAAGiwgsO/AAAAP3U9rD8AAAAEECq/PwAAAGTA76c/AAAATiXdwT8AAAAA9K67vwAAAPMUiLe/AACADU9+sj8AAABRNma5PwAAAAZ01r6/AAAAKD/Fvj8AAACwO3vEPwAAAKCXwZ2/AAAAaA9bpj8AAAAo3OCtvwAAAB7nLbE/AAAA9RGvrj8AAAB0RluxPwAAYO+YYqW/AAAA7k0Zub8AAACg5b2PvwAAgLnghr2/AAAAwGLBuL8AAADICQayPwAAADBjK56/AAAAQI7mo78AAIC/tZKmvwAAAEp5Qbg/AAAA8xAuoD8AAABeUJqnPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Thank",
      "Weve",
      "youre",
      "team"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " But that’s a group of some of the people that we are dealing with",
    "question": " Thank you… We’ve heard you’re going to be announcing your foreign policy team shortly… Any you can share with us?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAHGLqo78AAADbJnDAvwAAAPD8i4e/AAAAINPzwr8AAAC0y2uzPwAAAPQb78K/AAAAJupru78AAACYriLBPwAAAADAoWK/AAAAoG2qjj8AAABglOWZPwAAAEjV9b4/AAAAZxLnub8AAACAKReaPwAAAFgwBcA/AAAAADcgib8AAAAUS3u7PwAAAHhCW6g/AAAAAF+ZWD8AAADw9MaMvwAAAGiwgsO/AAAAP3U9rD8AAAAEECq/PwAAAGTA76c/AAAATiXdwT8AAAAA9K67vwAAAPMUiLe/AACADU9+sj8AAABRNma5PwAAAAZ01r6/AAAAKD/Fvj8AAACwO3vEPwAAAKCXwZ2/AAAAaA9bpj8AAAAo3OCtvwAAAB7nLbE/AAAA9RGvrj8AAAB0RluxPwAAYO+YYqW/AAAA7k0Zub8AAACg5b2PvwAAgLnghr2/AAAAwGLBuL8AAADICQayPwAAADBjK56/AAAAQI7mo78AAIC/tZKmvwAAAEp5Qbg/AAAA8xAuoD8AAABeUJqnPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Thank",
      "Weve",
      "youre",
      "team"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " We have many other people in different aspects of what we do, but that’s a representative group",
    "question": " Thank you… We’ve heard you’re going to be announcing your foreign policy team shortly… Any you can share with us?",
    "question_vector": "AAAAHGLqo78AAADbJnDAvwAAAPD8i4e/AAAAINPzwr8AAAC0y2uzPwAAAPQb78K/AAAAJupru78AAACYriLBPwAAAADAoWK/AAAAoG2qjj8AAABglOWZPwAAAEjV9b4/AAAAZxLnub8AAACAKReaPwAAAFgwBcA/AAAAADcgib8AAAAUS3u7PwAAAHhCW6g/AAAAAF+ZWD8AAADw9MaMvwAAAGiwgsO/AAAAP3U9rD8AAAAEECq/PwAAAGTA76c/AAAATiXdwT8AAAAA9K67vwAAAPMUiLe/AACADU9+sj8AAABRNma5PwAAAAZ01r6/AAAAKD/Fvj8AAACwO3vEPwAAAKCXwZ2/AAAAaA9bpj8AAAAo3OCtvwAAAB7nLbE/AAAA9RGvrj8AAAB0RluxPwAAYO+YYqW/AAAA7k0Zub8AAACg5b2PvwAAgLnghr2/AAAAwGLBuL8AAADICQayPwAAADBjK56/AAAAQI7mo78AAIC/tZKmvwAAAEp5Qbg/AAAA8xAuoD8AAABeUJqnPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Thank",
      "Weve",
      "youre",
      "team"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " New building",
    "question": " Mr. Trump, welcome to the Washington Post. Thank you for making time to meet with our editorial board.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfFy9hT8AAADY9je9PwAAAKpl86I/AAAAoJGWkD8AAACEwbixPwAAAKAB/b6/AAAAFG9zvr8AAAAA6qhFPwAAAOCNE66/AAAAMKzal78AAEDm6EG8vwAAAHKaFbY/AAAAuzbPvb8AAABAP3SMPwAAALxMH8E/AAAAK5IIsj8AAADlEd2CvwAAACSNEam/AAAAWONJgL8AAAAQgw90vwAAAFjAc6U/AAAATu1btj8AAADAKpORvwAAAOCur0A/AAAAuDBtrj8AAAAAXFvUvwAAAJwUAri/AAAAEBt6Zr8AAAC2KjySPwAAAIgzP6u/AAAAdR1t3D8AAAAwXFS7PwAAALjT9rS/AAAAANfHer8AAADUVJqnvwAAAGQyTqC/AADAXMWhoz8AAABsGqWlPwAAAMDJW3M/AAAAAEx4t78AAAAoAgObPwAAgASuRaU/AABAJXbKqb8AAADINBC1PwAAAEwO57e/AAAAoCNVqz8AAAAIgt+xvwAAACQIPq2/AAAARMDXpD8AAABoaQauPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Thank",
      "Post.",
      "Trump",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Yes this is very nice",
    "question": " Mr. Trump, welcome to the Washington Post. Thank you for making time to meet with our editorial board.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfFy9hT8AAADY9je9PwAAAKpl86I/AAAAoJGWkD8AAACEwbixPwAAAKAB/b6/AAAAFG9zvr8AAAAA6qhFPwAAAOCNE66/AAAAMKzal78AAEDm6EG8vwAAAHKaFbY/AAAAuzbPvb8AAABAP3SMPwAAALxMH8E/AAAAK5IIsj8AAADlEd2CvwAAACSNEam/AAAAWONJgL8AAAAQgw90vwAAAFjAc6U/AAAATu1btj8AAADAKpORvwAAAOCur0A/AAAAuDBtrj8AAAAAXFvUvwAAAJwUAri/AAAAEBt6Zr8AAAC2KjySPwAAAIgzP6u/AAAAdR1t3D8AAAAwXFS7PwAAALjT9rS/AAAAANfHer8AAADUVJqnvwAAAGQyTqC/AADAXMWhoz8AAABsGqWlPwAAAMDJW3M/AAAAAEx4t78AAAAoAgObPwAAgASuRaU/AABAJXbKqb8AAADINBC1PwAAAEwO57e/AAAAoCNVqz8AAAAIgt+xvwAAACQIPq2/AAAARMDXpD8AAABoaQauPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Thank",
      "Post.",
      "Trump",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "answer": " Good luck with it",
    "question": " Mr. Trump, welcome to the Washington Post. Thank you for making time to meet with our editorial board.",
    "question_vector": "AAAAfFy9hT8AAADY9je9PwAAAKpl86I/AAAAoJGWkD8AAACEwbixPwAAAKAB/b6/AAAAFG9zvr8AAAAA6qhFPwAAAOCNE66/AAAAMKzal78AAEDm6EG8vwAAAHKaFbY/AAAAuzbPvb8AAABAP3SMPwAAALxMH8E/AAAAK5IIsj8AAADlEd2CvwAAACSNEam/AAAAWONJgL8AAAAQgw90vwAAAFjAc6U/AAAATu1btj8AAADAKpORvwAAAOCur0A/AAAAuDBtrj8AAAAAXFvUvwAAAJwUAri/AAAAEBt6Zr8AAAC2KjySPwAAAIgzP6u/AAAAdR1t3D8AAAAwXFS7PwAAALjT9rS/AAAAANfHer8AAADUVJqnvwAAAGQyTqC/AADAXMWhoz8AAABsGqWlPwAAAMDJW3M/AAAAAEx4t78AAAAoAgObPwAAgASuRaU/AABAJXbKqb8AAADINBC1PwAAAEwO57e/AAAAoCNVqz8AAAAIgt+xvwAAACQIPq2/AAAARMDXpD8AAABoaQauPw==",
    "important_question": [
      "Thank",
      "Post.",
      "Trump",
      "time"
    ]
  }
]